<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>torrez market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/torrez-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:40:29 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>torrez market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>ToRReZ Announces Clean Exit Plan</title>
		<link>/torrez-announces-clean-exit-plan/</link>
					<comments>/torrez-announces-clean-exit-plan/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 12:40:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market shutdown]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[torrez market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1032</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the world’s largest and most popular darknet markets announced their impending closure on Thursday, creating a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/torrez-announces-clean-exit-plan/">ToRReZ Announces Clean Exit Plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the world’s largest and most popular darknet markets <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ddd40e047b7aec316d5f" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">announced</a> their impending closure on Thursday, creating a substantial power vacuum soon to be filled by rival markets. ToRReZ, which had been in rather steady operation since February 2020, credited its success to the slow, organic nature of its growth, bowing out at a time when it enjoys peak popularity.</p>



<p>Following examples set by White House Market in October and Cannazon in November, ToRReZ admins pledged a clean and honest exit, specifying the chance for active users to tie up loose ends. This includes the shipping and finalizing of outstanding orders, and the chance for all parties to withdrawal remaining funds.</p>



<p>ToRReZ had close to 50,000 listings in total on its site days before the notice and by its count had registered close to 300,000 users.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="462" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-1-1024x462.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1034" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-1-1024x462.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-1-300x135.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-1-768x346.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-1.jpg 1215w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Message currently displayed on the ToRReZ main market page.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>A <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FGx9rw-UUAE78_m?format=jpg&amp;name=large" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">PGP-signed message</a> now greets users when logging in to the market, replacing all browsing and order placement functionality. It states that the market will be kept online for “at least two to three weeks,” encouraging buyers and vendors to resolve any outstanding disputes and provide necessary information about the status of packages still in transit.</p>



<p>“Do not be a dick to each other,” pleads ToRReZ admin <em>mrblonde</em> in the message. “We give you an opportunity to leave the market with your gear or funds so help us to achieve that.”</p>



<p>“<em>It has been a great pleasure to work with most vendors and users. We are aware that we leave quite a big gap in darknet markets but we hope most of you will find a new home…</em></p>



<p><em>Please give a chance to the smaller markets, which are not that loud as others. This is exactly how we became no 1 &#8211; being quiet and doing our job, serving customers 24/7 for 675 fucking days.” – mrblonde, ToRReZ admin</em></p>



<p>ToRReZ broke new ground in the operation of darknet markets by doing things differently from the competition: they supported 2/3 multisig for Bitcoin transactions and allowed vendors to accept up to 4 different cryptos for payment (BTC, XMR, LTC, and ZEC). Since inception, the market claimed to be “the first community-driven market,” encouraging users to submit their feedback on how to make it more effective.</p>



<p>The market enjoyed a slow-and-steady rise to fame across the course of its near-two years in existence, receiving its first big clearnet mention shortly after the six-month mark of its operation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Six new darknet markets have already launched in the past five days according to my inbox. Expect a lot of scams.<br><br>Empire refugees are flocking to Monopoly and White House markets. ToRReZ looks interesting, Yellow Brick is trusted by some but has scammed before.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1298732392190861312?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 26, 2020</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The trend of gentle market closures – which could be considered “retirements” – is an affair that has thus far been unique to 2021, with most prior darknet market closures tending to be more violent, sinister or at the very least, unexplained in nature.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/torrez-announces-clean-exit-plan/">ToRReZ Announces Clean Exit Plan</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/torrez-announces-clean-exit-plan/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>‘Stronger than Fentanyl’: New Synthetic Found in ‘Oxy’ Pills on the Darknet</title>
		<link>/stronger-than-fentanyl-new-synthetic-found-in-oxy-pills-on-the-darknet/</link>
					<comments>/stronger-than-fentanyl-new-synthetic-found-in-oxy-pills-on-the-darknet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 08 Dec 2021 20:36:29 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Isotonitazene]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[opiod]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[torrez market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1009</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Deaths involving newer designer opioids are on the rise across the United States; some of which are readily</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-than-fentanyl-new-synthetic-found-in-oxy-pills-on-the-darknet/">‘Stronger than Fentanyl’: New Synthetic Found in ‘Oxy’ Pills on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Deaths involving newer designer opioids are <a href="https://thehill.com/homenews/state-watch/583563-opioids-more-powerful-than-fentanyl-found-in-dc-as-overdoses-rise" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">on the rise</a> across the United States; some of which are readily purchasable on darknet markets. Particularly hard hit is the Washington D.C. area, where the substances are being found in syringes and powders recovered from overdose victims. The chemicals are usually added as adulterants in brand name products &#8212; a practice which often poses significant health risks to the consumer.</p>



<p>Recently-synthesized opiate analogs like sotonitazene, protonitazene and isotonitazene are the new substitutes for fentanyl, which is facing increasing federal scrutiny and abolishment from most darknet markets. The biggest problem, according to the Centers for Disease Control and Prevention, is that these analogs are <a href="https://www.deadiversion.usdoj.gov/drug_chem_info/isotonitazene.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">even more powerful than fentanyl</a> (which is already 50-100 times more potent than morphine).</p>



<p>“We could be on the precipice of something devastating,” <a href="https://www.wusa9.com/article/news/local/dc/new-powerful-opioid-found-on-dc-streets/65-7f37d942-3660-419f-9eab-d9f12ec9ca80" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">said</a> Alexandra Evans, the chemist responsible for discovering protonitazene in the D.C. drug samples. &#8220;We&#8217;ve already seen mass fatalities because of fentanyl overdoses. Since this is more potent than fentanyl, we do expect an uptick in overdoses.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="884" height="180" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1011" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1.png 884w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-300x61.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-768x156.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 884px) 100vw, 884px" /><figcaption><em>ToRReZ Market listing for “Oxycodone” 30 mg pills “made with Isotonitazene.”</em></figcaption></figure>



<p><a href="https://www.deadiversion.usdoj.gov/drug_chem_info/isotonitazene.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Isotonitazene</a>, one of the three analogs found in the recovered drug samples, is currently for sale in different formulations on at least three major darknet markets, including the ToRReZ, Dark0de and Cartel marketplaces. Though one listing from a China-based supplier was for the chemical in its pure form, most of the time it was mentioned in the listing as being part of a formulation for a different brand, such as Dilaudid and Oxycodone.</p>



<p>A separate wholesale vendor of the product displays the following information about it in their current listing:</p>



<p>“<em>Isotonitazene is a benzimidazole derived opioid analgesic drug related to etonitazene, which has been sold as a designer drug.</em></p>



<p><em>It has only around half the potency of etonitazene in animal studies, but this still makes it a similar strength to fentanyl and its analogues, and consequently isotonitazene can be expected to pose a significant risk of producing life-threatening respiratory depression, as well as other typical opioid side effects such as sedation, itching, nausea and vomiting.” – from vendor MicroDroper</em></p>



<p>Isotonitazene has been blamed for overdose deaths as early as April 2019. Though a few vendors claim the substance is “legal in most of the world” in their listings, it was <a href="https://www.federalregister.gov/documents/2020/08/20/2020-17951/schedules-of-controlled-substances-temporary-placement-of-isotonitazene-in-schedule-i" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">added</a> to the US DEA Schedule I drugs list in August 2020, rendering it effectively illegal in that country.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stronger-than-fentanyl-new-synthetic-found-in-oxy-pills-on-the-darknet/">‘Stronger than Fentanyl’: New Synthetic Found in ‘Oxy’ Pills on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/stronger-than-fentanyl-new-synthetic-found-in-oxy-pills-on-the-darknet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:42 by W3 Total Cache
-->