<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>coinbase &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/coinbase/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 13:37:11 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>coinbase &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Coinbase Puts Self-Described Terrorist Back in Prison</title>
		<link>/coinbase-puts-self-described-terrorist-back-in-prison/</link>
					<comments>/coinbase-puts-self-described-terrorist-back-in-prison/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 28 Dec 2021 13:37:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[coinbase]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1044</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A proactive communication by Coinbase is ultimately responsible for the re-imprisonment of Khuram Iqbal, a radicalized UK student</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coinbase-puts-self-described-terrorist-back-in-prison/">Coinbase Puts Self-Described Terrorist Back in Prison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A proactive communication by Coinbase is ultimately responsible for the <a href="https://bangladesh.kivazen.com/the-self-styled-father-of-terror-from-cardiff-who-was-jailed-for-trading-bitcoin-in-the-dark-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">re-imprisonment of Khuram Iqbal</a>, a radicalized UK student who once titled himself “the father of terrorism” online. Iqbal’s account was initially flagged by the cryptocurrency exchange for sending Bitcoin to a wallet known to be associated with a darknet market for credit card information.</p>



<p>Iqbal, 29, was <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-wales-59748896" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">jailed</a> six days ago after local law enforcement apprehended him at home in Cardiff, Wales. He is being sentenced to 16 months for failure to report ownership of a cryptocurrency account and associated email address per the conditions of his 2016 release.</p>



<p>In a somewhat unusual twist, it was recently revealed that <a href="https://protos.com/coinbase-terrorism-snitches-cardiff-trading-crypto-bitcoin-dark-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Coinbase notified authorities</a> that Iqbal was using cryptocurrency for illicit purposes, instead of responding to a law enforcement request, as is more often the case. The exchange made the decision after having established his identity and considered his account actions potentially “terrorist” in nature.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A convicted terrorist from Cardiff has been jailed again over secret cryptocurrency trading on the dark web. Khuram Iqbal was first imprisoned in 2014 for having copies of Al-Qaeda&#39;s Inspire magazine and sharing terrorist information <a href="https://t.co/pnCpwpzFvc">https://t.co/pnCpwpzFvc</a></p>&mdash; William Baldét MBE (@WillBaldet) <a href="https://twitter.com/WillBaldet/status/1475563450692743175?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 27, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Iqbal made 392 transactions from his secret Coinbase account between Nov. 2017 and March 2021, sending funds to the darknet marketplace three times during January 2020. It is not known if Iqbal’s recent activity had anything to do with his old terrorist aspirations, but his failure to report ownership of the Coinbase</p>



<p>In 2011 and 2012, Iqbal attempted to join “the Jihadist cause;” first in Kenya, and later, in Turkey, per <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-wales-29167225" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a> by the <em>BBC</em>. He was unable to find a new home abroad and instead returned to Wales, where he allegedly engaged in the dissemination of “videos and texts glorifying terrorism.” During this time, Iqbal posted his content under the name <em>Abu Irhaab</em>, which is Arabic for “Father of Terrorism”.</p>



<p>In all, Iqbal was found to have shared 848 links to “extreme content” on social media by the time of his arrest, using several different Facebook and Twitter accounts in the process.</p>



<p>Iqbal was first apprehended in October 2013 and sentenced to three years and three months on charges related to the dissemination of terrorist publications. He was released “on license” in 2015 but later returned to finish his sentence the following year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/coinbase-puts-self-described-terrorist-back-in-prison/">Coinbase Puts Self-Described Terrorist Back in Prison</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/coinbase-puts-self-described-terrorist-back-in-prison/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:36 by W3 Total Cache
-->