<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>alphabay &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/alphabay/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:42:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>alphabay &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</title>
		<link>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seven months after the return of DeSnake, one of the original AlphaBay’s two administrators, the new incarnation of</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seven months after the <a href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">return of DeSnake</a>, one of the original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s two administrators, the new incarnation of the infamous darknet market is once again on top of the competition &#8212; sans Hydra, the Russian-language darknet market which still dwarfs all others in sales volume. The distinction comes about as its closest competitor in size, World Market, has been largely <a href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">deemed no longer operational</a>, even if the site remains technically accessible.</p>



<p>The rise of the “new” <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> is not something that much of the darknet market community was expecting as many feared it was simply an extravagant “honeypot” operation designed to collect the credentials of buyers and vendors. For its first few months, the market remained relatively void of users and activity. However, with over half a year of steady operation under its belt and an ever-increasing base of users, these fears have largely subsided, and AlphaBay currently enjoys its greatest degree of popularity yet in this new manifestation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">In 2017 the largest darknet market was seized, Alphabay &#8211; leading to the tragic suicide of its alleged admin Alex Cazes.<br><br>Recently its co-admin/fugitive DeSnake returned, relaunching the site in Alex&#39;s honor. With World&#39;s demise, Alphabay is close to reclaiming its throne as #1.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1506643215847411712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>AlphaBay now hosts over 22,000 listings and is home 5,228 vendors and 340,000+ buyers, according to statistics maintained by the market. It is now a Monero (XMR)-only market and forces its users to operate under some of the strictest guidelines to ever be implemented by a darknet market. These include a no-weapons and no-fentanyl policy, short-timed finalization periods, and an advanced captcha system that has proved capable of preventing DDOS attacks from occurring.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="934" height="406" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1409" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png 934w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-300x130.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-768x334.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 934px) 100vw, 934px" /><figcaption>lphabay</figcaption></figure>



<p><em>After a slow re-start, activity at AlphaBay is now bustling.</em></p>



<p>The recent string of darknet market closures in 2022 has also helped AlphaBay’s propulsion to the top of the list. World Market, previously the largest (English-speaking) market by sales volume, has all but closed shop, as admins on Dread have repeatedly warned users against making new deposits to avoid losses in the likely event of an exit scam.</p>



<p>Within the past week, World Market added the following message to its main market page, although accounts registered within the last six months (sans brand new accounts) are still unable to log in to the market:</p>



<p>“<em>World Market is operational again, listing images will be restored soon, if you are missing a deposit open a ticket.”</em></p>



<p>AlphaBay also seems to be making some strides in its promises to delivery a decentralized darknet market – the first of its kind – that can theoretically continue to operate even if service provided by an operator is discontinued, for whatever reason. Upcoming tasks have been scheduled in the market’s <a href="http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/roadmap" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">roadmap</a> for the project, and include building payment modules, multisig and escrow core functions, and a way for network operators to provide “initial decentralized infrastructure report.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</title>
		<link>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/</link>
					<comments>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What was initially believed to be hackers at work on Jan 31 turned out to be the world’s</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/">Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What was initially believed to be hackers at work on Jan 31 turned out to be the <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">worl</a><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">d’s</a><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> biggest-ever federal seizure of funds</a>, involving the recovery of some $3.6 billion in Bitcoin stolen from Bitfinex during a 2016 hack. The original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay darknet market</a> was mentioned as a money laundering utility for the funds in court documents, though the exact amount of BTC moved through the market was not mentioned.</p>



<p>Husband Ilya Lichtenstein, 34, and wife Heather Morgan (aka ‘Razzlekhan’), 31, are being <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">charged</a> with conspiracy to launder 119,754 BTC stolen off the Bitfinex exchange, which equates to $4.5 billion at today’s prices. The remainder of the funds, about 25,000 BTC, was moved through <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> and mixing services not specified by name.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">One overlooked detail in the Razzlekahn arrest.  Almost all the money went through AlphaBay, using it as a mixer.  The feds were able to see through this because they seized AlphaBay.  Its amazing how, even years after, darknet market seizures pay dividends to the feds.</p>&mdash; Nicholas Weaver (@ncweaver) <a href="https://twitter.com/ncweaver/status/1491118233973571585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 8, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>A Justice Department search warrant issued last week led to authorities’ decryption of a cloud-stored file containing the private keys for Bitcoin addresses known to hold stolen funds. Blockchain analysis led to the connection with the husband-and-wife pair, with transactions linking accounts opened under their names to laundered funds. About $2.9 million ended up in bank accounts belonging to Lichtenstein and Morgan, according to prosecutors.</p>



<p>Deputy Attorney General Lisa Monaco described the couple’s laundering operations as creating a “labyrinth of cryptocurrency transactions,” including transaction automation, using darknet markets like AlphaBay to break up blockchain linkages. The pair also cashed out BTC to other coins on various crypto exchanges using a money laundering tactic known as “chain hopping.” They attempted to launder additional funds by converting them into the anonymized crypto Monero (XMR).</p>



<p>As AlphaBay was seized by the US Justice Department in July 2017, security researchers suspect the two were <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">identified thro</a><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ugh internal t</a><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ransaction logs</a> kept by the market and obtained by investigators during the seizure. This associating information rendered any obfuscation attempts made by Lichtenstein and Morgan useless, thereby allowing authorities to locate all stolen Bitfinex funds the duo attempted to launder through the market.</p>



<p>Defense attorneys for Lichtenstein and Morgan <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">cla</a><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">i</a><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">m</a> their clients knew they were under investigation as early as November 2021 but nevertheless remained in the country, as rationale as to why they were not flight risks for their upcoming trial. They face up to 20 years behind bars if convicted.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/">Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</title>
		<link>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/</link>
					<comments>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A federal judge ruled on Monday that a 30-year-old Michigan man will spend seven years behind bars for</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/">US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A federal judge <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdpa/pr/judge-sentences-michigan-man-7-years-prison-hacking-upmc-hr-databases-and-stealing" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ruled</a> on Monday that a 30-year-old Michigan man will spend seven years behind bars for stealing personal information from 65,000 healthcare workers and selling it on the darknet. Justin Sean Johnson, who went by the vendor names “TheDearthStar” and “DearthyStar”, was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdpa/pr/michigan-man-arrested-2014-hack-upmc-hr-databases-and-theft-employees-personal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in June 2020 on charges of conspiracy, wire fraud and aggravated identity theft stemming from the 2014 hack of University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC). He plead guilty to those charges.</p>



<p>During several database breaches starting in late 2013 and continuing through early 2014, Johnson hacked into the UPMC databases several times undetected, collecting tens of thousands of records containing names, Social Security numbers, addresses and salary information. He then packaged the data for sale on the AlphaBay and Evolution markets where it was quickly purchased and used to file thousands of fraudulent tax returns.</p>



<p>Much of the stolen personal information was collected from UPMC employee W2 tax forms in quick bursts over a short period in January and February 2014.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="666" height="272" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-897" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.jpg 666w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-300x123.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 666px) 100vw, 666px" /><figcaption><em>TheDearthyStar item listing on AlphaBay in 2014. Source: Bleeping Computer</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In all, the Johnson’s customers managed to collect approximately $1.7 million in fraudulent tax refunds from the IRS. Most of this money was used to purchase Amazon gift cards that were spent on products sent to Venezuela through a Miami-based reshipping company.</p>



<p>The UPMC is Pennsylvania’s largest healthcare provider, employing close to 90,000 workers; all of which were thought to be at least partly affected by the breach.</p>



<p>Between 2014 and 2017, Johnson also stole 90,000 sets of personal information from other sources, which was then also sold on various darknet forums for the purposes of identity theft or bank fraud.</p>



<p>He was sentenced on Monday to 60 months in prison for conspiracy to defraud the United States and 24 months for aggravated identity theft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/">US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark.fail Admin Wary of AlphaBay</title>
		<link>/dark-fail-admin-wary-of-alphabay/</link>
					<comments>/dark-fail-admin-wary-of-alphabay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 16 Oct 2021 11:24:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=883</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The usually tight-lipped darknet market link provider at Dark.fail dropped a vague but real warning about the recently</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-wary-of-alphabay/">Dark.fail Admin Wary of AlphaBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The usually tight-lipped darknet market link provider at <a href="https://dark.fail/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dark.fail</a> dropped a <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1448672675036024834" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">vague but real warning</a> about the recently ‘restarted’ <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/">Alph</a><a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a</a><a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/">Bay</a> on Twitter yesterday, reminding potential customers that law enforcement can seize private keys “just like anything else” during a takedown. The admin does not list AlphaBay among their collection of darknet links, which includes PGP-verified URLs for most major darknet markets.</p>



<p>DeSnake, the AlphaBay admin who provided proof of original PGP key ownership in August and has been vouched for by several Dread forum members, quickly provided a flurry of <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/637c5c9836360022cab0/#c-cb8ead107f16b14391" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">rebuttals</a> on the forum, offering possible explanations for AlphaBay’s distinct non-endorsement from Dark.fail.</p>



<p>“Why we are not on darkfail or darknetlive &#8211; ask the owners,” wrote DeSnake. “Time might need to pass but I have said it before it’s a very closely guarded ecosystem and well, you can draw your conclusions from there…” He later went on to imply that Dark.fail had been engaging in gate-keeping for some time, failing to include markets that weren’t liked by the admin or didn’t pay bribes.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">AlphaBay, a #1 darknet market seized by law enforcement four years ago, recently returned. DeSnake proved their control of old PGP key, an original site admin.<br><br>Many naive people are trusting it. We&#39;ll see how this plays out. LE can seize PGP private keys just like anything else.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1448672675036024834?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 14, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The growth of AlphaBay during the first two months of its ‘comeback’ had been slow, complicated by an abundance of <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/deep-web-confusion-ostensible-alphabay-admin-desnake-claims-the-darknet-market-has-returned/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">media attention</a>. The market has been gaining traction, however, since the announcement of the closure of White House Market on October 1<sup>st</sup>.</p>



<p>The largest non-Russian darknet market prior to closing, <a href="/directory/listing/white-house-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">White House Market</a>’s exit was generally considered “graceful” by the community as admins allowed users to withdraw their remaining funds. The exit concluded just two days ago after the website went offline for good, drawing few complaints or criticisms.</p>



<p>While some White House refugees have made the decision to give AlphaBay a try, most of the darknet market community remains unconvinced and committed to a healthy skepticism over its return.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I think that DeSnake was just Alexandre Cazes all along and the FBI collected his PGP when they arrested him, and kept up the facade that they were separate people when they remade AlphaBay.</p>&mdash; anticommunistaction (@anticom20770264) <a href="https://twitter.com/anticom20770264/status/1449012152157675524?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 15, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“Just use the common sense,” advised one Dread member. “Alphabay&#8217;s servers were seized by LE and nobody knows what’s in (the) control of LE.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-wary-of-alphabay/">Dark.fail Admin Wary of AlphaBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dark-fail-admin-wary-of-alphabay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</title>
		<link>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/</link>
					<comments>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alexandre cazes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pandora papers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=869</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The deceased founder of darknet market AlphaBay, Alexandre Cazes, was among the hundreds of politicians and celebrities mentioned</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/">Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The deceased founder of darknet market <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>, Alexandre Cazes, was <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/pandora-papers-offshore-tax-avoidance-1.6197303" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">among the hundreds of politicians and celebrities</a> mentioned in the Pandora Papers, a name given to a data leak spanning some 11.9 million files across 14 offshore financial service providers. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists (ICIJ) performed a <a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">comprehensiv</a><a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> analysis</a> of leaked financial documents and found that Cazes used front companies to buy luxury homes, including a $ 7.6 million house in Thailand, where he was arrested.</p>



<p>Cazes was already known to have used shell companies to move customer funds in order not to draw suspicion to himself, but the revelations made by the ICIJ reveals the scope and breadth of his money laundering activities. After his arrest, business fronts and exchange wallets were quickly associated with bank accounts Cazes and his wife, a Thai citizen, registered in Thailand, Switzerland and the Caribbean to transform the funds into fiat currency, which included $770,000 in cash he had saved over the years.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Jacques Villeneuve &amp; Elvis Stojko, Firoz Patel, Alexandre Cazes , Fred Sharp and the other 495 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Canadians?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Canadians</a> Not pay their fair share of taxes PAY UP <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PandoraPapers?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PandoraPapers</a>  <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PandoraLeaks?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PandoraLeaks</a> <a href="https://t.co/qUQ0nOo2Vs">https://t.co/qUQ0nOo2Vs</a></p>&mdash; 𝔅𝔩𝔢𝔢𝔡𝔰𝔅𝔩𝔲𝔢𝔑𝔊𝔬𝔩𝔡 (@BleedsBlueNGold) <a href="https://twitter.com/BleedsBlueNGold/status/1445056540352782342?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 4, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Implicating hundreds of individuals in the process, the Pandora Papers collectively demonstrate that over 35 current or former world leaders hold assets in offshore tax havens, including former British Prime Minister Tony Blair and the current PMs of the Czech Republic and Kenya. The papers highlight the inconsistencies of politicians and their messages of duty and patriotism, revealing their access to a secret world of shell companies.</p>



<p>In all, the report names “more than 330 politicians and 130 Forbes billionaires, as well as celebrities, fraudsters, drug dealers, royal family members and leaders of religious groups around the world.”</p>



<p>While most of the asset value held by offshore service providers comes from secret funds and bank accounts, much of it is also held in the form of real estate. Cazes, who launched AlphaBay and operated it as admin from 2014 until its shutdown in 2017, owned properties in Thailand, Cyprus and Antigua and Barbuda &#8212; all of which were forfeited to the U.S. government after his arrest. Among his Thailand properties was a mansion-esque estate in Bangkok and a lavish villa in Phuket, where he spent much of his time.</p>



<p>Other well-known, non-political figures named in the leaked documents include Shakira, Ringo Starr, Claudia Schiffer, and Julio Iglesias.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/">Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</title>
		<link>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/</link>
					<comments>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, AlphaBay, is failing to impress the community, with</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/">AlphaBay</a>, is failing to impress the community, with many would-be users avoiding the site due to an assortment of concerns. Nearly seven weeks after AlphaBay’s supposed ‘re-opening,’ the market has managed to attract just a small number of vendors and even fewer customers. This is despite the relatively massive attention its re-opening has received in the media.</p>



<p>A recent article by <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-desnake-dark-web-interview/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Wired</em></a><em>, </em>which features an interview with <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> admin DeSnake, attempted to shed some light as to why the market hasn’t taken off. Among the reasons are persistent DDOS attacks and the decision to accept Monero (XMR)-only for order payments, but the main problem is a lack of trust by the community. Flashpoint security expert Ian Gray told <em>Wired</em> that he was personally distrustful of DeSnake and that “across communities there’s a general distrust.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="630" height="312" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-855" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png 630w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-300x149.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" /><figcaption><em>The legitimacy of the new AlphaBay is being heavily </em><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/pij727/is_the_new_alphabay_a_honeypot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>questioned</em></a><em> by Redditors on r/darknet.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s listings currently total slightly less than 800, with about 400 of them in the Drugs &amp; Chemicals section. As there were only 300 total listings just three weeks ago, this represents a 167% increase in the last 20 days. At the peak of its popularity in 2017, the market had approximately 350,000 listings.</p>



<p>Sales, on the other hand, remain scarce and limited to a handful of vendors. Most sections, though filled with listings and vendors awaiting customers, have zero product sales according to stats kept on each listing. There were single sales spotted for listings of shrooms, marijuana, cocaine, and alprazolam. One listing for Ecstasy had two sales.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="807" height="354" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-856" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png 807w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-300x132.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-768x337.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 807px) 100vw, 807px" /><figcaption><em>The scarcity of listings and near complete lack of sales on AlphaBay give it an almost ghost town feel.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The market’s welcome message and the first return <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/196fffff69ffe348636e" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">message</a> left by DeSnake insist this is not the “new AlphaBay” or “AlphaBay 2.0” but rather a continuation of the same market that shut down in 2017. Not many are sure that this is the case, however, despite DeSnake being verified as a former AlphaBay admin by senior members of the Dread forum.</p>



<p>“The entire point of us returning is about rebuilding the AlphaBay brand and creating something unique and new which will set the standard for a new way how things can be approached,” wrote DeSnake on Dread when asked why he chose not to rebrand the operation. “No other big market has come from the &#8216;dead&#8217; so whether it is a good decision business-wise &#8211; time will tell.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AlphaBay is Back says Former Admin DeSnake</title>
		<link>/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 10 Aug 2021 11:06:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=750</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It appears that AlphaBay, once one of the worlds biggest darknet markets, is now back in operation, following</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/">AlphaBay is Back says Former Admin DeSnake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It appears that AlphaBay, once one of the worlds biggest darknet markets, is <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/pulse/alphabay-darknet-market-back-tom-robinson/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">now back in operation</a>, following an announcement by one of the market’s former admins.</p>



<p>On Sunday, a message posted to the popular darknet forum <em>Dread</em> contained a PGP-signed <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ce2fdff4c9b511d944c3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">message</a> from DeSnake, a previous AlphaBay admin, which outlined plans for the continued operation of the once-deceased market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="398" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay-1024x398.png" alt="" class="wp-image-751" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay-1024x398.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay-300x117.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay-768x298.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay.png 1374w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>The message, also <a href="https://ghostbin.com/paste/SZqmV" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pasted in full</a> on the clearnet by DeSnake, is lengthy and provides the framework for a new model of darknet market that attempts to incorporate some ambitious elements to help protect the safety of its users and their funds.</p>



<p>“I know all of you lost millions to seizure from Law Enforcement,” writes DeSnake. “This time around I have created a very well tested system called AlphaGuard which ensures even if seizures happen on all servers, users will be able to withdraw their funds, settle disputes and leave without a cent lost.”</p>



<p>The message also covers guidelines for the market’s new administration, community functions, the setup of its forum, rules, and a thorough explanation of why DeSnake decided to return.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">AlphaBay &#8211; one of the largest darknet markets ever to operate &#8211; was shut down by US law enforcement in 2017. But now it&#39;s back: <a href="https://t.co/3gpfv6C0df">https://t.co/3gpfv6C0df</a></p>&mdash; Tom Robinson (@tomrobin) <a href="https://twitter.com/tomrobin/status/1424782284159324163?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 9, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Although the message could not be independently verified using standard PGP tools, the admin of the Dread forum, Paris, had the following to say about the recent re-emergence of DeSnake:</p>



<p>“To reduce any-kind of FUD that comes from this announcement. This user did verify his identity and provide proof that he was the tech staff at the original AlphaBay. <strong>It&#8217;s legitimate</strong>. I&#8217;m not saying he isn&#8217;t compromised; but if what he offers is true, at least some people will want to know about it.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="485" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay2-1024x485.png" alt="" class="wp-image-752" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay2-1024x485.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay2-300x142.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay2-768x364.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/alphabay2.png 1386w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Another former admin of AlphaBay, disc0, chimed in shortly thereafter, confirming that he had also been in contact with DeSnake, who mentioned “things that only he knew as a staff member of AlphaBay.” Both Paris and disc0 said they cryptographically confirmed DeSnake’s presence using the PGP keys he provided.</p>



<p>Accordingly, AlphaBay was given a market page of its own on <em>Dread</em>, and DeSnake has been promoted to an admin position. The side of the page gives the following description of what AlphaBay is to be in its second life:</p>



<p>“Legendary AlphaBay Market (est. 2014) has re-opened.</p>



<p>Almost same administration as in 2014-2017 period which means you will find again AlphaBay runs with mature management, unparalleled security, 24/7 professional &amp; well-trained Staff and of course unique vision for the future not only for itself but for the darknet market scene too.”</p>



<p>At its height, AlphaBay handled approximately 10-fold the sales of original darknet market, Silk Road. The market was taken offline in July 2017, as part of a multinational law enforcement effort. The market’s founder, Alexander Cazes, committed suicide in a Thai jail cell while waiting extradition to the United States on charges of drug laundering.</p>



<p>The “new” AlphaBay is also hosted on I2P, a hidden services network similar to Tor.</p>



<p>Some of the main differences between the new market and old are:</p>



<ul><li>The new market is Monero-only.</li><li>No fentanyl or related products.</li><li>No activity related to the countries of Russia, Belarus, Kazakhstan, Armenia, and Kyrgyzstan.</li><li>No ransomware-related activity.</li></ul>



<p>The revamped AlphaBay market was still offline as of the publishing of this article.</p>



<p>Alpahabay Tor link- <a href="http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/</a></p>



<p>Alphabay i2p link- <a href="http://tnaefzkcnhryeusi7hdpqujqiqmnbtah3dmjcg3gvezohunjuxbq.b32.i2p/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">http://tnaefzkcnhryeusi7hdpqujqiqmnbtah3dmjcg3gvezohunjuxbq.b32.i2p/</a></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/">AlphaBay is Back says Former Admin DeSnake</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FBI: Ex-Hedge Fund Employee Sold Stock Tips from AlphaBay</title>
		<link>/fbi-ex-hedge-fund-employee-sold-stock-tips-from-alphabay/</link>
					<comments>/fbi-ex-hedge-fund-employee-sold-stock-tips-from-alphabay/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 13 Jul 2021 10:44:35 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hedge fund]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=681</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Even after AlphaBay’s downfall, the Bitcoin made from selling secret Wall Street scoops on the darknet was too</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fbi-ex-hedge-fund-employee-sold-stock-tips-from-alphabay/">FBI: Ex-Hedge Fund Employee Sold Stock Tips from AlphaBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Even after AlphaBay’s downfall, the Bitcoin made from selling secret Wall Street scoops on the darknet was too lucrative to give up for a trader in his 20s.</em></p>



<p>Evidence collected during the 2017 law enforcement <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/alphabay-largest-online-dark-market-shut-down" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">seizure of AlphaBay</a>, the world’s largest darknet market at the time, continues to result in arrests, some four years later. On July 9<sup>th</sup>, the SEC <a href="https://www.sec.gov/news/press-release/2021-122" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">charged</a> 30-year-old Apostolos Trovias, alleged employee of a Wall Street hedge fund, with perpetrating fraud by selling insider trading tips through the market in exchange for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>Trovias went by the vendor name of “The Bull” and created a unique business model where he would sell stock trading tips in exchange for as little as $29.95 in BTC. Such tips often included highlights from confidential, unreleased earnings reports and other memos tantamount to insider information.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="975" height="693" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/alpha.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-683" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/alpha.jpg 975w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/alpha-300x213.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/alpha-768x546.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 975px) 100vw, 975px" /></figure>



<p><em>AlphaBay listing allegedly created by Trovias. Source: FBI</em></p>



<p>Other listings reveal Trovias was also offering a weekly rate of insider tips for $99.95, and a monthly rate of $329.95. In one instance, the Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdny/pr/dark-web-user-known-bull-charged-insider-trading-scheme" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">found</a> that he managed to sell a pre-release earnings report from a major company for $5,000.</p>



<p>“I am offering information on certain NYSE, NASDAQ and OTC (over the counter) stocks,” read the description of one listing by ‘The Bull’ on AlphaBay. “Buying my service will [give] you an edge by knowing what the big boys are buying or selling.”</p>



<p>As the FBI was already communicating with Trovias prior to the shut down of AlphaBay, it was easy for them to link logs and records collected from the AlphaBay server with Trovias, who established another account on Dream Market immediately following AlphaBay’s closure.</p>



<p>In Feb. 2020, Trovias allegedly told an undercover agent he was planning on setting up a darknet site for his insider information, but the plans never materialized.</p>



<p>Trovias was initially <a href="https://www.scribd.com/document/515111188/Trovias" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">charged with securities fraud</a> in February 2021, but the accompanying arrest warrant remained secret until news of his arrest in Peru, in May. He is likely to be extradited to the United States to face trial in the upcoming weeks.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fbi-ex-hedge-fund-employee-sold-stock-tips-from-alphabay/">FBI: Ex-Hedge Fund Employee Sold Stock Tips from AlphaBay</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fbi-ex-hedge-fund-employee-sold-stock-tips-from-alphabay/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:56:41 by W3 Total Cache
-->