<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>empire market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/empire-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:37:20 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>empire market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</title>
		<link>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/</link>
					<comments>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[empire market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OVO_sweatshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee indicted on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/24/nyregion/thomas-spieker-bitcoin-scheme.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">indicted</a> on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also funded a well-known darknet market vendor specializing in ketamine, according to charges recently filed by New York federal prosecutors.</p>



<p>In addition to converting BTC into cash for carding scammers, Nigerian “catfishers” and an “eastern European crime syndicate,” Thomas Spieker, 42, allegedly <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10650791/New-York-man-42-indicted-running-2-3M-cash-Bitcoin-money-laundering-scheme-crooks.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">provided $38,000 in laundered funds</a> to two people behind the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> darknet market vendor moniker, Zashan Khan and Cosma Siekierski. The vendor maintained a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/u/ovosweatshop" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">presence</a> on the <em>Dread</em> forum, racking up hundreds of positive reviews across multiple darknet markets during their 1-2 years in operation.</p>



<p>Investigators allege the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> vendor name was later taken over by John Humphrey and Fidello Palermo, both 51, who operated it out of a facility in Rochester, New York. The duo were arrested during a trip to Brooklyn where authorities found they were carrying 1.7 kg of ketamine powder/crystals and 140 vials of liquid ketamine.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="554" height="251" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1385" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg 554w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1-300x136.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 554px) 100vw, 554px" /></figure>



<p><em>John Humphrey, left, and Fidello Palermo, right, who allegedly assumed the popular New York ketamine vendor operation. Source: DailyMail.com</em></p>



<p>A total of seven people are being held in association with Spieker’s actions and face a large assortment of charges, ranging from conspiracy to commit money laundering to illegal drug charges.</p>



<p>According to his <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-spieker-60749062" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">LinkedIn profile</a>, Spieker was an Equity Derivates Specialist at Goldman Sachs from Feb 2001 to Mar 2003, founding a hip hop and club music promotion business named S!CK Productions in Nov 2010. His interest in music production and the club scene goes back to the year 2000.</p>



<p>The vendor name stems from a clothing line started by musician Drake, with ‘OVO’ standing for “October’s Very Own.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="718" height="495" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1386" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png 718w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-300x207.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 718px) 100vw, 718px" /></figure>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop vendor profile on the (now defunct) Empire Market. Source: The New York Times</em></p>



<p>Although Empire Market exit scammed in late August 2020, <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> was quick to set up replacement stores on White House Market and Dark Market within a matter of weeks. The quality of their operation apparently degraded over the following year, with customers complaining on <em>Dread</em> of receiving watered-down product and being victims of selective scamming by the vendor.</p>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop</em> also provided pills listed as Xanax and MDMA that received widely varying reviews, although this product took a back seat to their more consistent ketamine-vending operations.</p>



<p>All seven parties arrested and facing trial have pled not guilty to the charges against them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Former Empire Vendor &#8216;TheCommission&#8217; Pleads Guilty to Distribution Charges</title>
		<link>/former-empire-vendor-thecommission-pleads-guilty-to-distribution-charges/</link>
					<comments>/former-empire-vendor-thecommission-pleads-guilty-to-distribution-charges/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Dec 2021 15:42:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[empire market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor arrest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1038</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Fallout from 2020’s Operation DisrupTor continues to make headlines as vendors caught in the multi-national sting are now</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/former-empire-vendor-thecommission-pleads-guilty-to-distribution-charges/">Former Empire Vendor &#8216;TheCommission&#8217; Pleads Guilty to Distribution Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fallout from 2020’s <a href="https://midjersey.news/2020/09/22/international-law-enforcement-operation-targeting-opioid-traffickers-on-the-darknet-results-in-over-170-arrests-worldwide-and-the-seizure-of-weapons-drugs-and-over-6-5-million/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Operation DisrupTor</a> continues to make headlines as vendors caught in the multi-national sting are now entering plea agreements, going to trial, or getting ready for sentencing. The most recent exposed vendor to be named is 27-year-old California man Hunter Secrest, who sold a large variety of substances on the now-defunct Empire darknet market. Secrest <a href="https://gooddaysacramento.cbslocal.com/2021/12/18/california-man-pleads-guilty-to-dark-web-narcotics-distribution/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">pleaded guilty</a> on Saturday to charges related to his time as a vendor and is now awaiting sentencing.</p>



<p>Prosecutors allege Secrest, along with his “associates,” completed over 800 orders under vendor name <em>TheCommission</em> between April and June 2020 on the market. Though the background of Secrest’s arrest was not expanded upon in court documents, investigators had been on to his Empire dealings within a month, and he was indicted on Jun 25, 2020.</p>



<p>At the time of his arrest, Secrest was found to be in possession of 752 grams of heroin, 600 grams of cocaine, 11 grams of psilocybin mushrooms, 45 grams of morphine, 1.6 kilograms of substances containing fentanyl, 93 grams of substances containing methamphetamine, 285 grams of alprazolam, 277 grams of valium, and 35 grams of Adderall.</p>



<p>Operation DisrupTor was a coordinated effort by US and an assortment of international law enforcement agencies aimed to disrupt the flow of unregulated opioid and other drugs over the darknet. Over 170 vendors and their accomplices were arrested as a result of the operation, which also netted hundreds of thousands in cash and hundred of kilograms of various drugs meant for sale on the darknet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Go inside an FBI narcotics investigation with real footage from a search: A Joint Criminal Opioid Darknet Enforcement operation in Los Angeles uncovered a large cache of drugs, weapons, cash, gold, and cryptocurrency as part of Operation DisrupTor. <a href="https://t.co/lhWMolDRdf">https://t.co/lhWMolDRdf</a> <a href="https://t.co/pbvP8KhN9h">pic.twitter.com/pbvP8KhN9h</a></p>&mdash; FBI (@FBI) <a href="https://twitter.com/FBI/status/1308466094584352770?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 22, 2020</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Secrest will be <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.caed.376668/gov.uscourts.caed.376668.39.0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> on Mar 22, 2022. While he faces a maximum sentence of twenty years and a fine of $1 million, the government has said it will recommend a sentence on the low end to take into account the fact that he has pleaded guilty and is recognizant of his own errors in judgment.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/former-empire-vendor-thecommission-pleads-guilty-to-distribution-charges/">Former Empire Vendor &#8216;TheCommission&#8217; Pleads Guilty to Distribution Charges</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/former-empire-vendor-thecommission-pleads-guilty-to-distribution-charges/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:22 by W3 Total Cache
-->