<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>china &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/china/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 12:31:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>china &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Man Who Purchased Oxys From Chinese Bulk Supplier On Dark Web Gets Two Years</title>
		<link>/man-who-purchased-oxys-from-chinese-bulk-supplier-on-dark-web-gets-two-years/</link>
					<comments>/man-who-purchased-oxys-from-chinese-bulk-supplier-on-dark-web-gets-two-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 29 Sep 2021 12:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[oxy]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=848</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A North Carolina man will spend 26 months behind bars after pleading guilty to charges of Distribution of</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-who-purchased-oxys-from-chinese-bulk-supplier-on-dark-web-gets-two-years/">Man Who Purchased Oxys From Chinese Bulk Supplier On Dark Web Gets Two Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A North Carolina man will spend 26 months behind bars after pleading guilty to charges of Distribution of Oxycodone. Accused of importing the drug for resale to local markets, Wesley McKeehan, 34, admitted in federal court earlier this week to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdga/pr/north-carolina-man-sentenced-federal-prison-distributing-opioids-through-dark-web" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">obtaining it from a Chinese supplier on the dark web</a>.</p>



<p>McKeehan was initially indicted on the charges in April; the result of an investigation started by a tip-off from a postal center.</p>



<p>On Aug. 13, 2020, the DEA office in Savannah, Georgia was contacted by a local post office that had received a package suspected of containing controlled substances. DEA agents then followed delivery of the package to an address belonging to a 50-year-old Savannah man. Upon delivery, the agents searched the package and found that it contained oxycodone pills. They then confronted the package owner who admitted to allowing McKeehan to use his business address for drug order imports.</p>



<p>North Carolina is among the states hit hardest by America’s opioid crisis, with painkillers like oxycodone accounting for about <a href="https://www.drugabuse.gov/drug-topics/opioids/opioid-summaries-by-state/north-carolina-opioid-involved-deaths-related-harms" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">80% of drug-related deaths</a> in the state. Pills like the ones to be sold by McKeehan are a generic version of OxyContin, the Purdue Pharma drug largely regarded as responsible for <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/09/01/1031053251/sackler-family-immunity-purdue-pharma-oxcyontin-opioid-epidemic" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">igniting a health crisis across the United States</a>.</p>



<p>In February, corporate consultants who worked for Purdue agreed to pay North Carolina $20 million to <a href="https://ncdoj.gov/news-observer-opioid-settlement-will-bring-nearly-20-million-to-nc-how-should-it-be-spent/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">avoid a potential state-wide lawsuit</a> for their work in pushing the highly-addictive substance.</p>



<p>As part of the sentencing, McKeehan will serve an additional three years of supervised release after his prison sentence ends in 2023. McKeehan’s accomplice was charged with acquiring and possession of controlled substances by misrepresentation, fraud, forgery, and deception or subterfuge. He will serve no prison time but rather probation. Documents provided by McKeehan’s lawyers <a href="https://salisburypost.com/2021/09/28/salisbury-man-pleads-guilty-to-importing-opioids-into-georgia-through-the-dark-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">indicate</a> their client will not appeal the case.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/man-who-purchased-oxys-from-chinese-bulk-supplier-on-dark-web-gets-two-years/">Man Who Purchased Oxys From Chinese Bulk Supplier On Dark Web Gets Two Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/man-who-purchased-oxys-from-chinese-bulk-supplier-on-dark-web-gets-two-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Crackdown Lowering China’s Darknet Market Activity</title>
		<link>/crypto-crackdown-lowering-chinas-darknet-market-activity/</link>
					<comments>/crypto-crackdown-lowering-chinas-darknet-market-activity/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 18:41:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=730</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A new report by Chainalysis suggests China’s recent clampdown of cryptocurrency is responsible for the country’s dramatic reduction</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-crackdown-lowering-chinas-darknet-market-activity/">Crypto Crackdown Lowering China’s Darknet Market Activity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A new <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/china-report-preview-digital-yuan" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by Chainalysis suggests China’s recent clampdown of cryptocurrency is responsible for the country’s dramatic reduction in transfers to crypto addresses associated with “illicit activity.”</p>



<p>According to the report, over $2.2 billion in cryptocurrency was sent from “China addresses” to those associated with scams and darknet activity between April 2019 and June 2021. The same addresses also received $2 billion from illicit addresses, classified as coming from wallets belonging to illicit sources.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="645" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1-1024x645.png" alt="" class="wp-image-731" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1-1024x645.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1-300x189.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1-768x484.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/1.png 1062w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><em>Chinese contributions to “illicit” crypto addresses have been steadily declining. Source: Chainalysis</em></p>



<p>While these figures may sound large, Chainalysis notes that they are much smaller than they were in 2019 when the PlusToken Ponzi scam took billions from Chinese investors. The sell-off from the stolen proceeds of the scam was so great that it actually <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/plustoken-scam-bitcoin-price" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">managed to crash the price of Bitcoin</a> for a brief period of time.</p>



<p>Chainalysis also reports that U.S.-initiated <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/sm756" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sanctions against Chinese drug kingpins</a>, stemming from the country’s uncontrolled exportation of fentanyl analogues, has also likely contributed to the decline in illicit cryptocurrency activity.</p>



<p>China’s digital currency project, which has already conducted several test programs throughout the country, is several years in the making. Its impending nation-wide launch also helps explain the forced closure of Chinese Bitcoin mining operations earlier this year.</p>



<p>Although Chinese citizens do not currently have financial privacy with their current banking system, it is suspected that the digital yuan will be used by the government to block individuals or businesses from doing business as a form of punishment for wrongdoing. This allows for the possibility of what Chainalysis describes as a “financial death sentence” under the finality of a digital yuan system.</p>



<p>An anonymous cryptocurrency operator in China explained to Chainalysis that the Chinese Communist Party (CCP) takes a “top-down approach” in their goal of maintaining stability and control. “So, when government officials see people like early Bitcoiners getting ultra-rich and advocating for liberty and self-sovereignty, the natural inclination is to see them as dissidents,” he said.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-crackdown-lowering-chinas-darknet-market-activity/">Crypto Crackdown Lowering China’s Darknet Market Activity</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/crypto-crackdown-lowering-chinas-darknet-market-activity/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cybercrime in China Thriving on Darknet Data Schemes</title>
		<link>/cybercrime-in-china-thriving-on-darknet-data-schemes/</link>
					<comments>/cybercrime-in-china-thriving-on-darknet-data-schemes/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 09 Jul 2021 09:16:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[china]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=673</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An uptick in data breach and ransomware-related darknet sites in China suggests cyber crime has been profitable among</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cybercrime-in-china-thriving-on-darknet-data-schemes/">Cybercrime in China Thriving on Darknet Data Schemes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An uptick in data breach and ransomware-related darknet sites in China suggests cyber crime<em> has been profitable among its participants in the nation, and several operations appear to be expanding.</em></p>



<p>Chinese darknet sites are being blamed for fueling the rise of a data breach epidemic in which billions of data records are now being stolen on an annual basis.</p>



<p>According to information security service providers at CNSecurity, several Mandarin language sites on the dark web have been <a href="https://asia.nikkei.com/Business/Technology/China-s-dark-web-spawns-a-hard-to-crack-hacker-community" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">discovered hosting hacker wanted ads</a>, suggesting plans for further data breaches and ransomware attacks. The sites name international companies as targets and specify language requirements, of which Korean and Japanese tend to be the most popular.</p>



<p>China has long been known as the source for several famous ransomware attacks, and home to a well-established cyber criminal underground that capitalizes off data breaches in a surprising number of ways.</p>



<p>An in-depth breakdown of this particular criminal network, published by cyber intelligence experts at <a href="https://intel471.com/blog/china-cybercrime-big-data-privacy-laws/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Intel471</a>, details the several levels and connections between the various players. Data is initially obtained by a hacker or insider, repackaged for salability, sold to middlemen who place it for sale on darknet markets. The information is then purchased by scammers who use it to threaten, ransom, blackmail or extort their victims. Everyone involved is entitled to a cut of the resulting profits.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="661" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-2-1024x661.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-674" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-2-1024x661.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-2-300x194.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-2-768x496.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-2.jpg 1245w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><em>Diagram explaining how money is made off sales of data. Source: Intel471.com</em></p>



<p>In China, where the country’s ‘<a href="https://toomanyadapters.com/get-around-great-firewall-china/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Great Firewall</a>’ blocks access to thousands of websites, cyber criminals employ a secret system of communication within the framework of the country’s limited internet availability. Sometimes this involves conducting business on state-sponsored social media platforms in such a way that buyers and sellers of stolen data can remain undetected by government agencies.</p>



<p>In Sept. 2020, it was reported that the Chinese Communist Party (CCP) was <a href="https://www.wionews.com/world/china-spying-on-millions-around-the-world-by-harvesting-personal-details-from-the-dark-web-327896" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">spying on millions of people around the world</a> through harvesting information about them from the dark web.</p>



<p>Use of the Tor browser has been unofficially banned in China and the government has <a href="https://www.technologyreview.com/2012/04/04/186902/how-china-blocks-the-tor-anonymity-network/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">attempted to block Tor use by its citizens</a> for over a decade. Despite these attempts, thousands of Chinese continue to access the Tor network each day.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cybercrime-in-china-thriving-on-darknet-data-schemes/">Cybercrime in China Thriving on Darknet Data Schemes</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/cybercrime-in-china-thriving-on-darknet-data-schemes/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:21 by W3 Total Cache
-->