<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>dark0de reborn &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dark0de-reborn/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:14:56 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>dark0de reborn &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</title>
		<link>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/</link>
					<comments>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de reborn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After a week of delayed withdrawals and other issues suggesting an exit scam was likely, Dark0de – one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/">Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After a week of delayed withdrawals and other issues suggesting an exit scam was likely, Dark0de – one of the biggest and most popular darknet markets to ever exist – <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/3b03396226d17850311b" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">went offline</a> on Feb 24<sup>th</sup> without warning, taking user funds trapped in escrow along with it. There was no announcement made by the market admins as to what had happened or why the site was no longer available, but activity preceding the closure suggests it was a willful and coordinated effort to scam buyers and vendors.</p>



<p>“At this stage the facts are that onions are down and the dark0de admin /u/dark0dereborn has deleted their dread presence and scrubbed some posts/comments,” wrote Dread member <em>dontlaugh</em> on Thursday in a new thread in the <em>DarkNetMarkets</em> sub-Dread. “Not looking great for all involved as it would at this stage appear to be an ungraceful exit,” they added.</p>



<p>The post triggered a massive wave of comments from frustrated users, which had nearly exceeded 300 in count within its first 24 hours.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="733" height="467" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1339" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de.jpg 733w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de-300x191.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 733px) 100vw, 733px" /></figure>



<p><em>The famous welcome screen for Dark0de featured original, colorful artwork, giving it some rare personality that set it apart from competitors.</em></p>



<p>While most of Dark0de’s existence was uneventful and smooth for buyers and vendors, some users reported running into deposit and withdrawal issues as early as Dec 2021. On the Dread forum, one Dark0de user reported a XMR deposit requiring over 300 confirmations before funds were credited to their account. Other users commented on the increasing lack of professionalism exhibited by the market’s admins during its last few months.</p>



<p>“They would just make up half-arsed excuses and stall by insisting you prove something they should already be able to do,” said user <em>PaperHat</em> on Dread. “If not crooked, you can&#8217;t trust that level of incompetence either. Sometimes you can just tell someone is a compulsive liar from the way they talk and I got that sense from the admin,” they added.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dark0de had a great collection of vendors, and I wish all of the vendors well in their new endeavors. I wish dark0de would have exited normally, but it is what it is. <br>May The Markets Live On Forever. <a href="https://t.co/NsRCSQXmMD">pic.twitter.com/NsRCSQXmMD</a></p>&mdash; uɐpʇou@ ✸ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1e6.png" alt="🇺🇦" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@notdan) <a href="https://twitter.com/notdan/status/1496838344482779137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 24, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Dark0de is the fourth major darknet market to go down this year, with the other three being Cartel Market, Monopoly Market and CanadaHQ. All three are believed to have been seized by law enforcement. The market closures to occur this year stand in stark contrast to the comparatively “graceful exits” of White House Market and Cannazon; both of which provided their customers with a warning and ample time to withdraw their funds.</p>



<p>Dark0de was founded in the first half of 2020 and hailed for its comparatively wide range of features, which included support for Monero, Bitcoin multisig transactions, and Direct Pay, which allowed users to send payment to a designated address rather than from a market account balance. These and other features earned it a massive user base in the roughly two years of its existence. There were over 40,000 listings on the market at the time of its closure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/">Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:11:51 by W3 Total Cache
-->