<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hydra &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/hydra/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:14:53 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>hydra &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of Hydra, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been arrested</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been <a href="https://www.mskagency.ru/materials/3204351" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Russia per reports from the Meshchansky District Court in Moscow. The report names Dmitry Pavlov – a Russian citizen – as arrested on charges pertaining to “illegal drug trafficking on an especially large scale.” He faces up to 20 years in prison if convicted on the charges.</p>



<p>The arrest, which took place on April 11<sup>th</sup>, occurred less than a <a href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">week after Hydra’s servers</a> were knocked offline in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. German police also managed to confiscate about $25 million in Bitcoin during their takedown of the market.</p>



<p>The US Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-investigation-leads-shutdown-largest-online-darknet-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> its own charges against Pavlov on April 5<sup>th</sup>, which include conspiracy to distribute narcotics and conspiracy to commit money laundering. He is also <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1490906/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">named</a> as a Hydra admin and provider of hosting services for the now-defunct darknet market, which had been in steady operation since 2015.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia has arrested the alleged co-founder of dark web platform Hydra a week after American and German authorities said they shut down what they called the world’s largest illegal darknet marketplace.</p>&mdash; Fuad Alakbarov ⁠⁠ (@DrAlakbarov) <a href="https://twitter.com/DrAlakbarov/status/1514901753392680964?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 15, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Pavlov <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/alleged-hydra-administrator-dmitry-pavlov-reportedly-arrested-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stated</a> on April 6<sup>th</sup> that he had only been informed of the charges against him via the media, and that he had not been contacted by US authorities. He also said the server provision business he ran, in which he leased servers to other businesses, was fully-licensed and registered with Roskomanadzor, the Russian communications bureau. Pavlov also denied allegations of being a Hydra admin, claiming he did not have administration duties on any website.</p>



<p>“We are a hosting company and have all the necessary communications licenses,” Pavlov told BBC’s Russian service in an interview last week. “We don’t administer any sites but only provide servers for rent as intermediaries.”</p>



<p>Cybersecurity experts who had been investigating Hydra told <em>The Moscow Times </em>that <a href="https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2022/04/15/russia-arrests-alleged-co-founder-of-worlds-largest-darknet-marketplace-a77363" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russia had been monitoring the market since its inception</a>, and speculated that it was possible for Hydra to make a re-appearance under a different domain, hosted on different servers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</title>
		<link>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[v3 link]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The long awaited V3 onion Hydra Market link has finally been published. Hydra Market new V3 onion url</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/">Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The long awaited V3 onion Hydra Market link has finally been published.</p>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> new V3 onion url &#8211; <a href="http://hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="454" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-1024x454.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-738" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-1024x454.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-300x133.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-768x341.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3.jpg 1522w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> is the last dark net market to publish its V3 onion link, long after the rest of the dark net community has moved to V3 links and disabled their V2 onion links.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="184" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-1024x184.png" alt="" class="wp-image-737" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-1024x184.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-300x54.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-768x138.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2.png 1128w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> admin has published on Hydra Market forum-<br></p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>Dear users, in the near future the site will open at: hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion
Forwarding will be enabled on other mirrors. </code></pre>



<p>V2 onion links are expected to be disabled by the tor team on October of 2021. It is advised to save the new link and bookmark it.</p>



<p>Our <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Darknet list</a> will always have the updated links of all the darknet markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/">Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>8</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</title>
		<link>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysis by blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis revealed that the Russia-based Hydra darknet market is outpacing the growth</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/">Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Analysis by blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis <a href="https://go.chainalysis.com/crypto-crime-money-laundering-recording.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">revealed</a> that the Russia-based <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a> darknet market is outpacing the growth of competition at an alarming rate. In a presentation broadcast live yesterday, researchers from Chainalysis and Flashpoint described the unprecedented growth of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">H</a><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/">ydra</a>, noting that its monthly transaction volume was roughly 2.5x greater than all other darknet markets summed together.</p>



<p>By the end of 2020, <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a> was averaging roughly $160 million in transactions per month, while all other markets averaged about $35 million in total. The findings suggest that Hydra is single-handedly driving the growth of darknet market activity.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="886" height="543" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra.png" alt="" class="wp-image-649" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra.png 886w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra-768x471.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 886px) 100vw, 886px" /><figcaption>Source: Chainalysis</figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>The presentation also included findings from Hydra’s 2021 activity thus far, as well, noting that transactions over $100,000 in size were on the rise in the first half of the year. A number of transactions over $1 million to the market were also reported.</p>



<p>Of all funds sent to Hydra, about 20% ended up going through Bitcoin mixing services and “high risk exchanges.” The research also found that Hydra was becoming increasingly popular as a cashout option among those looking to perform money laundering of their own.</p>



<p>“These crypto laundering services are significantly more popular and sought after as verification requirements are becoming more and more stringent,” said Vlad Cuiujuclu, Team Lead from Flashpoint.</p>



<p>According to the researchers, darknet market activity is “remarkably consistent,” and the only major disruptions experienced are due to market closures. They also found that fluctuations in the price of BTC are irrelevant to activity.</p>



<p>Chainalysis had previously pinpointed Hydra as <a href="https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/blog/chainalysis-hydra-cryptocurrency-research/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the place where money trails come to an end</a>. BTC sent to the market is largely traded into fiat through Russia’s clandestine network of unregulated money exchangers, making it impossible to trace where the funds go next. The local government’s apparent unwillingness to dismantle the market has increased its reputation as a haven for darknet vendors.</p>



<p>“Whatever is operating and based in Russia is only under the watch of Russian law enforcement,” commented Andras Toth-Czifra, Senior Analyst at Flashpoint. “And it’s up to them to shut down those marketplaces or arrest the owners.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/">Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainalysis: Hydra Topped $1.37B in Sales in 2020</title>
		<link>/chainalysis-hydra-topped-1-37b-in-sales-in-2020/</link>
					<comments>/chainalysis-hydra-topped-1-37b-in-sales-in-2020/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 May 2021 05:40:11 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=592</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Despite a recent flurry of bad press, Hydra, the world’s largest and longest standing darknet market is more</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chainalysis-hydra-topped-1-37b-in-sales-in-2020/">Chainalysis: Hydra Topped $1.37B in Sales in 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Despite a recent flurry of <a href="https://www.foxbusiness.com/technology/firm-tracked-darkside-gang-ransomware-payments-and-the-massive-sums-paid" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">bad press</a>, Hydra, the world’s largest and longest standing darknet market is more popular than ever in 2021, thanks largely to lack of local regulation, interference from law enforcement, and oversight of crypto-fiat transfers.</p>



<p>In conjunction with research performed by Flashpoint, blockchain analytics firm Chainalysis <a href="https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/blog/chainalysis-hydra-cryptocurrency-research/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> a huge year-over-year surge in Hydra’s sales activity, which rose by 33% between 2019 and 2020. Despite plans being shelved for a long-hinted global expansion, Hydra is still on pace to top their previous sales record by the end of 2021, which will be bigger than its closest competitor by several hundred million dollars.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">We&#39;re excited to announce the release of our joint report with <a href="https://twitter.com/FlashpointIntel?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@FlashpointIntel</a> on Hydra, the biggest darknet market currently operating. Read it here, and register for our webinar on June 17 at 11am ET to learn more from the experts behind the report! <a href="https://t.co/pcoXNVYMN6">https://t.co/pcoXNVYMN6</a> <a href="https://t.co/jstz3uOioy">https://t.co/jstz3uOioy</a></p>&mdash; Chainalysis (@chainalysis) <a href="https://twitter.com/chainalysis/status/1397188137185595394?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 25, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Overall, Hydra grew an astounding 624% in the three years between 2018 and 2020, fueled by a lack of competition and the apparent unwillingness of local law enforcement to pursue closure of the market.</p>



<p>The report covers the history of Hydra, which opened in 2015 but remained relatively obscure until the collapse of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Russian_Anonymous_Marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russian Anonymous Marketplace</a> (RAMP) in July 2017. 2020 marks the second year in a row in which Hydra sales volume has exceeded $1 billion, according to estimates by Chainalysis. The firm’s research also indicates that Hydra experiences an unusually small amount of downtime for a darknet market, with one notable, pre-planned closure in March 2020 that was caused by covid-forced suspension of shipping infrastructure.</p>



<p>Hydra has been the subject of even more unwanted attention than usual in recent months. The market crossed into the focus of mainstream media sources after it was <a href="https://www.elliptic.co/blog/buried-treasure-criminals-to-go-to-extreme-lengths-to-cash-out-crypto" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">revealed</a> that ransomware profiteers at the now-infamous hacker group Darkside had moved a portion of their ill-gotten BTC through the market.</p>



<p>Not just darknet market vendors, but hackers, scammers and those running other criminal enterprises are increasingly turning to Hydra as they run low on KYC-free cashout options. In the report, Chainalysis details how the rise of regulatory oversight regarding fiat-crypto transfers is funneling most criminal crypto transfers to opaque cashout services. As a result, Hydra has a reputation of being where crypto money trails “go dark.”</p>



<p>“The longer Hydra runs unscathed, the more apparent its regional influence,” the report concludes.</p>



<p>“Despite hits to other well-established Russian-speaking cybercriminal communities and marketplaces in recent months… enforcement scrutiny and competitor chicanery have so far eluded Hydra. This may be a mere coincidence, or it could indicate that Hydra is more resilient to oscillating geopolitics and law enforcement efforts.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chainalysis-hydra-topped-1-37b-in-sales-in-2020/">Chainalysis: Hydra Topped $1.37B in Sales in 2020</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/chainalysis-hydra-topped-1-37b-in-sales-in-2020/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:08:15 by W3 Total Cache
-->