<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hitman &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/hitman/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 11:49:08 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>hitman &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</title>
		<link>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/</link>
					<comments>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1444</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a Tampa Bay woman was <a href="https://www.tampabay.com/news/tampa/2022/04/20/tampa-woman-gets-6-years-in-prison-for-dark-web-murder-for-hire/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced to six and a half years</a> in prison on Wednesday for using one such darknet site to order the murder of her ex-boyfriend’s wife.</p>



<p>A US District Judge ordered DeAnna Marie Stinson, 51, to serve the time and pay $12,000 in restitution for attempting to hire a hitman through one of the well-known fake hitman sites on the dark web &#8212; whose operators had <a href="https://gizmodo.com/besa-mafia-alleged-ringleaders-arrested-1848769128" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">recently been apprehended</a> by Romanian authorities.</p>



<p>Stinson admitted to attempting to hire what she believed was a professional assassin from a Besa Mafia site in exchange for <a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">payments</a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> </a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">totaling $12,307 in Bitcoin</a>. She also provided a photo of the intended victim, along with their name and address. The “assassin” turned out to be a US federal investigator who was likely tipped off to Stinson’s intentions by one of the site’s admins.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Tampa Accountant Sentenced to More Than Six Years in Federal Prison for Plotting a Murder-for-Hire: DeAnna Marie Stinson of Tampa has been sentenced to six years and six months in federal prison for murder-for-hire. <a href="https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv">https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv</a></p>&mdash; FBI Tampa (@FBITampa) <a href="https://twitter.com/FBITampa/status/1517179243406381065?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“I cited the old adage, ‘hell hath no fury like a woman scorned,’” said Federal Defender Alec Hall to the judge during Stinson’s sentencing, adding, “I think that’s what happened in this case.”</p>



<p>Stinson pleaded guilty to the charges in January.</p>



<p>Sprawling across a number of similar-looking darknet sites, the Besa Mafia operation has been known to exist since at least 2015, and famously <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">suffered a</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> dat</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a breach</a> in May 2016 in which they were firmly outed as a scam. On the site which Stinson traversed, “death by shooting” started at a rate of $5,000, while a “beating” was listed for $2,000. At the top of the supposed services list was “death by sniper,” which was priced at $20,000.</p>



<p>The Besa Mafia admins were captured earlier this month as the result of a US-based investigation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</title>
		<link>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/</link>
					<comments>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 14:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web were <a href="https://diicot.ro/mass-media/3498-comunicat-de-presa-3-06-04-2022" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Romania on April 6th, after years of steady operation. The arrests were performed at the behest of US authorities who had been investigating the sites and managed to link them to a group of Romanian citizens.</p>



<p>Seven house raids were performed in relation to the takedown, in the counties of Gorj and Hunedoara; the result of warrants issued against five suspects and four “witnesses.” The amount of financial damage directly linked to the sites’ operation was estimated to be around 500,000 EUR, although the total tally they collected over the years is likely to be far greater.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Yura (presumably), the owner of Besa Mafia, history&#39;s most profitably dark web murder-for-hire website has been arrested. I spent years corresponding with him about his business.</p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1512316762095710210?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 8, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Perhaps the most notorious type of darknet market, murder-for-hire sites have been a part of the dark web since just a year or two after the closure of the original <em>Silk Road</em> marketplace. However, it has been known for quite some time that just about <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/mg77bn/this-fake-hitman-site-is-the-most-elaborate-twisted-dark-web-scam-yet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">all of them are fake</a> &#8212; scam sites designed to separate vengeful parties from decent-to-large sums of Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The most famous of these sites was run by a group calling themselves the <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Besa M</em></a><em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">a</a></em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>fia</em></a>, of which the five arrested suspects are presumed to comprise. Other sites operated by the group are thought to include <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7d8j3/the-alleged-scammers-behind-the-most-notorious-murder-for-hire-site-have-been-arrested" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><u><em>Camorra Hitman</em> and <em>#1 Hitman Marketplace</em></u></a>, along with a list of less-famous names.</p>



<p>Besides being complete scams, all these sites shared the common feature of purporting to link “real hitmen” with a client looking for violence to be performed upon a particular victim &#8212; whether it be a beating, stabbing, torture, or even murder. Prices for these services usually ranged between $5,000 and $20,000, payable in Bitcoin, but never resulted in the actual delivery of service. Instead, clients were likely to become the subject of a police investigation, and dozens of arrests have been performed over the years for charges related to this type of attempted murder.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Flowchart of Besa Mafia&#39;s Business Model For Fake Hitman Dark Web Scam <a href="https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY">https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY</a> <a href="https://t.co/CKsjvS6TZI">pic.twitter.com/CKsjvS6TZI</a></p>&mdash; Arnout de Vries (@ADeVries23) <a href="https://twitter.com/ADeVries23/status/733185111064236032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 19, 2016</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>While <a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">real m</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">urder</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">-for-hire sites</a> have been found to exist on the dark web, they are not advertised in the transparent fashion of the <em>Besa Mafia</em> sites (which were usually found via darknet link lists) and are nearly impossible to stumble upon.</p>



<p>The arrests were the result of a joint operation between the US Homeland Security Investigations and the US Embassy in Bucharest, performed by police officers from Romania’s Service for Combating Cybercrime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida Woman Pays Darknet ‘Hitman’ Directly From Exchange</title>
		<link>/florida-woman-pays-darknet-hitman-directly-from-exchange/</link>
					<comments>/florida-woman-pays-darknet-hitman-directly-from-exchange/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 Jan 2022 09:20:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1104</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A woman from Tampa, Florida whose murderous desires led her to a fake assassin-for-hire site on the darknet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-pays-darknet-hitman-directly-from-exchange/">Florida Woman Pays Darknet ‘Hitman’ Directly From Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A woman from Tampa, Florida whose murderous desires led her to a fake assassin-for-hire site on the darknet <a href="https://www.businessobserverfl.com/article/accountant-pleads-guilty-to-murder-for-hire-plot-involving-dark-web-and-bitcoin" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">pleaded guilty</a> yesterday to charges related to arranging the death of her ex-boyfriend’s wife. DeAnna Stimpson, a 50-year-old accountant and local church organizer, admitted to hiring what she thought was a hitman on the dark web to commit the murder in exchange for Bitcoin sent directly from her crypto exchange wallet.</p>



<p>Stimpson was <a href="https://www.wfla.com/news/hillsborough-county/tampa-woman-arrested-in-murder-for-hire-plot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> at home in September of last year by what reporters described as “an army of federal agents,” for a crime that has played out similarly several times in recent past. She was charged with solicitation to commit a crime of violence and murder for hire after investigators confirmed she had sent BTC to a scammer-operated darknet site in hopes of hiring a hitman.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="891" height="425" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1106" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2.jpg 891w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2-300x143.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2-768x366.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 891px) 100vw, 891px" /><figcaption><em>Deanna Stinson, mugshot.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Stimpson first registered an account on the scam hitman site on June 24, 2021. The next day, she placed her request and provided the name and address of the intended target, along with a picture. After receiving the BTC payment and Stimpson’s preferences on how to perform the “quick hit in southern Florida”, the operator of the phony website contacted an unnamed “media source” with information pertaining to the would-be crime. The media source then passed the information on to authorities in the US, who began conducting their investigation.</p>



<p>Stimpson had sent more than $12,300 in BTC to the fake site operator by the end of July across several different payments, hoping with each one to spur the fake assassin into completing their end of the deal. On July 31<sup>st</sup>, dismayed by having fallen out of contact with the ‘hitman’ she had been assigned, Stimpson sent the operator a message requesting they “reassign the job to someone who has a history of getting jobs done.”</p>



<p>In August, authorities in the US took staged photographs of the intended victim while pretending to be the new assassin assigned to her job. They then sent the photos to Stimpson to confirm if it was indeed the target. After Stimpson acknowledged they were correct, the agents then requested she send an additional $350 in Bitcoin for the purchase of revolver with which the job would be completed. Stimpson agreed, sending funds on Sept 13<sup>th</sup> which were then traced back to a US cryptocurrency exchange. Federal investigators then confirmed the identity of Stimpson with the help of the exchange, leading to her arrest ten days later.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-pays-darknet-hitman-directly-from-exchange/">Florida Woman Pays Darknet ‘Hitman’ Directly From Exchange</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/florida-woman-pays-darknet-hitman-directly-from-exchange/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>D.C. Area Woman Latest to Fall for Fake Murder-for-Hire Darknet Site</title>
		<link>/d-c-area-woman-latest-to-fall-for-fake-murder-for-hire-darknet-site/</link>
					<comments>/d-c-area-woman-latest-to-fall-for-fake-murder-for-hire-darknet-site/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Oct 2021 10:25:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[murder for hire]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=910</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 25-year-old Virginia woman was arrested on Wednesday after allegedly attempting to hire a darknet hitman to murder</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/d-c-area-woman-latest-to-fall-for-fake-murder-for-hire-darknet-site/">D.C. Area Woman Latest to Fall for Fake Murder-for-Hire Darknet Site</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 25-year-old Virginia woman was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdva/pr/culpeper-woman-arrested-dark-web-murder-hire-plot" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> on Wednesday after allegedly attempting to hire a darknet hitman to murder an unknown potential victim. Annie Nicole Ritenour, from near the Washington D.C. area of the state, is the latest to fall for a well-known entrapment scam luring would-be conspirers into thinking they are dealing with a real hitman on the dark web. Now she faces federal criminal charges relating to an attempt to pay $3,200 in Bitcoin to the would-be murderer-for-hire.</p>



<p>Charged with solicitation to commit a crime of violence and murder-for-hire, Ritenour faces a maximum penalty of 20 years in prison if convicted.</p>



<p>“I am just looking for a simple quick job,” prosecutors allege Ritenour wrote to the assumed hitman, next providing the make, model, and license plate of the intended victim’s car. She also attached photos of the target which were also passed along to law enforcement.</p>



<p>“<em>The address of the person will be the best place to make the target, as it’s his workplace… I would say wait until he’s off at 3 and then make your move.”</em></p>



<p>Though indetectable to those generally unfamiliar with the darknet, the site employed by Ritenour contained language that is now considered to be boilerplate among those familiar with this particular scam. The scam itself is believed to be orchestrated by a lone actor or small group that operates several similarly-themed websites. They are also believed to have a journalist contact at BBC News.</p>



<p>As with several instances in the past, the news contact would then go on to notify the relevant authorities of potential harm being orchestrated against an individual in their jurisdiction, using evidence provided by the website admin in court against the perpetrator. In this case, prosecutors state that FBI in Knoxville, Tennessee, were tipped off by a “confidential human source” with information from the murder-for-hire website.</p>



<p>“We can kill any person you want, as long as it is not a president or very important person that is guarded by the military,” read the introduction page of the fake murder-for-hire website, going on to specify that they can “make the murder look accidental, so that police will not suspect anyone.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/d-c-area-woman-latest-to-fall-for-fake-murder-for-hire-darknet-site/">D.C. Area Woman Latest to Fall for Fake Murder-for-Hire Darknet Site</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/d-c-area-woman-latest-to-fall-for-fake-murder-for-hire-darknet-site/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</title>
		<link>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 10:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=820</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 38-year-old Russian man was arrested on Sept. 8 for allegedly running an actual ‘hitman-for-hire’ service on the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/">Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 38-year-old Russian man was <a href="https://www.svoboda.org/a/sud-v-moskve-arestoval-podozrevaemogo-v-sozdanii-sayta-dlya-nayomnyh-ubiyts-v-darknete/31453709.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrested</a> on Sept. 8 for allegedly running an actual ‘hitman-for-hire’ service on the darknet which led to the deaths of at least two people. Sergei Magdanov was apprehended by law enforcement at the behest of a Moscow court in his home city of Izhevsk, accused of creating and running a darknet site where he accepted cryptocurrency and digital cash to arrange murder for his customers.</p>



<p>In addition to his site administration duties, authorities allege Magdanov also acted as assassin.</p>



<p>Magdanov’s takedown was the result of a multi-agency effort which included the Ministry of Internal Affairs and Investigative Committee of Russia, which uncovered what local media refers to as <a href="https://ren.tv/news/v-rossii/877666-politsiia-zaderzhala-podozrevaemogo-v-organizatsii-ubiistv-cherez-darknet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">especially grave crimes</a>. In addition to murder charges, Magdanov will face charges related to murder conspiracy as well as weapons and ammunition sales.</p>



<p>Magdanov was first identified by law enforcement as a <a href="https://ren.tv/news/kriminal/877875-zhertvoi-vladeltsa-magazina-ubiits-cherez-darknet-stal-narkodiler" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">potential suspect</a> in the murder of a young married couple last year, when a 25-year-old man and a 29-year-old-woman were found dead near a stream with their hands tied and mouths taped, shot execution style. The man, who had a criminal history tied to selling synthetic drugs online, was thought to be targeted due to his status as a drug dealer, possibly by rival dealers.</p>



<p>During a raid on his home and safehouse, authorities found Magdanov was in possession of around 500 bank cards, 1000 SIM cards, and “a large amount of cash.” Also seized was computer equipment, mobile phones, and electronic data carriers.</p>



<p>Most assassination or “hitman-for-hire” sites on the dark web have long been <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/04/technology/can-you-hire-a-hit-man-online.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exposed as scams</a>. The majority of such sites are believed to be run by a single organization or individual who may be responsible for indirectly passing on tips about would-be customers to law enforcement. Sites like Magdanov’s &#8211; which authorities purport offered the real deal &#8211; remain an extremely rare finding.</p>



<p>As part of a Sept. 9 <a href="https://ren.tv/news/v-rossii/877854-sud-arestoval-na-2-mesiatsa-podozrevaemogo-v-ubiistvakh-cherez-darknet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ruling</a>, Magdanov will be detained as a “preventative measure” for at least two months for his pending trial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/">Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</title>
		<link>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/</link>
					<comments>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Berkett thought he hired a darknet killer to dispatch a woman who rejected him. A Beverly Hills</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/">California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Scott Berkett thought he hired a darknet killer to dispatch a woman who rejected him.</p>



<p>A Beverly Hills man arrested on charges pertaining to murder-for-hire last week was <a href="https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/24/beverly-hills-man-arrested-friday-in-alleged-murder-for-hire-plot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">granted a detention hearing</a> yesterday to determine if he is a flight risk. Federal prosecutors <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-cdca/pr/beverly-hills-man-arrested-federal-charges-attempting-hire-hitman-murder-one-time" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">allege</a> that Scott Quinn Berkett, 24, made payments totaling $14,000 in Bitcoin to what he thought was a professional <a href="/hire-hitman-deep-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hitman</a> service to have a previous acquaintance murdered.</p>



<p>In a court affidavit filed May 21, prosecutors describe how investigators had been made aware of Berkett’s plans by a foreign media outlet. The media outlet had themselves been tipped off by an anonymous party thought to be the owner of the darknet-hosted <a href="/hire-hitman-deep-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hitman</a> service. The service itself is most likely a scam.</p>



<p>Court documents describe how Berkett met his intended target online, where they shared duties of administrator for a Facebook group dedicated to the animated television series RWBY. The target, an unidentified woman, flew out to Los Angeles in 2019 to meet Berkett at his request. She described Berkett to investigators as “sexually aggressive” during the encounter and cut off contact with him after returning home.</p>



<p>According to the affidavit, information provided by the media outlet was “very specific about the identity and location” of the woman, “as well as social media accounts, nicknames, email and a distinctive tattoo.”</p>



<p>The outlet also provided investigators with “transaction information from an unnamed source on the Dark Web.” Prosecutors believe the transactions demonstrate that “Bitcoin payments were made with an understanding that an unknown individual would murder (the target).”</p>



<p>Of the $14,000 Berkett allegedly paid for the task, payments totaling $13,000 in BTC went to the darknet site owner, with the final $1,000 paid to an undercover investigator posing as a professional killer, which he had met on WhatsApp days earlier. Rather than making what would be the final payment in Bitcoin, Berkett was instructed to send the funds via Western Union. He was then videotaped outside of the Western Union office around the time the transaction was processed, further lending evidence to his guilt.</p>



<p>If convicted, Berkett faces a minimum 10-year prison sentence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/">California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:56:46 by W3 Total Cache
-->