<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>world market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/world-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:42:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>world market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</title>
		<link>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seven months after the return of DeSnake, one of the original AlphaBay’s two administrators, the new incarnation of</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seven months after the <a href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">return of DeSnake</a>, one of the original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s two administrators, the new incarnation of the infamous darknet market is once again on top of the competition &#8212; sans Hydra, the Russian-language darknet market which still dwarfs all others in sales volume. The distinction comes about as its closest competitor in size, World Market, has been largely <a href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">deemed no longer operational</a>, even if the site remains technically accessible.</p>



<p>The rise of the “new” <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> is not something that much of the darknet market community was expecting as many feared it was simply an extravagant “honeypot” operation designed to collect the credentials of buyers and vendors. For its first few months, the market remained relatively void of users and activity. However, with over half a year of steady operation under its belt and an ever-increasing base of users, these fears have largely subsided, and AlphaBay currently enjoys its greatest degree of popularity yet in this new manifestation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">In 2017 the largest darknet market was seized, Alphabay &#8211; leading to the tragic suicide of its alleged admin Alex Cazes.<br><br>Recently its co-admin/fugitive DeSnake returned, relaunching the site in Alex&#39;s honor. With World&#39;s demise, Alphabay is close to reclaiming its throne as #1.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1506643215847411712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>AlphaBay now hosts over 22,000 listings and is home 5,228 vendors and 340,000+ buyers, according to statistics maintained by the market. It is now a Monero (XMR)-only market and forces its users to operate under some of the strictest guidelines to ever be implemented by a darknet market. These include a no-weapons and no-fentanyl policy, short-timed finalization periods, and an advanced captcha system that has proved capable of preventing DDOS attacks from occurring.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="934" height="406" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1409" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png 934w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-300x130.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-768x334.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 934px) 100vw, 934px" /><figcaption>lphabay</figcaption></figure>



<p><em>After a slow re-start, activity at AlphaBay is now bustling.</em></p>



<p>The recent string of darknet market closures in 2022 has also helped AlphaBay’s propulsion to the top of the list. World Market, previously the largest (English-speaking) market by sales volume, has all but closed shop, as admins on Dread have repeatedly warned users against making new deposits to avoid losses in the likely event of an exit scam.</p>



<p>Within the past week, World Market added the following message to its main market page, although accounts registered within the last six months (sans brand new accounts) are still unable to log in to the market:</p>



<p>“<em>World Market is operational again, listing images will be restored soon, if you are missing a deposit open a ticket.”</em></p>



<p>AlphaBay also seems to be making some strides in its promises to delivery a decentralized darknet market – the first of its kind – that can theoretically continue to operate even if service provided by an operator is discontinued, for whatever reason. Upcoming tasks have been scheduled in the market’s <a href="http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/roadmap" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">roadmap</a> for the project, and include building payment modules, multisig and escrow core functions, and a way for network operators to provide “initial decentralized infrastructure report.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</title>
		<link>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/</link>
					<comments>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators on the <em>Dread</em> darknet forum. On March 26<sup>th</sup>, forum moderator <em>Shakybeats</em> <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ann</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">oun</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ced</a> they had removed moderation privileges for the World Market administrator on <em>Dread</em>, disabling their ability to continue posting and confirming that an impending exit scam was likely.</p>



<p>Warning signs that something at World Market was amiss had been present for weeks, going back to a cautionary <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/d01b3750e9320def61f7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> by a self-described former colleague of the World Market admin, written late last month. In the post, user <em>nightmaremarket</em> accused the market of preparing for an exit scam &#8212; a plan which its admin immediately denied.</p>



<p>On March 23<sup>rd</sup>, <em>Dread</em> user <em>dontlaugh</em> started a new <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">th</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ead</a> urging World Market users to take heed of “a number of red flags,” which most notably included a rollback to a previous version of the website. Other warning signs included a sudden jump in the cost of vendor bond – from $1,500 to $3,000 – and reports from several vendors that their payments were trapped in the market, with withdrawal requests being ignored.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="671" height="98" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1393" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-300x44.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /><figcaption><em>One of many posts responding to World Market user complaints on Dread.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In an effort to respond to mounting complaints, World Market admin and <em>Dread</em> user <em>makarov</em> wrote the following <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ab00d26a769f65030710" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">counter-post</a>, which was heavily downvoted, with its rationale being dismissed by most respondents:</p>



<p>“The time has come that the World Market team must close shop. The team tried to fix numerous technical issues over the past week but could not recover what has been lost. We have worked hard to be the best market and to serve the community.</p>



<p>As much as I care for everyone at World Market, I also care about the vendors and buyers, and it would not be fair to continue at this point.” – <em>Dread user makarov</em></p>



<p>Less than two days later, the post by <em>dontlaugh</em> was edited to include the following text: “UPDATE: I think we can call it. Either one of the admins fucked the other (who would have thunk it) or they both pulled this to squeeze out as much as possible from everyone,” thus signaling the end of the market’s functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="477" height="407" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1394" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png 477w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1-300x256.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 477px) 100vw, 477px" /><figcaption><em>World Market welcome message that is currently still being displayed.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>After the closures of White House Market and Dark0de, World Market was for a short while one of the biggest darknet markets in operation, hosting well over 30,000 listings at its peak. The market used the traditional account deposit system, making an exit scam especially lucrative for a market its size.</p>



<p>As of March 27<sup>th</sup>, the rolled-back version of World Market was still accessible and allowing those who had created older accounts to still login and even make deposits. However, many functions have been removed, making purchases or withdrawals impossible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:16 by W3 Total Cache
-->