<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>cyber attack &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/cyber-attack/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 12:24:05 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>cyber attack &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ransomware Back in the Headlines as Conti Posts Jeweler Customer List</title>
		<link>/ransomware-back-in-the-headlines-as-conti-posts-jeweler-customer-list/</link>
					<comments>/ransomware-back-in-the-headlines-as-conti-posts-jeweler-customer-list/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 01 Nov 2021 12:24:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyber attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hack]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=912</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Russian ransomware gang Conti released the details of 11,000 clients of diamond jeweler Graff yesterday, apparently deciding to</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ransomware-back-in-the-headlines-as-conti-posts-jeweler-customer-list/">Ransomware Back in the Headlines as Conti Posts Jeweler Customer List</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Russian ransomware gang Conti <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10148265/Massive-cyber-heist-rocks-high-society-jeweller-Graff.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">released</a> the details of 11,000 clients of diamond jeweler Graff yesterday, apparently deciding to make good on its <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2021/10/conti-ransom-gang-starts-selling-access-to-victims/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">threats</a> to publish the data of malware-infected businesses that refused to pay the ransom. The story, initially broken by <em>The Daily Mail</em>, describes those named in the leaked files as a veritable list of “world leaders, Hollywood A-listers and billionaire tycoons.”</p>



<p>Among the published documents are receipts, invoices, client lists and credit notes which equal an approximated total of 69,000 documents.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ransomware attacks making the front pages again&#8230;<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Conti?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Conti</a> <a href="https://t.co/qqbU9JawQn">pic.twitter.com/qqbU9JawQn</a></p>&mdash; Graham Cluley (@gcluley) <a href="https://twitter.com/gcluley/status/1454727045162938377?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 31, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Some of the many celebrities named in a list include Tom Hanks, Samuel L. Jackson, and Alec Baldwin. Documents provided in leaks show addresses associated with Donald and Melania Trump, and records of purchases made by David and Victoria Beckham. Other notable figures to be mentioned within the documents include disgraced socialite Ghislane Maxwell and Saudi Crown Prince Mohammed bin Salman.</p>



<p>“&#8217;Given the profile of the customer database, this is absolutely massive,” a former colonel in British military intelligence told <em>The Daily Mail</em>. “This is going to bring the highest levels of international law enforcement down on the gang,” he added.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="929" height="329" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-914" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1.png 929w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-300x106.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-768x272.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 929px) 100vw, 929px" /></figure>



<p>A Conti-run clearnet site that posted snippets of hacked records and documents was updated days after the posting of a <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2021/10/conti-ransom-gang-starts-selling-access-to-victims/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">long-winded rant</a> in which they praised REvil and ranted against the U.S. government. Security researchers believe a <a href="https://thecyberwire.com/newsletters/daily-briefing/10/206" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">recent shift in Conti’s business model</a> may have underpinned their decision to make the Graff files public.</p>



<p>Based in London, Graff was founded in 1960 and is considered to be one of the worlds pre-eminent jewelers, with 50 stores worldwide. A spokesperson for Graff described the cyber-attack as “limited” and noted that only addresses and other publicly-available information was exposed. The information could still potentially be used as leverage against certain customers and the true damage of the attack’s fallout remains to be ascertained.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ransomware-back-in-the-headlines-as-conti-posts-jeweler-customer-list/">Ransomware Back in the Headlines as Conti Posts Jeweler Customer List</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ransomware-back-in-the-headlines-as-conti-posts-jeweler-customer-list/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</title>
		<link>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/</link>
					<comments>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 10:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyber attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hacker]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Personal data collected off insecure systems by phishers and attackers is being used to steal even more data</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/">Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Personal data collected off insecure systems by phishers and attackers is being used to steal even more data in a positive feedback loop that is amplifying out of control.</em></p>



<p>A new <a href="https://www.imperva.com/resources/resource-library/white-papers/lessons-learned-from-analyzing-100-data-breaches/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by security research experts at Imperva predicts that roughly 40 billion records will be compromised in data breaches by the end of 2021. This figure represents a 100% increase from 2020, a year which saw a lot of businesses transition operations online due to restrictions imposed by COVID. The report analyzed 100 data breaches and found that 74% of stolen records contained personal data, while 15.6% contained login credentials and 10.4% was credit card information. All three types of data are frequently found for sale on darknet markets.</p>



<p>The report comes at a time when <a href="https://www.csis.org/programs/strategic-technologies-program/significant-cyber-incidents" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">significant cyberattacks are at an all-time high</a>. In addition to the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/04/politics/white-house-ransomware/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">highly-publicized ransomware attacks</a> that have netted attackers tens of millions in 2021, the number of reported data breaches is skyrocketing. According to cyber attack report aggregators at <a href="https://www.databreaches.net/news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Databreaches.net</a>, there were 11 major data breach incidents reported just yesterday, Jun 4<sup>th</sup>. This represents a significant uptick from activity reported just one year ago.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="868" height="364" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart.png" alt="" class="wp-image-603" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart.png 868w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart-300x126.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart-768x322.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 868px) 100vw, 868px" /><figcaption>Source: Lessons learned from analyzing 100 data breaches, imperva.com</figcaption></figure>



<p>“We are definitely seeing a spike in ransomware attacks that also have a data breach component to them,” said cybersecurity attorney Brian Finch on a <a href="https://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/ransomware-data-breaches-and-the-5474731/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recent legal podcast episode</a>.</p>



<p>“Not only is your data encrypted, but it’s being stolen as well, and the hackers are demanding a ransom not only to unlock your system, but also to prevent them from releasing the private information&#8230; So, it’s sort of a two-fer attack. You get the ransom, and you get data breach as well.”</p>



<p>As noted in the report by Imperva, the stolen data put up for sale on the dark web is often used for extortion and phishing attempts designed to pilfer even more data. The report also analyzed root causes of initial breaches and found that almost 50% of the time it was due to poor website design.</p>



<p>“In most of the analyzed breaches the lack of in-depth security stands out as a main reason,” the report concludes.</p>



<p>“Organizations can reduce the attack surface by securing their database environments. Since a significant number of the attacks target web applications, separating the database server from the application server can make a big difference. Together with dilution of excessive privileges from key users and strong authentication mechanisms, these practices in combination can help you avoid a data breach.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/">Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:00 by W3 Total Cache
-->