<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>white house market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/white-house-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 11:44:57 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>white house market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Social Media Hails “Graceful” White House Market Exit</title>
		<link>/social-media-hails-graceful-white-house-market-exit/</link>
					<comments>/social-media-hails-graceful-white-house-market-exit/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 08 Oct 2021 11:44:51 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[white house market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[whm]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=872</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>It’s been one week since one of the world’s top darknet markets, White House Market, announced they were</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-media-hails-graceful-white-house-market-exit/">Social Media Hails “Graceful” White House Market Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>It’s been one week since one of the world’s top darknet markets, White House Market, <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/77f2b8521f9ae0fda3a5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> they were pulling the plug on operations, and its admins are being praised for the orderliness of the closure across social media.</p>



<p>Darknet market communities on Reddit, Twitter and Dread have thus far expressed overwhelmingly positive sentiment about the way the closure is being handled, which includes processing withdrawals from remaining user balances as promised and allowing vendors to let customers know on what other markets they can be found.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Proof you can run a good, respectable, risk-reducing market and exit without scamming people, or getting busted. Be Like WHM.</p>&mdash; uɐpʇou@ ✸ (@notdan) <a href="https://twitter.com/notdan/status/1444291649165684736?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 2, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“Compromises are not a matter of if but when,” commented Dread admin Paris, in a forum thread dedicated to the market’s closure.</p>



<p>“<em>All markets should have a path to exit the scene. Get in, do what you want to do, and then leave with bags of money. Gracefully exiting allows another market to shine.” – Paris, Dread Forum</em></p>



<p>Also up for discussion was which market would be most likely to assume White House’s position as the world’s number one darknet market (outside of Russia, which is still dominated by Hydra). Most opinion seemed to lean toward Dark0de as the replacement as it is the next biggest by sales volume, slightly trailed by ToRReZ, and AlphaBay still a dark horse with continued lackluster activity.</p>



<p>“The people running WHM are the best of the best,” said one <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/q1omp4/comment/hfhot00/?utm_source=share&amp;utm_medium=web2x&amp;context=3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">redditor</a>, going on to explain how the market had always come through for him in times of disputes and other issues.</p>



<p>“<em>I wished them good will and personally if I lost me last order to (a) scammer I wouldn&#8217;t care. But I didn’t, they are still working , and coming through. Fkn legends. The best of the best.” – Deancrypt, Reddit</em></p>



<p>Making the decision to go out on top has so far proven to be a good one for the White House admins, who are <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/q1omp4/how_much_money_did_whm_make/">estima</a><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/q1omp4/how_much_money_did_whm_make/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">t</a><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/q1omp4/how_much_money_did_whm_make/">ed</a> to have walked away with somewhere between $25 and $50 million in crypto proceeds, based on buyer and seller statistics displayed on the market. This includes vendor bond deposits, the 5% collected by the market from each sale, funds in abandoned wallets, and funds confiscated from banned users.</p>



<p>“I&#8217;m sad to see it go but as far as exits go, this is about as clean as it gets folks,” said another Dread user in the market’s retirement PSA. “Kudos to WHM, I&#8217;m glad you all made it out before a negative event caused the demise.”</p>



<p>As of the writing of this article, the URL for White House was still up and available for access by customers to withdraw their remaining balances.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/social-media-hails-graceful-white-house-market-exit/">Social Media Hails “Graceful” White House Market Exit</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/social-media-hails-graceful-white-house-market-exit/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>White House Market Announces Closure, Retires On Top</title>
		<link>/white-house-market-announces-closure-retires-on-top/</link>
					<comments>/white-house-market-announces-closure-retires-on-top/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 11:05:36 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[white house market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=858</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the world’s biggest and most well-known darknet markets, White House Market, announced on Oct. 1st they</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-house-market-announces-closure-retires-on-top/">White House Market Announces Closure, Retires On Top</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the world’s biggest and most well-known darknet markets, White House Market, announced on Oct. 1<sup>st</sup> they would soon be going into retirement, ceasing order placements immediately and winding down other operations. The announcement comes on the eve of the 8-year anniversary of the shutdown of <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Silk_Road_(marketplace)" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Silk Road</a>, the original darknet marketplace.</p>



<p>Per the message signed by White House Market admins, users can still withdraw their remaining balances and communicate with others until the market goes offline, estimated to be sometime within the next six months.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ALERT: White House Market is retiring. New orders and registrations are disabled. The site remains online. There is no indication of an exit scam or compromise.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1444194496279875585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 2, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The market, which was popular among European and American customers, is closing at the peak of its prime, with over 3,400 active vendors, 42,000 listings and 287,000 daily visitors in the weeks before Friday’s announcement. Displaced vendors are being given the opportunity to update their profiles to let customers know what other markets they can be found on in the future.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="819" height="309" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-860" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-1.png 819w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-1-300x113.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-1-768x290.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 819px) 100vw, 819px" /><figcaption><em>White House Market homepage notice indicating its impending closure.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Opening for business in early 2020, White House Market was different from many other markets in that it was built from entirely original coding and without the use of market scripts. It was one of the first markets to ditch BTC, going Monero-only, and switch to the wallet-less, per order payment system (Direct Pay). These features earned it a positive reputation among the community, along with the market’s readiness to learn from the mistakes of its peers. Buyers and sellers flocked to White House particularly after a wave of market closures in the first half of 2020.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Clarification for vendors from MrWhite about advertising availability on other platforms <a href="https://t.co/gmYYpY40IL">pic.twitter.com/gmYYpY40IL</a></p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1444166833083334661?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 2, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Now it seems the market’s admins feel they’ve done well enough.</p>



<p>“We have reached our goal and now, according to plan, it&#8217;s time to for us to retire,” reads the message signed by the admins, which goes on to assure users it is not exit scamming, and even promising to refund vendors who had recently paid for featured listing space. The message also encouraged former customers to give new markets a chance, praising Monopoly and Versus markets for their innovation.</p>



<p>“<em>Thanks everybody for your business, trust, support and of course for placing decent amounts of money in our pockets. We may come back some time in the future with a different project or we may not… Good luck and stay safe.”</em> – White House Market admins</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/white-house-market-announces-closure-retires-on-top/">White House Market Announces Closure, Retires On Top</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/white-house-market-announces-closure-retires-on-top/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:15:17 by W3 Total Cache
-->