<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>bitcoin &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/bitcoin/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:26:59 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>bitcoin &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</title>
		<link>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/</link>
					<comments>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Oct 2021 10:26:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alexandre cazes]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[pandora papers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=869</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The deceased founder of darknet market AlphaBay, Alexandre Cazes, was among the hundreds of politicians and celebrities mentioned</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/">Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The deceased founder of darknet market <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>, Alexandre Cazes, was <a href="https://www.cbc.ca/news/pandora-papers-offshore-tax-avoidance-1.6197303" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">among the hundreds of politicians and celebrities</a> mentioned in the Pandora Papers, a name given to a data leak spanning some 11.9 million files across 14 offshore financial service providers. The International Consortium of Investigative Journalists (ICIJ) performed a <a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">comprehensiv</a><a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://www.icij.org/investigations/pandora-papers/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> analysis</a> of leaked financial documents and found that Cazes used front companies to buy luxury homes, including a $ 7.6 million house in Thailand, where he was arrested.</p>



<p>Cazes was already known to have used shell companies to move customer funds in order not to draw suspicion to himself, but the revelations made by the ICIJ reveals the scope and breadth of his money laundering activities. After his arrest, business fronts and exchange wallets were quickly associated with bank accounts Cazes and his wife, a Thai citizen, registered in Thailand, Switzerland and the Caribbean to transform the funds into fiat currency, which included $770,000 in cash he had saved over the years.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Jacques Villeneuve &amp; Elvis Stojko, Firoz Patel, Alexandre Cazes , Fred Sharp and the other 495 <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Canadians?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Canadians</a> Not pay their fair share of taxes PAY UP <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PandoraPapers?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PandoraPapers</a>  <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/PandoraLeaks?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#PandoraLeaks</a> <a href="https://t.co/qUQ0nOo2Vs">https://t.co/qUQ0nOo2Vs</a></p>&mdash; 𝔅𝔩𝔢𝔢𝔡𝔰𝔅𝔩𝔲𝔢𝔑𝔊𝔬𝔩𝔡 (@BleedsBlueNGold) <a href="https://twitter.com/BleedsBlueNGold/status/1445056540352782342?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 4, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Implicating hundreds of individuals in the process, the Pandora Papers collectively demonstrate that over 35 current or former world leaders hold assets in offshore tax havens, including former British Prime Minister Tony Blair and the current PMs of the Czech Republic and Kenya. The papers highlight the inconsistencies of politicians and their messages of duty and patriotism, revealing their access to a secret world of shell companies.</p>



<p>In all, the report names “more than 330 politicians and 130 Forbes billionaires, as well as celebrities, fraudsters, drug dealers, royal family members and leaders of religious groups around the world.”</p>



<p>While most of the asset value held by offshore service providers comes from secret funds and bank accounts, much of it is also held in the form of real estate. Cazes, who launched AlphaBay and operated it as admin from 2014 until its shutdown in 2017, owned properties in Thailand, Cyprus and Antigua and Barbuda &#8212; all of which were forfeited to the U.S. government after his arrest. Among his Thailand properties was a mansion-esque estate in Bangkok and a lavish villa in Phuket, where he spent much of his time.</p>



<p>Other well-known, non-political figures named in the leaked documents include Shakira, Ringo Starr, Claudia Schiffer, and Julio Iglesias.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/">Pandora Papers: Alexandre Cazes Paid for $7.6M Thai Mansion with Shell Company Money</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/pandora-papers-alexandre-cazes-paid-for-7-6m-thai-mansion-with-shell-company-money/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Italy’s Oldest Mafias are Upgrading to Crypto and the Darknet</title>
		<link>/italys-oldest-mafias-are-upgrading-to-crypto-and-the-darknet/</link>
					<comments>/italys-oldest-mafias-are-upgrading-to-crypto-and-the-darknet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 27 Sep 2021 09:46:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[italian mafia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=843</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Different factions of the Italian mafia are bringing more areas of criminal operations to the darknet, according to</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/italys-oldest-mafias-are-upgrading-to-crypto-and-the-darknet/">Italy’s Oldest Mafias are Upgrading to Crypto and the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Different factions of the Italian mafia are bringing more areas of criminal operations to the darknet, according to a recent local language <a href="https://www.informazione.it/a/EDBB652C-8B31-4C0D-BE52-F9898DCFF1A8/Mafie-Dia-Darknet-market-per-recapito-droga-a-domicilio" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">assessment</a> of the developing trend. While still feared, centuries-old organizations like Cosa Nostra and ‘Ndrangheta are attempting to economically modernize themselves by adopting cryptocurrency payments and darknet markets to better evade the attention of law enforcement.</p>



<p>The news comes on the heels of the <a href="https://bitcoinpress.co.uk/police-arrest-106-people-tied-to-mafia-connected-cybercrime-group" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrest of 106 mafia-related cybercriminals</a> in a takedown spanning 16 houses across Italy and Spain.</p>



<p>In August, Italy’s anti-mafia police force, known as the DIA, published a lengthy <a href="https://direzioneinvestigativaantimafia.interno.gov.it/semestrali/sem/2020/1sem2020.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> detailing the online expansion of organized crime in the nation during the covid crisis. The report found that all mafioso and other criminal organizations stood to gain from the adoption of sophisticated privacy technologies, such as cryptocurrency and hidden services. In addition, many are already using crypto to launder large sums of ill-gotten wealth, keeping them invisible to law enforcement and tax regulators.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">“The Italian Anti-Mafia Directorate (DIA) report that the ‘Ndrangheta is becoming increasingly tech-savvy, using cryptocurrencies such as Bitcoin and Monero to transact anonymously on the dark web.” <a href="https://t.co/1v2betwP4M">https://t.co/1v2betwP4M</a> <a href="https://t.co/9mdxiblsum">pic.twitter.com/9mdxiblsum</a></p>&mdash; Mafia News (@MafiaNews_Org) <a href="https://twitter.com/MafiaNews_Org/status/1437732967338627073?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 14, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Of the country’s different mafia factions, the report noted that the ‘Ndrangheta of the Calabria region were the most advanced in this area, selling synthetic drugs and counterfeit PPE materials for Bitcoin and Monero over the dark web. Strict lockdown conditions across the country have forced the organization to move several of its operations online.</p>



<p>Regarded as the biggest mafia organization in the world, ‘Ndrangheta has reportedly taken up a particular interest Monero (XMR), which Italy’s anti-mafia division <a href="https://www.zeit.de/news/2021-08/18/kriminelle-nutzen-vermehrt-kryptowaehrungen">bel</a><a href="https://www.zeit.de/news/2021-08/18/kriminelle-nutzen-vermehrt-kryptowaehrungen" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">i</a><a href="https://www.zeit.de/news/2021-08/18/kriminelle-nutzen-vermehrt-kryptowaehrungen">eves</a> is used to purchase cocaine from Latin American cartels. The organization remains largely non-penetrable by law enforcement due to its highly-secretive nature and the fierce loyalty of its members.</p>



<p>The <a href="https://www.lastampa.it/esteri/la-stampa-in-english/2017/10/14/news/shutting-them-down-is-almost-impossible-fighting-the-deep-web-s-drug-market-1.34401566" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">mafia’s involvement with darknet market drug sales</a> has been known about since at least 2017, but shutting down their activity there is a task local law enforcement deems as “near impossible.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/italys-oldest-mafias-are-upgrading-to-crypto-and-the-darknet/">Italy’s Oldest Mafias are Upgrading to Crypto and the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/italys-oldest-mafias-are-upgrading-to-crypto-and-the-darknet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</title>
		<link>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/</link>
					<comments>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 18:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[money laundering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday added 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/policy-issues/financial-sanctions/recent-actions/20210921" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">added</a> 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred from engaging in business with companies operating in the country. Sanctions placed by the U.S. government primarily effect Suex, a Czechoslovakia-based over-the-counter cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">b</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">lieved</a> to have handled hundreds of millions of dollars in cryptocurrency obtained from illicit sources.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="489" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-832" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-300x143.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-768x367.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11.jpg 1418w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Suex employees at Suex office location at 12 Federation East Tower, Moscow City, Moscow</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The sanctions are the result of the Biden administration’s <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-target-crypto-ransomware-payments-with-sanctions-11631885336" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pledge</a> to disrupt the network of exchanges which process the conversion of cryptocurrency obtained via malware ransom payments. Biden had asked for Russia’s cooperation in dismantling the financial services support for ransomware groups like REvil, which was responsible for the Colonial Pipeline attack in May.</p>



<p>According to Paul Abbate, FBI deputy director, “there is no indication that the Russian government has taken action to crack down on ransomware actors,” prompting the U.S. to move to sanctions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Great move today by the <a href="https://twitter.com/USTreasury?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@USTreasury</a> to sanction a Suex, a Moscow-based crypto exchange, one of the top money laundering outlets for cybercrime in the world. <br><br>Actions like these are a key component in a more aggressive strategy against ransomware<a href="https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy">https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy</a> <a href="https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3">https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3</a></p>&mdash; Dmitri Alperovitch (@DAlperovitch) <a href="https://twitter.com/DAlperovitch/status/1440371668786896898?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 21, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite the initial praise by several in the cybersecurity industry, the Treasury Department’s move to selectively block crypto addresses also provoked negative response from Bitcoin and privacy advocates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="566" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-833" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-300x166.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-768x424.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1536x849.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1.jpg 1839w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>“Repeat after me: stop trying to use the financial system in order to prosecute crimes after the fact,” exclaimed computer scientist and professor Emin Gun Sirer in a <a href="https://twitter.com/el33th4xor/status/1439193943183351810" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">tweet</a>. “The root cause of ransomware attacks is the weak state of computer security, not the mechanism used for payment.”</p>



<p>The Suex website, though still functioning, is now stripped of its ability to utilize the Visa and Mastercard payment processors much of its business is reliant upon, effectively dismantling its ability to do business. The company’s <a href="https://suex.io/terms-of-use" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">terms and conditions</a> indicate it adheres to rather common AML and KYC standards, requiring provision of personal identification for transactions over $500 in value.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="539" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-834" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-300x158.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-768x404.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1536x808.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Future sanctions are also expected to single out specific targets but the extent to which this measure will be employed for cryptocurrency addresses is not yet known.</p>



<p>In Nov. 2018, the Treasury dept. <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/sm556" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">blacklisted</a> two Bitcoin addresses belonging to Iranian nationals implicated in the laundering of millions in terrorist-designated funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AlphaBay Vendor ‘Fentmaster’ Sentenced to 15 Years, Forfeits 680 BTC</title>
		<link>/alphabay-vendor-fentmaster-sentenced-to-15-years-forfeits-680-btc/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-vendor-fentmaster-sentenced-to-15-years-forfeits-680-btc/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 02 Aug 2021 09:28:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=724</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The brash vendor exhibited signs of carelessness throughout his short-lived career and is thought to have written about</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-vendor-fentmaster-sentenced-to-15-years-forfeits-680-btc/">AlphaBay Vendor ‘Fentmaster’ Sentenced to 15 Years, Forfeits 680 BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>The brash vendor exhibited signs of carelessness throughout his short-lived career and is thought to have written about his ongoing drug dealing exploits on Reddit.</em></p>



<p>The U.S. Attorney for a New York district court announced on Friday a prison sentence of 15 years for Chukwuemeka Okparaeke after he plead guilty to charges of importing and fentanyl analogues which he later sold on the dark web.</p>



<p>Okparaeke went by the AlphaBay vendor name of “Fentmaster,” allegedly ordering several kilograms of fentanyl analogues from suppliers in Hong Kong and China for resale to U.S. buyers. Prosecutors allege the defendant conducted millions of dollars-worth of fentanyl sales during his less-than-a-year stint at AlphaBay.</p>



<p>During the court proceedings, Okparaeke admitted selling a synthetic opiate product, known as U-47700, to an 18-year-old in 2016, who subsequently died of an overdose shortly thereafter. In addition to the 15-year prison sentence, Okparaeke was given five years of supervised release and ordered to pay $105,177, in addition to the amount of Bitcoin kept in his personal wallet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dark web narcotics dealer Chukwuemeka Okparaeke, aka “Fentmaster,” responsible for overdose death, sentenced to 15 years in prison <a href="https://t.co/qS3lSfJwxe">https://t.co/qS3lSfJwxe</a></p>&mdash; US Attorney SDNY (@SDNYnews) <a href="https://twitter.com/SDNYnews/status/1421179933976580097?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 30, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>An early 2017 raid on Okparaeke’s residence resulted in the seizure of more than 10 kilograms of the imported drugs, along with smaller quantities of drugs found in 82 envelopes waiting to be mailed out to customers.</p>



<p>In September 2020, Okparaeke told the U.S. Attorney’s Office that the 680 BTC he had accrued through his AlphaBay sales was no longer in his possession – a claim that was later proven to be false.</p>



<p>A 2017 Reddit <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/DNMBusts/comments/6waqm7/vendor_fentmaster_busted_what_he_did_wrong/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">post</a> detailed the mistakes made by Fentmaster as a vendor that allowed him to be caught by the authorities. Among them was continuing to send scores of packages in a non-discrete manner even after being questioned by police about his activities at the post office.</p>



<p>In a bizarre twist, Okparaeke was assumed to be the author of Reddit <a href="https://www.nj.com/hudson/2017/03/man_busted_by_feds_allegedly_detailed_drug_operati.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market fan fiction</a>, in which he chronicled his own drug sales operations in the context of a fictional setting.</p>



<p>Previously regarded only as a fringe research chemical, the DEA made U-47700 a Schedule 1 drug in November 2016 after the substance was linked to several deaths across the United States earlier in the year.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-vendor-fentmaster-sentenced-to-15-years-forfeits-680-btc/">AlphaBay Vendor ‘Fentmaster’ Sentenced to 15 Years, Forfeits 680 BTC</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-vendor-fentmaster-sentenced-to-15-years-forfeits-680-btc/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rideshare Platform Account Scammers Headed for Court</title>
		<link>/rideshare-platform-account-scammers-headed-for-court/</link>
					<comments>/rideshare-platform-account-scammers-headed-for-court/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 17 Jul 2021 09:29:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lyft]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[scheme]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[uber]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=696</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Personal data collected through illicit sources was used to create an army of underqualified, non-approved drivers. Court hearings</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rideshare-platform-account-scammers-headed-for-court/">Rideshare Platform Account Scammers Headed for Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Personal data collected through illicit sources was used to create an army of underqualified, non-approved drivers.</em></p>



<p>Court hearings are now underway in the case against 19 Brazilian nationals accused of operating a scheme in which over 2,000 driver accounts were fraudulently registered on several rideshare services using stolen personal data.</p>



<p>One of the accused, Bruno Proencio Abreu, appeared at a District Court detention hearing in Massachusetts yesterday to face a wire fraud charge. Abreu allegedly played a role in the <a href="https://www.nbcboston.com/news/local/19-charged-in-ride-hailing-fake-driver-account-scheme/2375154/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">scheme</a> by instructing live-in partner and mastermind Priscila Barbosa on how to purchase Bitcoin for the purpose of buying Social Security numbers off the dark web.</p>



<p>Abreu is also suspected of abusing his position as an alcohol delivery driver to get pictures of driver’s licenses from his customers, which he would then hand over to Barbosa to use in the account registration scam. In October 2020, Barbosa allegedly took a picture from her cell phone of a darknet market site displaying Social Security numbers being sold for Bitcoin.</p>



<p>In May 2021, the Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ma/pr/nineteen-brazilian-nationals-charged-nationwide-conspiracy-open-fraudulent-driver" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> charges against the 19 individuals; 8 of which remain of large. A court <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ma/page/file/1392541/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">affidavit</a> filed in support of the charges describes an intricate plan devised by Barbosa and other conspirators to sell fraudulent rideshare service accounts to underqualified drivers. The group pocketed not only a portion of the drivers’ earnings but all the resulting referral commissions, as well.</p>



<p>Federal prosecutors allege the Boston-based consortium referred to themselves as “Mafia” in a group on WhatsApp, a popular mobile communication platform, and are believed to have operated from mid-2019 through April 2021. They used WhatsApp to share driver’s license pictures, corresponding selfies, and social security numbers for the purpose of forging accounts on rideshare platforms like Uber and Lyft.</p>



<p>The group also shared tips on how to get around the companies’ fraud detection services. Some of these included keeping printouts of the registered face when prompted for a selfie, editing their own picture onto a victim’s driver’s license, and making use of GPS “spoofing” technology to match the geographic coordinates of a selfie photo to the current coordinates of the driver.</p>



<p>Some victims whose compromised information was used to register phony accounts have <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ma/victim-and-witness-assistance-program/us-v-wemerson-dutra-aguiar-and-us-v-priscila-barbosa-et-al" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> receiving tax documents in their name from the rideshare services, which reflects income they did not actually earn.</p>



<p>All 19 suspects are being charged with a single count of wire fraud, which carries a maximum sentence of 20 years in prison. 10 of the suspects are set to have arraignments on July 29.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rideshare-platform-account-scammers-headed-for-court/">Rideshare Platform Account Scammers Headed for Court</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/rideshare-platform-account-scammers-headed-for-court/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Doctor Accused of Hiring Darknet Hitman to Kidnap Wife Denied Bail</title>
		<link>/doctor-accused-of-hiring-darknet-hitman-to-kidnap-wife-denied-bail/</link>
					<comments>/doctor-accused-of-hiring-darknet-hitman-to-kidnap-wife-denied-bail/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 22 Jun 2021 11:47:04 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=658</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Washington state doctor accused of ordering the kidnapping and extortion of his estranged wife will remain in</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doctor-accused-of-hiring-darknet-hitman-to-kidnap-wife-denied-bail/">Doctor Accused of Hiring Darknet Hitman to Kidnap Wife Denied Bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A Washington state doctor accused of <a href="https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2021/apr/16/spokane-doctor-accused-of-attempted-kidnapping-in-/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ordering the kidnapping and extortion of his estranged wife</a> will remain in jail after a judge <a href="https://www.spokesman.com/stories/2021/jun/16/federal-judge-orders-attempted-kidnapping-defendan/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">overruled</a> objections that he should be allowed free on bail. Dr. Ronald Ilg, neonatologist and childbirth specialist with a career of 27 years, allegedly made Bitcoin payments to a supposed “hitman-for-hire” darknet site to have his wife kidnapped and extorted in March of this year.</p>



<p>According to court documents, Ilg traveled to Mexico with a woman on Apr. 10<sup>th</sup>. The following day, FBI agents gathered evidence at his home in Washington state pertaining to his wife’s kidnapping. In a safe that could only be opened using the doctor’s fingerprint, agents discovered a username and password for the murder-for-hire dark web service.</p>



<p>After logging in to Ilg’s account, messages were found detailing his request to the website. In addition to getting his wife addicted to heroin, the physician requested that she be coerced into dropping court proceedings against him, also agreeing to remain married to him while “keeping her mouth shut” about the kidnapping incident.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="522" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-2-1-1024x522.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-660" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-2-1-1024x522.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-2-1-300x153.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-2-1-768x392.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-2-1.jpg 1041w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Message left by Ilg to would-be darknet kidnappers. Source: U.S. Attorney Office</figcaption></figure>



<p>Ilg also instructed the would-be hitman to physically assault a woman who had accused him of harassment at work, noting in particular that her hands should be damaged or even broken.</p>



<p>FBI agents were waiting to question Ilg at the Spokane International Airport when he returned home. He initially claimed that the whole plot was a plan to commit suicide so that his assets would be transferred to his mistress rather than his estranged wife.</p>



<p>The following day, Sherriff deputies responded to reports of an assault at Ilg’s home. He was found with a black eye, with a bottle missing 46 Xanax pills nearby. Found in addition was a signed note to his mistress with the words, “I am about to drift off to sleep. I pray that God forgives me.” He was booked into jail a few days later where he remains.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="387" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/2-1-1024x387.png" alt="" class="wp-image-661" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/2-1-1024x387.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/2-1-300x113.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/2-1-768x290.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/2-1.png 1389w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Screenshot from the darknet site where Ilg reportedly created an account.</figcaption></figure>



<p>The FBI also linked payments made to an escrow deposit address on the site to a Coinbase account owned by Ilg.</p>



<p>Similar to other murder-for-hire darkweb investigations, the FBI was tipped off by an “unnamed international news organization.” This organization receives tips itself from darknet website administrators who would rather not interact directly with law enforcement.</p>



<p>A <a href="https://www.healthgrades.com/physician/dr-ron-ilg-ycb24" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">review</a> from Jan. 2020 on a doctor rating site claimed Ilg is “a terrible human being and should not be working with patients,” noting his apparent lack of empathy and bedside manner. Ilg’s wife filed for divorce in June 2020.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/doctor-accused-of-hiring-darknet-hitman-to-kidnap-wife-denied-bail/">Doctor Accused of Hiring Darknet Hitman to Kidnap Wife Denied Bail</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/doctor-accused-of-hiring-darknet-hitman-to-kidnap-wife-denied-bail/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</title>
		<link>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Jun 2021 13:56:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=647</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Analysis by blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis revealed that the Russia-based Hydra darknet market is outpacing the growth</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/">Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Analysis by blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis <a href="https://go.chainalysis.com/crypto-crime-money-laundering-recording.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">revealed</a> that the Russia-based <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a> darknet market is outpacing the growth of competition at an alarming rate. In a presentation broadcast live yesterday, researchers from Chainalysis and Flashpoint described the unprecedented growth of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">H</a><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/">ydra</a>, noting that its monthly transaction volume was roughly 2.5x greater than all other darknet markets summed together.</p>



<p>By the end of 2020, <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a> was averaging roughly $160 million in transactions per month, while all other markets averaged about $35 million in total. The findings suggest that Hydra is single-handedly driving the growth of darknet market activity.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="886" height="543" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra.png" alt="" class="wp-image-649" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra.png 886w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra-300x184.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/hydra-768x471.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 886px) 100vw, 886px" /><figcaption>Source: Chainalysis</figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>The presentation also included findings from Hydra’s 2021 activity thus far, as well, noting that transactions over $100,000 in size were on the rise in the first half of the year. A number of transactions over $1 million to the market were also reported.</p>



<p>Of all funds sent to Hydra, about 20% ended up going through Bitcoin mixing services and “high risk exchanges.” The research also found that Hydra was becoming increasingly popular as a cashout option among those looking to perform money laundering of their own.</p>



<p>“These crypto laundering services are significantly more popular and sought after as verification requirements are becoming more and more stringent,” said Vlad Cuiujuclu, Team Lead from Flashpoint.</p>



<p>According to the researchers, darknet market activity is “remarkably consistent,” and the only major disruptions experienced are due to market closures. They also found that fluctuations in the price of BTC are irrelevant to activity.</p>



<p>Chainalysis had previously pinpointed Hydra as <a href="https://www.flashpoint-intel.com/blog/chainalysis-hydra-cryptocurrency-research/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the place where money trails come to an end</a>. BTC sent to the market is largely traded into fiat through Russia’s clandestine network of unregulated money exchangers, making it impossible to trace where the funds go next. The local government’s apparent unwillingness to dismantle the market has increased its reputation as a haven for darknet vendors.</p>



<p>“Whatever is operating and based in Russia is only under the watch of Russian law enforcement,” commented Andras Toth-Czifra, Senior Analyst at Flashpoint. “And it’s up to them to shut down those marketplaces or arrest the owners.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/">Hydra Activity 250% Greater Than All Other Darknet Markets Combined</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>FBI’s Unexpected Recovery of BTC from Ransomware Group Ignites Market Panic</title>
		<link>/fbis-unexpected-recovery-of-btc-from-ransomware-group-ignites-market-panic/</link>
					<comments>/fbis-unexpected-recovery-of-btc-from-ransomware-group-ignites-market-panic/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 08 Jun 2021 13:22:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darkside]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fbi]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hackers]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=611</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>No, the FBI did not just “hack Bitcoin.” The price of Bitcoin suffered a FUD-fueled sell-off after the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fbis-unexpected-recovery-of-btc-from-ransomware-group-ignites-market-panic/">FBI’s Unexpected Recovery of BTC from Ransomware Group Ignites Market Panic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>No, the FBI did not just “hack Bitcoin.”</em></p>



<p>The price of Bitcoin suffered a FUD-fueled sell-off after the U.S. Department of Justice filed a public <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1402056/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">court document</a> today, supporting the seizure of 63.7 BTC from the Colonial Pipeline ransomware attackers. The seizure, performed by a <a href="https://www.npr.org/2021/06/08/1004223000/how-a-new-team-of-feds-hacked-the-hackers-and-got-colonial-pipelines-bitcoin-bac" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">newly assembled unit in the FBI</a>, had occurred just hours earlier. News of the unexpected recovery spread quickly on <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/07/politics/colonial-pipeline-ransomware-recovered/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">mainstream news outlets</a> after a brief press conference by the Department of Justice.</p>



<p>A lack of clarity by the DoJ and abundance of speculation on social media led some to believe that <a href="https://decrypt.co/72992/bitcoin-tumbles-9-fears-that-us-law-enforcement-hacked-network" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the FBI had actually managed to hack the Bitcoin network</a>. This would involve “reverse-engineering” or “brute forcing” their way into finding the private key of the address in question &#8211; a feat long considered impossible &#8211; even with today’s top-of-the-line quantum computers.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="905" height="409" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-613" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1.png 905w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-300x136.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/1-768x347.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 905px) 100vw, 905px" /></figure>



<p><em>Source: </em><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1402056/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>court filing</em></a><em> in the U.S. District Court of Northern California, San Francisco</em></p>



<p>The confusion was compounded by <a href="https://www.businessinsider.com/fbi-used-hackers-bitcoin-password-to-recover-colonial-pipeline-ransom-2021-6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">incorrect characterizations</a> of what had occurred by several popular websites. The overwhelming wave of negativity triggered a sudden sell-off in the price of BTC, which fell from $35,500 to a low of $32,200 across the day, representing a loss of 9.3%.</p>



<p>Not long after the press conference, a <a href="https://twitter.com/JordanSchachtel/status/1401996717394960389/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">warrant</a> was found online related to the seizure which revealed that the FBI had determined the BTC in question was being held in Northern California; most likely by a web wallet service or exchange. The discovery quickly led to the deduction that investigators had not actually managed to “crack” the private key of the address holding the ill-gotten Bitcoin, but rather received it from a California-based company.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">I&#39;m having a tough time believing that this supposedly Russian hacking network was so sophisticated it could shut down our infrastructure, but not knowledgable enough to maintain safe custody over their bitcoin.<br><br>We&#39;re missing the whole story, here&#8230;.</p>&mdash; Jordan Schachtel (@JordanSchachtel) <a href="https://twitter.com/JordanSchachtel/status/1401988543493332994?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 7, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>According to journalist Jordan Schachtel who <a href="https://twitter.com/JordanSchachtel/status/1402010089075183617" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">covered</a> the incident throughout the day, “The entity responsible for the ransomware attack did not in fact have custody over their bitcoin. Instead, they were using a custodian for their funds with servers in the United States.” Schachtel noted the inconsistencies of stories in mainstream media and was quick to dispel incorrect assumptions made by their authors.</p>



<p>“To be clear, there was no hack. Feds did not do something innovative here. They used legal mechanisms and tracked a publicly available ledger to secure the bitcoin from this alleged hacking group.”</p>



<p>Adam Back, the Bitcoin developer employed by Blockstream, provided further confirmation that <a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us/status/1402179970277982210" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">the FBI did not “hack” Bitcoin</a>, and that the panic rocking the market was indeed overblown.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/Bitcoin?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#Bitcoin</a> was NOT hacked<br>No bitcoin wallet was hacked, nor is even known to be possible. Ransom hackers used a rented cloud server. FBI got a subpoena and took control of it and recovered coins. That&#39;s it.</p>&mdash; Adam Back (@adam3us) <a href="https://twitter.com/adam3us/status/1402179970277982210?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 8, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Additionally, it appears the effects of the sudden seizure have forced DarkSide, the ransomware group behind the attack, <a href="https://krebsonsecurity.com/2021/05/darkside-ransomware-gang-quits-after-servers-bitcoin-stash-seized/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">into an early retirement</a>. According to KrebsOnSecurity, a message posted by a DarkSide admin on Telegram confirmed the organization had lost access to their infrastructure, and as a result would be ceasing operations. The admin also stated DarkSide would provide decryption tools to infected companies who did not pay a ransom to regain access to their files.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fbis-unexpected-recovery-of-btc-from-ransomware-group-ignites-market-panic/">FBI’s Unexpected Recovery of BTC from Ransomware Group Ignites Market Panic</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fbis-unexpected-recovery-of-btc-from-ransomware-group-ignites-market-panic/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</title>
		<link>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/</link>
					<comments>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 25 May 2021 10:06:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=589</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Scott Berkett thought he hired a darknet killer to dispatch a woman who rejected him. A Beverly Hills</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/">California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Scott Berkett thought he hired a darknet killer to dispatch a woman who rejected him.</p>



<p>A Beverly Hills man arrested on charges pertaining to murder-for-hire last week was <a href="https://losangeles.cbslocal.com/2021/05/24/beverly-hills-man-arrested-friday-in-alleged-murder-for-hire-plot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">granted a detention hearing</a> yesterday to determine if he is a flight risk. Federal prosecutors <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-cdca/pr/beverly-hills-man-arrested-federal-charges-attempting-hire-hitman-murder-one-time" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">allege</a> that Scott Quinn Berkett, 24, made payments totaling $14,000 in Bitcoin to what he thought was a professional <a href="/hire-hitman-deep-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hitman</a> service to have a previous acquaintance murdered.</p>



<p>In a court affidavit filed May 21, prosecutors describe how investigators had been made aware of Berkett’s plans by a foreign media outlet. The media outlet had themselves been tipped off by an anonymous party thought to be the owner of the darknet-hosted <a href="/hire-hitman-deep-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hitman</a> service. The service itself is most likely a scam.</p>



<p>Court documents describe how Berkett met his intended target online, where they shared duties of administrator for a Facebook group dedicated to the animated television series RWBY. The target, an unidentified woman, flew out to Los Angeles in 2019 to meet Berkett at his request. She described Berkett to investigators as “sexually aggressive” during the encounter and cut off contact with him after returning home.</p>



<p>According to the affidavit, information provided by the media outlet was “very specific about the identity and location” of the woman, “as well as social media accounts, nicknames, email and a distinctive tattoo.”</p>



<p>The outlet also provided investigators with “transaction information from an unnamed source on the Dark Web.” Prosecutors believe the transactions demonstrate that “Bitcoin payments were made with an understanding that an unknown individual would murder (the target).”</p>



<p>Of the $14,000 Berkett allegedly paid for the task, payments totaling $13,000 in BTC went to the darknet site owner, with the final $1,000 paid to an undercover investigator posing as a professional killer, which he had met on WhatsApp days earlier. Rather than making what would be the final payment in Bitcoin, Berkett was instructed to send the funds via Western Union. He was then videotaped outside of the Western Union office around the time the transaction was processed, further lending evidence to his guilt.</p>



<p>If convicted, Berkett faces a minimum 10-year prison sentence.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/">California Man Heads Back to Court in Bitcoin Murder-For-Hire Case</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/california-man-heads-back-to-court-in-bitcoin-murder-for-hire-case/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US ramping up crackdown on Bitcoin mixers, tax evaders</title>
		<link>/us-ramping-up-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixers-tax-evaders/</link>
					<comments>/us-ramping-up-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixers-tax-evaders/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 08:14:08 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin mixer]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=543</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Recent court rulings and IRS guidance show the US government is taking a hard stance against large, unregulated</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-ramping-up-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixers-tax-evaders/">US ramping up crackdown on Bitcoin mixers, tax evaders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Recent court rulings and IRS guidance show the US government is taking a hard stance against large, unregulated cryptocurrency transactions, coming down on Bitcoin mixing services in particular. A research report by law firm Rahman Ravelli describes the Department of Justice’s view on mixers to be “dim,” noting that any such service that could be used to launder money is “potentially in the cross hairs of US law enforcement.”</p>



<p>Toward the end of April &#8211; less than a month before the IRS said that <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2021/05/20/us-treasury-calls-for-stricter-cryptocurrency-compliance-with-irs.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">cryptocurrencies create tax evasion risk</a> – there were two particularly unfavorable legal developments for Bitcoin mixers:</p>



<ul><li>The alleged operator of Bitcoin Fog, a Swedish/Russian national living in California, was <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/bitcoin-fog-dark-web-cryptocurrency-arrest/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrested</a> at the Los Angeles International Airport after ten years on the run, accused of having laundered 1.2 million BTC across ten years.</li><li>Federal charges against the operator of Helix, a Bitcoin mixer which allegedly tumbled some 354,000+ BTC while in service, will go forward as planned after a judge <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/opinion/4874437/united-states-v-harmon/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">denied</a> the defendant’s motion to dismiss the case.</li></ul>



<p>The arrests and charges reflect an increased level of scrutiny over services the government considers to be “unlicensed money transmitters” (such as mixers), and in line with tax policy changes recently unveiled by other branches of the government.</p>



<p>According to a <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/system/files/136/The-American-Families-Plan-Tax-Compliance-Agenda.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">tax plan guide</a> released by the Department of Treasury, “Cryptocurrency already poses a significant detection problem by facilitating illegal activity broadly including tax evasion.” The guide explains that the IRS now considers cryptocurrency transactions to be an “enforcement priority,” even including a new spot for crypto reporting on the standard 1040 income reporting form.</p>



<p>The guide clarifies that businesses only need to report crypto transactions if they are over $10,000 in value, as they would for a cash transaction. The DoT emphasizes that the new guidelines are aimed primarily at curbing tax evasion committed by “the top end of the income distribution.” This includes those who have access to “sophisticated strategies” to help them launder large amounts of cash.</p>



<p>One such strategy was described as “moving taxable assets into the crypto economy,” which potentially involves the use of crypto mixing services.</p>



<p>The IRS news coincides with a significant market correction which saw several top cryptocurrencies drop 30-50% in price in less than 24 hours; many of which have since exhibited signs of recovery.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-ramping-up-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixers-tax-evaders/">US ramping up crackdown on Bitcoin mixers, tax evaders</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/us-ramping-up-crackdown-on-bitcoin-mixers-tax-evaders/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:56:32 by W3 Total Cache
-->