<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>hydra market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/hydra-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>hydra market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over one ton of drugs was seized in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over one ton of drugs was <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/russian-police-say-caught-drug-gang-led-by-uk-1504121.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">seized</a> in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation into 26 individuals believed to have been operating a shop on the former Hydra darknet marketplace. The criminal group, led by Ukrainian nationals, organized the production of the drugs and their sale in Russia under the name “Murmur Shop,” which operated on Hydra between 2019 and 2021.</p>



<p>According to investigators, the group included 15 people from Ukraine, seven from Russia, two from Moldova, one from Tajikistan, and one from Belarus. While the leadership was based in Ukraine, Russian nationals were hired to help transport the drugs to <a href="https://aif.ru/society/law/v_mosgorsud_napravili_delo_mezhdunarodnoy_gruppy_iz_26_narkotorgovcev" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">more than 60 constituent entities</a> across the Russian Federation. Four clandestine drug laboratories in the Moscow, Vladimir and Ivanovo regions were also uncovered during the investigation.</p>



<p>“The leadership of the drug group and the management of its financial assets was carried out from the territory of Ukraine,” said Irina Volk, a spokeswoman for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs, on Thursday. “The recruitment of laboratory staff was also carried out there for the further dispatch to Russia. Applicants were forced to undergo polygraph tests,” she added.</p>



<p>In early April, Hydra’s servers were <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">s</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ei</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zed</a> in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement, knocking the world’s biggest darknet market offline in the process. Days earlier, the US Department of Justice had filed sanctions against Hydra and an online money exchanger known to be associated with the market. On April 11<sup>th</sup>, the Meshchansky Court of Moscow arrested Dmitry Pavlov, one of the alleged founders of the online drug platform.</p>



<p>In January, a group of Russian nationals were <a href="https://www.gazeta.ru/social/news/2022/01/20/17168629.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> for their roles in importing cocaine from Argentina, some of which had been hidden at the Russian embassy in Buenos Aires. The group’s mastermind was sentenced to 18 years in a penal colony while other members received sentences between 13 and 17 years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of Hydra, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been arrested</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been <a href="https://www.mskagency.ru/materials/3204351" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Russia per reports from the Meshchansky District Court in Moscow. The report names Dmitry Pavlov – a Russian citizen – as arrested on charges pertaining to “illegal drug trafficking on an especially large scale.” He faces up to 20 years in prison if convicted on the charges.</p>



<p>The arrest, which took place on April 11<sup>th</sup>, occurred less than a <a href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">week after Hydra’s servers</a> were knocked offline in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. German police also managed to confiscate about $25 million in Bitcoin during their takedown of the market.</p>



<p>The US Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-investigation-leads-shutdown-largest-online-darknet-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> its own charges against Pavlov on April 5<sup>th</sup>, which include conspiracy to distribute narcotics and conspiracy to commit money laundering. He is also <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1490906/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">named</a> as a Hydra admin and provider of hosting services for the now-defunct darknet market, which had been in steady operation since 2015.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia has arrested the alleged co-founder of dark web platform Hydra a week after American and German authorities said they shut down what they called the world’s largest illegal darknet marketplace.</p>&mdash; Fuad Alakbarov ⁠⁠ (@DrAlakbarov) <a href="https://twitter.com/DrAlakbarov/status/1514901753392680964?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 15, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Pavlov <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/alleged-hydra-administrator-dmitry-pavlov-reportedly-arrested-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stated</a> on April 6<sup>th</sup> that he had only been informed of the charges against him via the media, and that he had not been contacted by US authorities. He also said the server provision business he ran, in which he leased servers to other businesses, was fully-licensed and registered with Roskomanadzor, the Russian communications bureau. Pavlov also denied allegations of being a Hydra admin, claiming he did not have administration duties on any website.</p>



<p>“We are a hosting company and have all the necessary communications licenses,” Pavlov told BBC’s Russian service in an interview last week. “We don’t administer any sites but only provide servers for rent as intermediaries.”</p>



<p>Cybersecurity experts who had been investigating Hydra told <em>The Moscow Times </em>that <a href="https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2022/04/15/russia-arrests-alleged-co-founder-of-worlds-largest-darknet-marketplace-a77363" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russia had been monitoring the market since its inception</a>, and speculated that it was possible for Hydra to make a re-appearance under a different domain, hosted on different servers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/</link>
					<comments>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hydra, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. On Tuesday, April 5<sup>th</sup>, Federal police in Germany shut down servers hosting the market’s main URL on the dark web that were located within the country, seizing approximately $25 million in bitcoin in the process.</p>



<p>In a statement, federal police said they were also investigating unnamed individuals believed to be &#8220;operating criminal trading platforms on the internet on a commercial basis.”</p>



<p>Hydra was thought to have a userbase consisting of over 19,000 vendors, 2.5 million regular users, and 17 million registered clients overall. Blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis estimate that <a href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">roughly $3.4 billion in BTC transactions had transpired</a> at the market over its lifetime, with much of the proceeds collected by admins being passed on to legitimate cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>



<p>Though Hydra was long-believed to be operating out of Russia, yesterday’s reveal of its servers being hosted in Germany – along with other recently-uncovered factors – suggests this was never actually the case.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="960" height="535" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1415" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-300x167.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-768x428.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /><figcaption><em>Screenshot of the Hydra darknet marketplace taken during November 2021.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>In February, two Ukrainian-based individuals were named as “responsible for Hydra’s operations” based on an <a href="https://geminiadvisory.io/alleged-hydra-market-operators-identified-6/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">assessment</a> of recently-released information performed by the dark web intelligence-gathering company, Gemini Advisory. The information, initially posted by an anonymous individual behind the hydra.expert domain, was partially confirmed by Gemini and revealed that JavaScript found to be embedded in the marketplace contained the names of the two Hydra masterminds as file authors.</p>



<p>An <a href="https://archive.ph/cFQy6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">archived version</a> of hydra.expert details the process by which the two Ukrainian nationals were identified, breaking down the JavaScript code supposedly uncovered from the market and detailing an investigation into the subdomains associated with a domain mentioned in it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The United States is sanctioning the world’s largest darknet market for Russian speakers, Hydra, and the virtual currency exchange Garantex. Today’s action, coordinated with <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1ea.png" alt="🇩🇪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, demonstrates our commitment to continue disrupting ransomware infrastructure and actors.</p>&mdash; Secretary Antony Blinken (@SecBlinken) <a href="https://twitter.com/SecBlinken/status/1511433500154478592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 5, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The Russian-language market, founded in 2015, had also recently been <a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">placed unde</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r sanctio</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ns by the US</a> in an effort to cripple financial infrastructure used by cybercriminals associated with massive ransomware attacks that interrupted supply lines across much of the country throughout 2021. It suffered very little downtime during its nearly-seven years in operation, going offline only a few times; the most recent of which was during the early stages of the pandemic.</p>



<p>A Bitcoin-only market, Hydra limited services and sales to residents of countries comprising the former USSR. It made heavy use of the “dead drop” product delivery system through which buyers would dig up or uncover purchases (referred to as “treasures”) hidden at pre-specified locations, thus avoiding use of traditional postal delivery systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</title>
		<link>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 04 Aug 2021 22:09:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[v3 link]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=734</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The long awaited V3 onion Hydra Market link has finally been published. Hydra Market new V3 onion url</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/">Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The long awaited V3 onion Hydra Market link has finally been published.</p>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> new V3 onion url &#8211; <a href="http://hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion</a></p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="454" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-1024x454.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-738" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-1024x454.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-300x133.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3-768x341.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra3.jpg 1522w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> is the last dark net market to publish its V3 onion link, long after the rest of the dark net community has moved to V3 links and disabled their V2 onion links.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="184" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-1024x184.png" alt="" class="wp-image-737" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-1024x184.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-300x54.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2-768x138.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/08/hydra2.png 1128w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> admin has published on Hydra Market forum-<br></p>



<pre class="wp-block-code"><code>Dear users, in the near future the site will open at: hydram6esdjf6otepmr5c3vjyndsoddz22afphbbjznwb5ln2c6op7ad.onion
Forwarding will be enabled on other mirrors. </code></pre>



<p>V2 onion links are expected to be disabled by the tor team on October of 2021. It is advised to save the new link and bookmark it.</p>



<p>Our <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Darknet list</a> will always have the updated links of all the darknet markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/">Hydra Market Finally Publish V3 Onion Link</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-market-finally-publish-v3-onion-link/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>8</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Market Announces Switch to V3 Onion Links Soon</title>
		<link>/hydra-market-announces-switch-to-v3-onion-links-soon/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-market-announces-switch-to-v3-onion-links-soon/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 19 Jul 2021 18:10:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=700</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>With the Tor project turning off V2 onion links in October, most of the dark net markets have</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-announces-switch-to-v3-onion-links-soon/">Hydra Market Announces Switch to V3 Onion Links Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>With the Tor project turning off V2 onion links in October, most of the dark net markets have switched to V3 onion address, However <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market</a> has still to do so.</p>



<p>Recently it was published that <a href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market has made more than 1.3 billion dollars in 2020</a>, and now in a recent forum post they have announced that the switch will come soon.</p>



<p>Active user browser users have already noticed a warning that this address will soon cease to work.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="700" height="544" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-701" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra1.jpg 700w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra1-300x233.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 700px) 100vw, 700px" /></figure>



<p>As well as when attaching a pop-up tip on the changed icon.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="648" height="231" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra2.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-702" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra2.jpg 648w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/hydra2-300x107.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 648px) 100vw, 648px" /></figure>



<p>All this does not mean Hydra will cease to work.<br>This message is a notification of the network that soon supporting the onion addresses of the old sample is referred to.<br>Hydra will provide the transition to new ONION V3 addresses, what users will be notified in advance. Information and new addresses will be posted on the main page of the site.</p>



<p><strong>Q: Addresses v2 will work?</strong><br>Oh yeah. Old V2 addresses will work in parallel with the new V3 addresses up to the network of the TOR network on October 15, 2021, when the transition to a new standard will be transmitted and the corresponding code update will be released.</p>



<p><strong>Q: Why can&#8217;t I open Hydra now?</strong><br>A: Old (short) addresses can no longer be opened in Tor browser version 0.4.6 and below.</p>



<p><strong>Q: How do I find out what version of the address?</strong><br>A: The new ONION V3 addresses will be visually different, as they will be 56 characters.</p>



<p><strong>Q: When will the V3 Hydra addresses appear?</strong><br>A: Soon information and new addresses will be published on the main page of the site.</p>



<p><strong>Q: What will happen to insulated shops?</strong><br>A: With the network transition on Onion V3 domains, we stop provide an isolated shopping service.</p>



<p>Ofcourse any new links that will published will be updated on our <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra Market page</a> and our <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Darknet Markets list</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-market-announces-switch-to-v3-onion-links-soon/">Hydra Market Announces Switch to V3 Onion Links Soon</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-market-announces-switch-to-v3-onion-links-soon/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:08:07 by W3 Total Cache
-->