<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>darknet arrest &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/darknet-arrest/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>darknet arrest &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over one ton of drugs was seized in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over one ton of drugs was <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/russian-police-say-caught-drug-gang-led-by-uk-1504121.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">seized</a> in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation into 26 individuals believed to have been operating a shop on the former Hydra darknet marketplace. The criminal group, led by Ukrainian nationals, organized the production of the drugs and their sale in Russia under the name “Murmur Shop,” which operated on Hydra between 2019 and 2021.</p>



<p>According to investigators, the group included 15 people from Ukraine, seven from Russia, two from Moldova, one from Tajikistan, and one from Belarus. While the leadership was based in Ukraine, Russian nationals were hired to help transport the drugs to <a href="https://aif.ru/society/law/v_mosgorsud_napravili_delo_mezhdunarodnoy_gruppy_iz_26_narkotorgovcev" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">more than 60 constituent entities</a> across the Russian Federation. Four clandestine drug laboratories in the Moscow, Vladimir and Ivanovo regions were also uncovered during the investigation.</p>



<p>“The leadership of the drug group and the management of its financial assets was carried out from the territory of Ukraine,” said Irina Volk, a spokeswoman for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs, on Thursday. “The recruitment of laboratory staff was also carried out there for the further dispatch to Russia. Applicants were forced to undergo polygraph tests,” she added.</p>



<p>In early April, Hydra’s servers were <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">s</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ei</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zed</a> in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement, knocking the world’s biggest darknet market offline in the process. Days earlier, the US Department of Justice had filed sanctions against Hydra and an online money exchanger known to be associated with the market. On April 11<sup>th</sup>, the Meshchansky Court of Moscow arrested Dmitry Pavlov, one of the alleged founders of the online drug platform.</p>



<p>In January, a group of Russian nationals were <a href="https://www.gazeta.ru/social/news/2022/01/20/17168629.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> for their roles in importing cocaine from Argentina, some of which had been hidden at the Russian embassy in Buenos Aires. The group’s mastermind was sentenced to 18 years in a penal colony while other members received sentences between 13 and 17 years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</title>
		<link>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/</link>
					<comments>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1444</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a Tampa Bay woman was <a href="https://www.tampabay.com/news/tampa/2022/04/20/tampa-woman-gets-6-years-in-prison-for-dark-web-murder-for-hire/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced to six and a half years</a> in prison on Wednesday for using one such darknet site to order the murder of her ex-boyfriend’s wife.</p>



<p>A US District Judge ordered DeAnna Marie Stinson, 51, to serve the time and pay $12,000 in restitution for attempting to hire a hitman through one of the well-known fake hitman sites on the dark web &#8212; whose operators had <a href="https://gizmodo.com/besa-mafia-alleged-ringleaders-arrested-1848769128" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">recently been apprehended</a> by Romanian authorities.</p>



<p>Stinson admitted to attempting to hire what she believed was a professional assassin from a Besa Mafia site in exchange for <a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">payments</a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> </a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">totaling $12,307 in Bitcoin</a>. She also provided a photo of the intended victim, along with their name and address. The “assassin” turned out to be a US federal investigator who was likely tipped off to Stinson’s intentions by one of the site’s admins.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Tampa Accountant Sentenced to More Than Six Years in Federal Prison for Plotting a Murder-for-Hire: DeAnna Marie Stinson of Tampa has been sentenced to six years and six months in federal prison for murder-for-hire. <a href="https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv">https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv</a></p>&mdash; FBI Tampa (@FBITampa) <a href="https://twitter.com/FBITampa/status/1517179243406381065?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“I cited the old adage, ‘hell hath no fury like a woman scorned,’” said Federal Defender Alec Hall to the judge during Stinson’s sentencing, adding, “I think that’s what happened in this case.”</p>



<p>Stinson pleaded guilty to the charges in January.</p>



<p>Sprawling across a number of similar-looking darknet sites, the Besa Mafia operation has been known to exist since at least 2015, and famously <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">suffered a</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> dat</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a breach</a> in May 2016 in which they were firmly outed as a scam. On the site which Stinson traversed, “death by shooting” started at a rate of $5,000, while a “beating” was listed for $2,000. At the top of the supposed services list was “death by sniper,” which was priced at $20,000.</p>



<p>The Besa Mafia admins were captured earlier this month as the result of a US-based investigation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of Hydra, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been arrested</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been <a href="https://www.mskagency.ru/materials/3204351" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Russia per reports from the Meshchansky District Court in Moscow. The report names Dmitry Pavlov – a Russian citizen – as arrested on charges pertaining to “illegal drug trafficking on an especially large scale.” He faces up to 20 years in prison if convicted on the charges.</p>



<p>The arrest, which took place on April 11<sup>th</sup>, occurred less than a <a href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">week after Hydra’s servers</a> were knocked offline in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. German police also managed to confiscate about $25 million in Bitcoin during their takedown of the market.</p>



<p>The US Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-investigation-leads-shutdown-largest-online-darknet-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> its own charges against Pavlov on April 5<sup>th</sup>, which include conspiracy to distribute narcotics and conspiracy to commit money laundering. He is also <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1490906/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">named</a> as a Hydra admin and provider of hosting services for the now-defunct darknet market, which had been in steady operation since 2015.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia has arrested the alleged co-founder of dark web platform Hydra a week after American and German authorities said they shut down what they called the world’s largest illegal darknet marketplace.</p>&mdash; Fuad Alakbarov ⁠⁠ (@DrAlakbarov) <a href="https://twitter.com/DrAlakbarov/status/1514901753392680964?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 15, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Pavlov <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/alleged-hydra-administrator-dmitry-pavlov-reportedly-arrested-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stated</a> on April 6<sup>th</sup> that he had only been informed of the charges against him via the media, and that he had not been contacted by US authorities. He also said the server provision business he ran, in which he leased servers to other businesses, was fully-licensed and registered with Roskomanadzor, the Russian communications bureau. Pavlov also denied allegations of being a Hydra admin, claiming he did not have administration duties on any website.</p>



<p>“We are a hosting company and have all the necessary communications licenses,” Pavlov told BBC’s Russian service in an interview last week. “We don’t administer any sites but only provide servers for rent as intermediaries.”</p>



<p>Cybersecurity experts who had been investigating Hydra told <em>The Moscow Times </em>that <a href="https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2022/04/15/russia-arrests-alleged-co-founder-of-worlds-largest-darknet-marketplace-a77363" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russia had been monitoring the market since its inception</a>, and speculated that it was possible for Hydra to make a re-appearance under a different domain, hosted on different servers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</title>
		<link>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/</link>
					<comments>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 14:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web were <a href="https://diicot.ro/mass-media/3498-comunicat-de-presa-3-06-04-2022" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Romania on April 6th, after years of steady operation. The arrests were performed at the behest of US authorities who had been investigating the sites and managed to link them to a group of Romanian citizens.</p>



<p>Seven house raids were performed in relation to the takedown, in the counties of Gorj and Hunedoara; the result of warrants issued against five suspects and four “witnesses.” The amount of financial damage directly linked to the sites’ operation was estimated to be around 500,000 EUR, although the total tally they collected over the years is likely to be far greater.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Yura (presumably), the owner of Besa Mafia, history&#39;s most profitably dark web murder-for-hire website has been arrested. I spent years corresponding with him about his business.</p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1512316762095710210?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 8, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Perhaps the most notorious type of darknet market, murder-for-hire sites have been a part of the dark web since just a year or two after the closure of the original <em>Silk Road</em> marketplace. However, it has been known for quite some time that just about <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/mg77bn/this-fake-hitman-site-is-the-most-elaborate-twisted-dark-web-scam-yet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">all of them are fake</a> &#8212; scam sites designed to separate vengeful parties from decent-to-large sums of Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The most famous of these sites was run by a group calling themselves the <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Besa M</em></a><em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">a</a></em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>fia</em></a>, of which the five arrested suspects are presumed to comprise. Other sites operated by the group are thought to include <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7d8j3/the-alleged-scammers-behind-the-most-notorious-murder-for-hire-site-have-been-arrested" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><u><em>Camorra Hitman</em> and <em>#1 Hitman Marketplace</em></u></a>, along with a list of less-famous names.</p>



<p>Besides being complete scams, all these sites shared the common feature of purporting to link “real hitmen” with a client looking for violence to be performed upon a particular victim &#8212; whether it be a beating, stabbing, torture, or even murder. Prices for these services usually ranged between $5,000 and $20,000, payable in Bitcoin, but never resulted in the actual delivery of service. Instead, clients were likely to become the subject of a police investigation, and dozens of arrests have been performed over the years for charges related to this type of attempted murder.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Flowchart of Besa Mafia&#39;s Business Model For Fake Hitman Dark Web Scam <a href="https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY">https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY</a> <a href="https://t.co/CKsjvS6TZI">pic.twitter.com/CKsjvS6TZI</a></p>&mdash; Arnout de Vries (@ADeVries23) <a href="https://twitter.com/ADeVries23/status/733185111064236032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 19, 2016</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>While <a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">real m</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">urder</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">-for-hire sites</a> have been found to exist on the dark web, they are not advertised in the transparent fashion of the <em>Besa Mafia</em> sites (which were usually found via darknet link lists) and are nearly impossible to stumble upon.</p>



<p>The arrests were the result of a joint operation between the US Homeland Security Investigations and the US Embassy in Bucharest, performed by police officers from Romania’s Service for Combating Cybercrime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/</link>
					<comments>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hydra, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. On Tuesday, April 5<sup>th</sup>, Federal police in Germany shut down servers hosting the market’s main URL on the dark web that were located within the country, seizing approximately $25 million in bitcoin in the process.</p>



<p>In a statement, federal police said they were also investigating unnamed individuals believed to be &#8220;operating criminal trading platforms on the internet on a commercial basis.”</p>



<p>Hydra was thought to have a userbase consisting of over 19,000 vendors, 2.5 million regular users, and 17 million registered clients overall. Blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis estimate that <a href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">roughly $3.4 billion in BTC transactions had transpired</a> at the market over its lifetime, with much of the proceeds collected by admins being passed on to legitimate cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>



<p>Though Hydra was long-believed to be operating out of Russia, yesterday’s reveal of its servers being hosted in Germany – along with other recently-uncovered factors – suggests this was never actually the case.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="960" height="535" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1415" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-300x167.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-768x428.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /><figcaption><em>Screenshot of the Hydra darknet marketplace taken during November 2021.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>In February, two Ukrainian-based individuals were named as “responsible for Hydra’s operations” based on an <a href="https://geminiadvisory.io/alleged-hydra-market-operators-identified-6/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">assessment</a> of recently-released information performed by the dark web intelligence-gathering company, Gemini Advisory. The information, initially posted by an anonymous individual behind the hydra.expert domain, was partially confirmed by Gemini and revealed that JavaScript found to be embedded in the marketplace contained the names of the two Hydra masterminds as file authors.</p>



<p>An <a href="https://archive.ph/cFQy6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">archived version</a> of hydra.expert details the process by which the two Ukrainian nationals were identified, breaking down the JavaScript code supposedly uncovered from the market and detailing an investigation into the subdomains associated with a domain mentioned in it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The United States is sanctioning the world’s largest darknet market for Russian speakers, Hydra, and the virtual currency exchange Garantex. Today’s action, coordinated with <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1ea.png" alt="🇩🇪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, demonstrates our commitment to continue disrupting ransomware infrastructure and actors.</p>&mdash; Secretary Antony Blinken (@SecBlinken) <a href="https://twitter.com/SecBlinken/status/1511433500154478592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 5, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The Russian-language market, founded in 2015, had also recently been <a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">placed unde</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r sanctio</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ns by the US</a> in an effort to cripple financial infrastructure used by cybercriminals associated with massive ransomware attacks that interrupted supply lines across much of the country throughout 2021. It suffered very little downtime during its nearly-seven years in operation, going offline only a few times; the most recent of which was during the early stages of the pandemic.</p>



<p>A Bitcoin-only market, Hydra limited services and sales to residents of countries comprising the former USSR. It made heavy use of the “dead drop” product delivery system through which buyers would dig up or uncover purchases (referred to as “treasures”) hidden at pre-specified locations, thus avoiding use of traditional postal delivery systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</title>
		<link>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/</link>
					<comments>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 25-year-old US man was ordered to pay $2.3 million in Bitcoin proceeds late last week and sentenced</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/">Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 25-year-old US man was <a href="https://cryptoinsidermag.com/ecstasy-kingpin-from-brockton-forfeits-2-3m-in-bitcoin-to-massachusetts-law-enforcement/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ordered to pay $2.3 million</a> in Bitcoin proceeds late last week and sentenced to eight years in prison for his principal role in the EastSideHigh darknet market vendor operation. Binh Thanh Le, of Brockton, Massachusetts, opened for business under the vendor name on Wall Street Market in 2018, when he was only 22 years old.</p>



<p>Le, <a href="https://www.bostonherald.com/2022/03/12/darknet-ecstasy-kingpin-from-brockton-to-serve-8-years-in-prison-forfeit-2-3-million-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">described</a> by local media as a darknet “kingpin,” managed to raise 59 BTC during his brief career on Wall Street Market with the help of two associates, selling Ecstasy, Xanax, and ketamine in bulk quantities. He was indicted in June 2019 for conspiracy to manufacture and distribute narcotics.</p>



<p>Federal agents managed to track Le down through a series of fictitious business names he used for drug transportation purposes, with the help of local postal inspectors. Agents also intercepted packages being delivered to the fake business addresses from international importers, arriving from Canada, Belgium, and the Netherlands.</p>



<p>The intercepted packages shared a common trait of being labeled as “Lego box(es) for kids.” While the packages did contain actual boxes for Lego toys, the toys had been removed and replaced with vacuum-sealed bags containing drugs to be repackaged and sold on Wall Street Market.</p>



<p>EastSideHigh’s disappearance from Wall Street Market and the Dread forum – two places where the vendor maintained consistent communication with their customers – coincided with <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ma/pr/three-brockton-men-indicted-selling-drugs-dark-web" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Le’s arrest</a>, which occurred on Mar 27<sup>th</sup>, 2019. On that day, Le unwittingly met with undercover officers in a Massachusetts hotel to perform a Bitcoin-for-cash exchange of $150,000.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="579" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-1024x579.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1380" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-1024x579.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-300x170.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-768x434.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><em>Binh Thanh Le, next to two co-conspirators, headed to a hearing after their 2019 arrest. Source: The Patriot Ledger</em></p>



<p>“I imagine this kind of situation is so tempting for vendors,” wrote Dread user <em>TurboSnail</em> in reference to the BTC-for-cash setup, in a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/68dd001b20631f25d9f3/#c-5df9a56332b87a52e0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> dated almost two years ago, shortly after news broke of Le’s arrest. “Many have the contacts and knowledge to sell product, but then fall short when it comes to turning all that crypto into real world cash,” they added. “Then along comes MrFriendlyMoneyLaunderer who offers irl cash in exchange for a quiet chat at a local hotel lol.”</p>



<p>A co-conspirator believed to be part of the vendor operation was also arrested at the hotel where Le met with the undercover officers. In addition, an alleged third member was arrested at a storage facility associated with the operation, where law enforcement confiscated 6,200 grams of MDMA, 5,000 grams of ketamine, and more than 10,000 generic Xanax pills. The two co-conspirators have pleaded not guilty to related charges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/">Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</title>
		<link>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/</link>
					<comments>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 10 Feb 2022 10:57:14 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1319</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>What was initially believed to be hackers at work on Jan 31 turned out to be the world’s</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/">Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>What was initially believed to be hackers at work on Jan 31 turned out to be the <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">worl</a><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">d’s</a><a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> biggest-ever federal seizure of funds</a>, involving the recovery of some $3.6 billion in Bitcoin stolen from Bitfinex during a 2016 hack. The original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay darknet market</a> was mentioned as a money laundering utility for the funds in court documents, though the exact amount of BTC moved through the market was not mentioned.</p>



<p>Husband Ilya Lichtenstein, 34, and wife Heather Morgan (aka ‘Razzlekhan’), 31, are being <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/two-arrested-alleged-conspiracy-launder-45-billion-stolen-cryptocurrency" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">charged</a> with conspiracy to launder 119,754 BTC stolen off the Bitfinex exchange, which equates to $4.5 billion at today’s prices. The remainder of the funds, about 25,000 BTC, was moved through <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> and mixing services not specified by name.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">One overlooked detail in the Razzlekahn arrest.  Almost all the money went through AlphaBay, using it as a mixer.  The feds were able to see through this because they seized AlphaBay.  Its amazing how, even years after, darknet market seizures pay dividends to the feds.</p>&mdash; Nicholas Weaver (@ncweaver) <a href="https://twitter.com/ncweaver/status/1491118233973571585?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 8, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>A Justice Department search warrant issued last week led to authorities’ decryption of a cloud-stored file containing the private keys for Bitcoin addresses known to hold stolen funds. Blockchain analysis led to the connection with the husband-and-wife pair, with transactions linking accounts opened under their names to laundered funds. About $2.9 million ended up in bank accounts belonging to Lichtenstein and Morgan, according to prosecutors.</p>



<p>Deputy Attorney General Lisa Monaco described the couple’s laundering operations as creating a “labyrinth of cryptocurrency transactions,” including transaction automation, using darknet markets like AlphaBay to break up blockchain linkages. The pair also cashed out BTC to other coins on various crypto exchanges using a money laundering tactic known as “chain hopping.” They attempted to launder additional funds by converting them into the anonymized crypto Monero (XMR).</p>



<p>As AlphaBay was seized by the US Justice Department in July 2017, security researchers suspect the two were <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">identified thro</a><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ugh internal t</a><a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/how-the-feds-tracked-down-3-6-billion-in-stolen-bitcoin-11644447110" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ransaction logs</a> kept by the market and obtained by investigators during the seizure. This associating information rendered any obfuscation attempts made by Lichtenstein and Morgan useless, thereby allowing authorities to locate all stolen Bitfinex funds the duo attempted to launder through the market.</p>



<p>Defense attorneys for Lichtenstein and Morgan <a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">cla</a><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">i</a><a href="https://www.reuters.com/technology/us-arrests-couple-allegedly-laundering-45-bln-crypto-tied-bitfinex-hack-2022-02-08/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">m</a> their clients knew they were under investigation as early as November 2021 but nevertheless remained in the country, as rationale as to why they were not flight risks for their upcoming trial. They face up to 20 years behind bars if convicted.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/">Bitfinex Seizure has AlphaBay Ties</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/bitfinex-seizure-has-alphabay-ties/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</title>
		<link>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/</link>
					<comments>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 57-year-old Kentucky woman will spend 15 months in prison for helping her son to launder proceeds from</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/">Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 57-year-old Kentucky woman will spend 15 months in prison for helping her son to launder proceeds from a <a href="/directory/listing/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> vending operation. Cara Leann Naber <a href="https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2022/02/04/oldham-county-woman-sentenced-prison-laundering-sons-drug-money/6663021001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">was sentenced</a> in front of a US District Judge on Wednesday for charges pertaining to conspiracy to launder drug trafficking proceeds and structuring bank transactions to evade federal cash transaction reporting requirements.</p>



<p>Her son, 22-year-old John Frank Naber, was <a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arres</a><a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">t</a><a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ed</a> on drug trafficking charges in Feb 2019 and sentenced to 11 years in prison. Cara Naber’s <a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plea a</a><a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">gre</a><a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ement</a> offered the following explanation of how she had helped her son obfuscate funds from drug purchases:</p>



<p>“<em>By depositing cash proceeds in both safety deposit boxes and in traditional bank accounts not in John Frank Naber III’s name, transferring money between various bank accounts to layer funds, and using drug proceeds to purchase Bitcoin, and by other means, defendants John Frank Naber II and Cara Leann Naber acted in concert to conceal or disguise the nature, the location, the source, the ownership, or the control of the proceeds of unlawful activity.”</em></p>



<p>The criminal complaint filed by prosecutors claims Cara Naber moved over $150,000 in drug sales proceeds between banks in 2018, attempting to create transactional layers to partially legitimize some of the funds. The attempt to launder the funds was quickly discovered after the arrest of her son.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="400" height="225" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1315" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.jpg 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1-300x169.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /><figcaption><em>John Naber III mugshot. Source: wdrb.com</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>John Naber allegedly sold cocaine, meth, and marijuana-derived products not only over <a href="/directory/listing/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet markets</a> but via hand-delivered orders, as well. Prosecutors claim Naber’s best-selling product was “fake Adderall pills” which he would manufacturer from the home of his parents, with a pill press and an inert, orange powder.</p>



<p>The principal ingredient in the fake Adderall pills was methamphetamine, according to investigators, who found approximately 1,000 grams of the substance during the Feb 2019 raid on family property in Oldham County, Kentucky. Investigators also recovered a large quantity of cash, the seed phrase to a cryptocurrency wallet, premeasured and bagged amounts of MDMA, and a digital scale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/">Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</title>
		<link>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/</link>
					<comments>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 11:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent court appearance by Kamil Balicki, a 32-year-old man living in Northern Ireland, shed some light on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/">Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A recent court <a href="https://www.northernirelandworld.com/news/people/dark-web-online-drugs-shop-linked-to-ballymena-address-court-told-3550893" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">appearance</a> by Kamil Balicki, a 32-year-old man living in Northern Ireland, shed some light on the takedown of one of the biggest independent darknet market operators in the UK. The native of Poland <a href="https://courtnewsni.co.uk/man-32-appears-at-court-in-ballymena-accused-of-attempting-to-import-heroin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">attended</a> a remote hearing on Jan. 18<sup>th</sup> and was aided by a Polish interpreter. He is charged with attempting to import heroin and the possession of cocaine, amphetamine, and cannabis with the intent to supply, using a self-created shop on the dark web to do so.</p>



<p>Prosecutors allege Balicki began his career as a darknet market vendor in May 2020, operating his independent market from his Ballymena address up until January 17<sup>th</sup> of this year, when he was arrested.</p>



<p>Police were tipped off about Balicki’s operations in October 2020 after Border Force officers stopped two heat-sealed envelopes containing 123 grams of heroin from reaching his home address. The heroin was being imported from the Netherlands for local resale via his site on the dark web, according to “cyber-investigators” working the case.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A &#39;DARK web&#39; online &#39;shopping site&#39; advertising heroin, cocaine and cannabis was allegedly linked to a property in Ballymena, a court in the town was told. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CourtCorner?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CourtCorner</a></p>&mdash; CourtNewsNI (@CourtNewsNI) <a href="https://twitter.com/CourtNewsNI/status/1488542144721731584?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 1, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Police described Balicki’s enterprise as an “online shopping site on the dark web which was openly advertising heroin, cocaine, as well as cannabis”. The site purported to have accumulated 270 “positive feedbacks” from supposed customers, suggesting it was fairly popular in the area.</p>



<p>Confiscated during his arrest were 40-50 grams of heroin, 30-40 grams of cocaine, and 30 grams of marijuana. Police also confiscated mixing bowls, an assortment of unidentified powders, electronic devices, and a large quantity of cash.</p>



<p>Balicki, a factory worker with no prior criminal record, was denied bail and will be remanded in custody in Maghaberry Prison until the case resumes on Feb. 10<sup>th</sup>.</p>



<p>Ballymena, in County Antrim, has appeared as the center of darknet market-related news in the past. In April 2017, a 14-year-old boy was <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arr</a><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sted</a> in the town for attempting to buy a sub-machine gun and several thousand rounds of ammunition off the internet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/">Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</title>
		<link>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/</link>
					<comments>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monopoly market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The administrator of darknet market link repository dark.fail tweeted an uncharacteristically certain warning about the fate of Monopoly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/">Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The administrator of darknet market link repository dark.fail <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">twe</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ete</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">d</a> an uncharacteristically certain warning about the fate of <a href="/directory/listing/monopoly-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Monopoly Market</a> yesterday, claiming that its servers had been seized by law enforcement and thus explaining why it had unexpectedly gone offline toward the end of Dec. 2021. Monopoly Market</p>



<p>“ALERT: Monopoly Market&#8217;s servers were seized,” reads a recently-placed message at the top of <a href="https://dark.fail/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">dark.fail</a>. “If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands,” the usually tight-lipped admin warned.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ALERT: Monopoly Market&#39;s servers were seized by their host, very likely law enforcement action. This was one of the largest cryptomarkets on the darknet.<br><br>If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 29, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Although the news quickly made its way to the <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/20305bd93499c392a0df" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>Dread</em></a> darknet forum, not everybody in the community was convinced dark.fail’s claims were accurate.</p>



<p>“Until there is proof this is just random fake news,” commented one <em>Dread</em> user on the subject. “Dark fail admin has 0 inside knowledge on the darknet markets scene, he just provides links to some darknet sites. Since he did not provide any source or proof this need to be classified as fake news until there is proof that it happened,” they added.</p>



<p>Other commentors from <em>Dread</em>, including moderator <em>crackheaddom101</em>, preferred to adopt an “assume the worst” mentality, warning former market users to prepare for potential fallout if dark.fail’s claims proved to be true:</p>



<p>“<em>ALERT: Monopoly Market&#8217;s servers were seized by their host, very likely law enforcement action. This was one of the largest cryptomarkets on the darknet. If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands…<br><br>Seems like they had their servers seized and most likely either will be given to LE or was requested by LE. Hopefully everyone used PGP and kept OPSEC very well <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></em></p>



<p><em>This is the only post i can find about this, Could be false or FUD or Exit scam strategy. Just stay careful.”</em></p>



<p>The Monopoly Market admin reported on <em>Dread</em> the site started experiencing problems around Dec. 28<sup>th</sup> of last year, sticking around to answer questions and berate accusers for a few days before disappearing completely in early January, along with the market. Former users remained in full speculation mode until yesterday’s tweet by dark.fail.</p>



<p>Focusing on the use of Monero and a wallet-less ordering system, Monopoly Market was a drugs-only market and considered to be one of the “safer” darknet markets to ever exist. It had been in operation since July 2019.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/">Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:55:30 by W3 Total Cache
-->