<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>desnake &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/desnake/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 11:42:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>desnake &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</title>
		<link>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seven months after the return of DeSnake, one of the original AlphaBay’s two administrators, the new incarnation of</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seven months after the <a href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">return of DeSnake</a>, one of the original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s two administrators, the new incarnation of the infamous darknet market is once again on top of the competition &#8212; sans Hydra, the Russian-language darknet market which still dwarfs all others in sales volume. The distinction comes about as its closest competitor in size, World Market, has been largely <a href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">deemed no longer operational</a>, even if the site remains technically accessible.</p>



<p>The rise of the “new” <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> is not something that much of the darknet market community was expecting as many feared it was simply an extravagant “honeypot” operation designed to collect the credentials of buyers and vendors. For its first few months, the market remained relatively void of users and activity. However, with over half a year of steady operation under its belt and an ever-increasing base of users, these fears have largely subsided, and AlphaBay currently enjoys its greatest degree of popularity yet in this new manifestation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">In 2017 the largest darknet market was seized, Alphabay &#8211; leading to the tragic suicide of its alleged admin Alex Cazes.<br><br>Recently its co-admin/fugitive DeSnake returned, relaunching the site in Alex&#39;s honor. With World&#39;s demise, Alphabay is close to reclaiming its throne as #1.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1506643215847411712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>AlphaBay now hosts over 22,000 listings and is home 5,228 vendors and 340,000+ buyers, according to statistics maintained by the market. It is now a Monero (XMR)-only market and forces its users to operate under some of the strictest guidelines to ever be implemented by a darknet market. These include a no-weapons and no-fentanyl policy, short-timed finalization periods, and an advanced captcha system that has proved capable of preventing DDOS attacks from occurring.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="934" height="406" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1409" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png 934w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-300x130.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-768x334.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 934px) 100vw, 934px" /><figcaption>lphabay</figcaption></figure>



<p><em>After a slow re-start, activity at AlphaBay is now bustling.</em></p>



<p>The recent string of darknet market closures in 2022 has also helped AlphaBay’s propulsion to the top of the list. World Market, previously the largest (English-speaking) market by sales volume, has all but closed shop, as admins on Dread have repeatedly warned users against making new deposits to avoid losses in the likely event of an exit scam.</p>



<p>Within the past week, World Market added the following message to its main market page, although accounts registered within the last six months (sans brand new accounts) are still unable to log in to the market:</p>



<p>“<em>World Market is operational again, listing images will be restored soon, if you are missing a deposit open a ticket.”</em></p>



<p>AlphaBay also seems to be making some strides in its promises to delivery a decentralized darknet market – the first of its kind – that can theoretically continue to operate even if service provided by an operator is discontinued, for whatever reason. Upcoming tasks have been scheduled in the market’s <a href="http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/roadmap" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">roadmap</a> for the project, and include building payment modules, multisig and escrow core functions, and a way for network operators to provide “initial decentralized infrastructure report.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</title>
		<link>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/</link>
					<comments>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, AlphaBay, is failing to impress the community, with</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/">AlphaBay</a>, is failing to impress the community, with many would-be users avoiding the site due to an assortment of concerns. Nearly seven weeks after AlphaBay’s supposed ‘re-opening,’ the market has managed to attract just a small number of vendors and even fewer customers. This is despite the relatively massive attention its re-opening has received in the media.</p>



<p>A recent article by <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-desnake-dark-web-interview/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Wired</em></a><em>, </em>which features an interview with <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> admin DeSnake, attempted to shed some light as to why the market hasn’t taken off. Among the reasons are persistent DDOS attacks and the decision to accept Monero (XMR)-only for order payments, but the main problem is a lack of trust by the community. Flashpoint security expert Ian Gray told <em>Wired</em> that he was personally distrustful of DeSnake and that “across communities there’s a general distrust.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="630" height="312" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-855" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png 630w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-300x149.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" /><figcaption><em>The legitimacy of the new AlphaBay is being heavily </em><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/pij727/is_the_new_alphabay_a_honeypot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>questioned</em></a><em> by Redditors on r/darknet.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s listings currently total slightly less than 800, with about 400 of them in the Drugs &amp; Chemicals section. As there were only 300 total listings just three weeks ago, this represents a 167% increase in the last 20 days. At the peak of its popularity in 2017, the market had approximately 350,000 listings.</p>



<p>Sales, on the other hand, remain scarce and limited to a handful of vendors. Most sections, though filled with listings and vendors awaiting customers, have zero product sales according to stats kept on each listing. There were single sales spotted for listings of shrooms, marijuana, cocaine, and alprazolam. One listing for Ecstasy had two sales.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="807" height="354" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-856" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png 807w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-300x132.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-768x337.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 807px) 100vw, 807px" /><figcaption><em>The scarcity of listings and near complete lack of sales on AlphaBay give it an almost ghost town feel.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The market’s welcome message and the first return <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/196fffff69ffe348636e" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">message</a> left by DeSnake insist this is not the “new AlphaBay” or “AlphaBay 2.0” but rather a continuation of the same market that shut down in 2017. Not many are sure that this is the case, however, despite DeSnake being verified as a former AlphaBay admin by senior members of the Dread forum.</p>



<p>“The entire point of us returning is about rebuilding the AlphaBay brand and creating something unique and new which will set the standard for a new way how things can be approached,” wrote DeSnake on Dread when asked why he chose not to rebrand the operation. “No other big market has come from the &#8216;dead&#8217; so whether it is a good decision business-wise &#8211; time will tell.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:15 by W3 Total Cache
-->