<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>xanax &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/xanax/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:40:43 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>xanax &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>‘Xanax’ Vendor Who Sold Pills Cut With Dangerous Designers Pleads Guilty</title>
		<link>/xanax-vendor-who-sold-pills-cut-with-dangerous-designers-pleads-guilty/</link>
					<comments>/xanax-vendor-who-sold-pills-cut-with-dangerous-designers-pleads-guilty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 11 Dec 2021 14:40:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[benzodiazepine]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[clonazolam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xanax]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1016</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 26-year-old man from Virginia Beach, Virginia pleaded guilty to charges related to selling fake Xanax pills on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/xanax-vendor-who-sold-pills-cut-with-dangerous-designers-pleads-guilty/">‘Xanax’ Vendor Who Sold Pills Cut With Dangerous Designers Pleads Guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 26-year-old man from Virginia Beach, Virginia <a href="https://www.wtkr.com/investigations/a-virginia-beach-man-plead-guilty-to-dealing-fake-xanax-pills-on-dark-web" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">pleaded guilty</a> to charges related to selling fake Xanax pills on the dark web on Friday. Federal investigators allege that Anthony Dimaiuat sold around 968 pills containing clonazolam and/or flubromazolam as a darknet market vendor. The substances are two high potency benzodiazepine analogs that mimic the effects of alprazolam, the active ingredient in Xanax, and do not have known medical use.</p>



<p>Dimaiuat was apprehended in late June after a 16-month investigation conducted by multiple federal agencies. Posing as buyers, investigators had been placing orders for pills labeled as Xanax with the unsuspecting vendor since February 2020.</p>



<p>Packages allegedly sent by Dimaiuat to undercover investigators were labeled with return addresses in the Hampton Roads area of Virginia Beach, allowing them to eventually reveal the vendor’s exact identity.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A Virginia Beach man pleaded guilty to dealing fake Xanax pills on the dark web. Law enforcement found 2,400 grams of white pills made of &quot;designer&quot; benzos in his house in February 2020.  <a href="https://t.co/NRVdZBMnx7">https://t.co/NRVdZBMnx7</a></p>&mdash; Partnership for Safe Medicines (@SafeMedicines) <a href="https://twitter.com/SafeMedicines/status/1469407199994998784?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>After a search warrant was executed at the home of Dimaiuat, law enforcement found 2,400 grams worth of “white pills”, as well as “two glass containers with white powder and packaging material.” It was determined that the pills contained the benzodiazepine analogs mentioned above and the “white powder” was a highly-impure cocaine &#8212; though it was not clear if that was deemed for sale or personal use.</p>



<p>After a brief incarceration, a Virginia judge granted Dimaiuat’s release while awaiting trial, on the condition that he participated in an evaluation “to assess the presence, nature, (and) severity of substance abuse problem.”</p>



<p>In court, Dimaiuat told investigators that he started buying a different formulation of “fake Xanax” off the dark web a year prior to setting out on his own as a vendor. He admitted to regularly purchasing between 250 and 500 pills at a time, consuming some while reselling the rest.</p>



<p>Though not illegal, <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Clonazolam" rel="nofollow">clonazolam</a> is active in tiny amounts, capable of causing severe social, psychological, and mental impairment in microscopic doses, with as little as 0.5 mg being enough to cause an overdose.</p>



<p>The specific law violated by <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> vendors like Dimaiuat who sell fake prescription drugs fall under the Introduction Into Interstate Commerce of Misbranded Drugs With the Intent to Defraud and Mislead federal statutes.</p>



<p>Dimaiuat is scheduled to be sentenced next Thursday.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/xanax-vendor-who-sold-pills-cut-with-dangerous-designers-pleads-guilty/">‘Xanax’ Vendor Who Sold Pills Cut With Dangerous Designers Pleads Guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/xanax-vendor-who-sold-pills-cut-with-dangerous-designers-pleads-guilty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Xanaxman Caught Trying to Move $137M in Bitcoin</title>
		<link>/xanaxman-caught-trying-to-move-137m-in-bitcoin/</link>
					<comments>/xanaxman-caught-trying-to-move-137m-in-bitcoin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 15 Aug 2021 12:23:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[xanax]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=776</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Although he was ordered to fork over his BTC stash, its price rise since entering prison in 2018</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/xanaxman-caught-trying-to-move-137m-in-bitcoin/">Xanaxman Caught Trying to Move $137M in Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Although he was ordered to fork over his BTC stash, its price rise since entering prison in 2018 made trying to keep it too irresistible an option for Ryan Farace.</em></p>



<p>A former darknet market vendor currently serving a 57-month prison sentence was <a href="https://www.baltimoresun.com/news/crime/bs-md-ci-cr-dark-web-farace-laundering-20210812-wgxyzg76vzfi3e3eblzanibgiq-story.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">indicted on new money laundering charges</a> late last week. Baltimore area man Ryan Farace, who went by the vendor name ‘Xanaxman’ between 2013 and 2017, is now accused of hiding $137 million in Bitcoin from darknet market proceeds from the U.S. Department of Justice.</p>



<p>Prosecutors allege that between Oct. 2019 and Apr. 2021, Farace, 37, conducted an elaborate scheme from prison to obfuscate the trail of funds collected as a vendor &#8212; all with the help of his father, who was also named in the indictment.</p>



<p>The indictment states that Farace employed his father to help him hide a large amount of Bitcoin – 2,933 to be exact – which was already seized by the DEA earlier this year. This equates to slightly over $137 million at today’s price of $47,000 per BTC.</p>



<p>The result of a joint effort between federal and state law enforcement, Farace was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-md/pr/maryland-men-plead-guilty-charges-relating-dark-web-drug-distribution-and-money" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">apprehended</a> by Maryland authorities in Jan. 2018 and pled guilty to charges related to his time as a vendor in Oct. 2018. The U.S. federal court <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-md/pr/maryland-man-sentenced-57-months-federal-prison-and-ordered-forfeit-least-5665-million-s">ruling</a> against Farace the next month sentenced him to 57 months in prison, ordering that he repay a money judgment of $5,665,000, along 4,000 BTC.</p>



<p>As part of a plea agreement, Farace admitted to purchasing Xanax pill molds which he used to press loose alprazolam powder into fake Xanax pills. He is believed to have <a href="https://www.safemedicines.org/2018/12/man-who-made-and-sold-nearly-one-million-counterfeit-xanax-pills-sentenced.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pressed nearly one million pills</a> during his time as a vendor, selling over 400,000 of them during his first year at the Hansa darknet market. In all, Farace cashed out a total of approximately $5 million worth of BTC over the course of nearly five years.</p>



<p>In July 2020, a motion filed by Farace for his compassionate release was <a href="https://www.govinfo.gov/content/pkg/USCOURTS-mdd-1_18-cr-00018/pdf/USCOURTS-mdd-1_18-cr-00018-0.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">denied</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/xanaxman-caught-trying-to-move-137m-in-bitcoin/">Xanaxman Caught Trying to Move $137M in Bitcoin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/xanaxman-caught-trying-to-move-137m-in-bitcoin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:47 by W3 Total Cache
-->