<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>tripwithscience &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/tripwithscience/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:23:44 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>tripwithscience &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Liquid Shrooms Vendor TripWithScience Lived Double Life in US Army</title>
		<link>/liquid-shrooms-vendor-tripwithscience-lived-double-life-in-us-army/</link>
					<comments>/liquid-shrooms-vendor-tripwithscience-lived-double-life-in-us-army/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 17:23:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Shrooms]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tripwithscience]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=946</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An in-depth report by Forbes reveals famed darknet psychedelics vendor James Verl Barlow, aka TripWithScience, was employed by</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liquid-shrooms-vendor-tripwithscience-lived-double-life-in-us-army/">Liquid Shrooms Vendor TripWithScience Lived Double Life in US Army</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An in-depth <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/thomasbrewster/2021/11/01/us-army-vet-became-a-dark-web-psychelic-dealer-bought-teslas-with-a-15-million-fortune-the-doj-says/?sh=4e8806c35c13" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by <em>Forbes</em> reveals famed darknet psychedelics vendor James Verl Barlow, aka <em>TripWithScience</em>, was employed by the army during many of his years as a vendor. The report details how the 44-year-old vendor’s high-profile lifestyle – complete with “two Teslas, a Mercedes and a two jet skis” – was a mismatch from the day job supposedly providing from it all.</p>



<p>Barlow served in the army from 1994 to 2019, both in the National Guard and as an active-duty soldier. His foray into darknet market activities began as early as November 2013, shortly after the shutdown of Silk Road. For years, he lived a lavish lifestyle, purchasing fancy clothing, cars and real estate – all the while still actively employed by the U.S. military. He even ran a few esoteric businesses on the side, one of which specialized in t-shirts with LED lights sewn into the fabric.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full is-resized"><img src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-948" width="513" height="351" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3.jpg 512w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3-300x205.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 513px) 100vw, 513px" /><figcaption><em>A picture of Jim Barlow, center, taken from his personal Facebook page.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>Barlow was not shy about his flamboyant habits and was known for spending large amounts of money all around Las Vegas, the city of his residence. Despite his attempts to pursue legitimate business on the side, the Department of Justice noted that Barlow “was not generating enough, if any, income from these businesses to support his lifestyle, which included travel on private jets, world travel, purchases of high-end automobiles, and ownership of multiple properties.”</p>



<p>With sales on nearly all major darknet markets through April 2021, Barlow is considered to be one of the most successful and longest-running vendors of psychedelics. His primary product was a well-branded psychedelic named “Liquid Mushrooms,” which he sold in small vials for around $20 per order, plus shipping. The primary psychoactive component of the popular product was determined to be <a href="https://www.drugsdata.org/view.php?id=6172" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">4-Ac0-DMT</a>, a mild-to-strong hallucinogen extracted from psychedelic mushrooms.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="899" height="440" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-949" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2-300x147.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/2-768x376.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /><figcaption><em>A TripWithScience product listing on AlphaBay, from 2015.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>Barlow was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdoh/pr/six-defendants-charged-selling-millions-dollars-worth-psychedelic-mushrooms-online" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">charged</a> in May with charges related to “conspiring to manufacture, distribute and dispense controlled substances using cryptocurrencies via the dark web.” He has been <a href="https://www.pacermonitor.com/public/case/40352818/USA_v_Barlow" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">detained</a> since his arrest as he awaits trial. He and his younger brother, Matthew Barlow, accused of assisting in the preparation of the dark web products, have yet to enter a plea.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/liquid-shrooms-vendor-tripwithscience-lived-double-life-in-us-army/">Liquid Shrooms Vendor TripWithScience Lived Double Life in US Army</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/liquid-shrooms-vendor-tripwithscience-lived-double-life-in-us-army/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Prominent ‘Liquid Mushroom’ Vendor Faces Charges by Homeland Security</title>
		<link>/prominent-liquid-mushroom-vendor-faces-charges-by-homeland-security/</link>
					<comments>/prominent-liquid-mushroom-vendor-faces-charges-by-homeland-security/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 09:15:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tripwithscience]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=184</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mistakes made early in career finally catch up to the well-known vendor. One of the U.S.’s longest-running darknet</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/prominent-liquid-mushroom-vendor-faces-charges-by-homeland-security/">Prominent ‘Liquid Mushroom’ Vendor Faces Charges by Homeland Security</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Mistakes made early in career finally catch up to the well-known vendor.</em></p>



<p>One of the U.S.’s longest-running darknet vendors is being <a href="https://anonfiles.com/9499e8w4uc">charged</a> with conspiring to distribute a controlled substance, along with five co-conspirators. The charges are against James Barlow, known as <em>TripWithScience</em> on at least a dozen darknet markets, and are the result of a Homeland Security investigation which spans two and a half years.</p>



<p>Investigators allege that Barlow had been a darknet market vendor since 2011, completing over 15,000 transactions; the vast majority of which are sales of his defining product, “Liquid Mushrooms.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="899" height="440" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/trip.png" alt="" class="wp-image-186" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/trip.png 899w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/05/trip-300x147.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/05/trip-768x376.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 899px) 100vw, 899px" /></figure>



<p>(caption: <em>TripWithScience</em> product listing from 2015)</p>



<p>According to the court document, authorities began monitoring <em>TripWithScience</em>’s darknet market activities in 2019. As part of their investigation, they placed several orders for Liquid Mushrooms and in October 2020 managed to track down one of Barlow’s re-shippers, who was being paid $4,000 &#8211; $6,000 every two weeks to help meet order demand.</p>



<p>Investigators were also provided with a list of BTC addresses for withdrawals from <em>TripWithScience</em>’s vendor account, from a <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> seized by law enforcement. Among these addresses was a Coinbase address which belonged to Barlow. In all, investigators found five instances between 2013 and 2014 in which Barlow sent Bitcoin directly to Coinbase from his vendor account – a mistake they note is common among darknet vendors in the early stages of their career.</p>



<p>The document alleges that Barlow was most recently active on the Monopoly, Televend and Cannahome darknet markets, though most sales were conducted on Dream, Empire and Silk Road 2.0.</p>



<p>In 2018, a lab analysis determined that the “liquid psilocybin” sold by <em>TripWithScience</em> was <a href="https://www.drugsdata.org/view.php?id=6172">actually 4-AcO-DMT</a>, a synthetic, lab-made product that produces effects similar to that of psilocybin. As with psilocybin, this chemical is a DEA Schedule I controlled substance, carrying similar penalties for distribution and possession.</p>



<p>Barlow has a <a href="https://www.dailydot.com/debug/dark-net-doctors-without-borders-donation/">history of donating to charitable causes</a>. In May 2015, he donated $6,000 to <em>Change Nepal</em>, an earthquake relief group. Months later, he donated $1,000 to the medical aid group <em>Medicins Sans Frontieres</em>, after the accidental bombing of a hospital in Afghanistan. In a 2015 Reddit <a href="http://web.archive.org/web/20150525032207/https:/pay.reddit.com/r/DarkNetMarkets/comments/348rsf/psaarticle_im_donating_100_of_my_profits_this/cqt525h">post</a> in which he defends his decision to make the donation, Barlow laments the negative perceptions cast upon darknet market participants, arguing that they are actually “a net positive for society and the economy.”</p>



<p>“I truly believe that we are a collection of (relatively) law-abiding citizens safely exploring the limits of our consciousness, and the nature of these darknet markets eliminates or drastically reduces the crime that most people associate with drug culture,” wrote Barlow. “Just in case I fuck up my OPSEC and end up in jail, this might help my case.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/prominent-liquid-mushroom-vendor-faces-charges-by-homeland-security/">Prominent ‘Liquid Mushroom’ Vendor Faces Charges by Homeland Security</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/prominent-liquid-mushroom-vendor-faces-charges-by-homeland-security/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:15:24 by W3 Total Cache
-->