<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Darknet Diaries &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/darknet-diaries/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 19:31:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Darknet Diaries &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</title>
		<link>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/</link>
					<comments>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Darknet Diaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An email from crypto exchange Kraken to UK customers was posted on Reddit yesterday, revealing the exchange’s plans</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/">Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An email from crypto exchange Kraken to UK customers was <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/qwww81/kraken_are_now_delisting_xmr_monero_from_their/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">posted</a> on Reddit yesterday, revealing the exchange’s plans to delist Monero (XMR) from coins accessible for trade in the region. Kraken claims they were forced to suspend listing of the privacy coin to remain “in compliance with UK regulations.” This also includes the gradual reduction and closure of all XMR margin positions.</p>



<p>Kraken is currently the second biggest exchange for Monero, processing about $5 &#8211; $6 million in trades daily. Binance remains the largest exchange for XMR, offering both BTC and USDT pairings, though non-KYC exchange services built into wallets like Exodus and Cake Wallet have been rising in popularity. In Nov. 2020, South Korea <a href="https://www.cpomagazine.com/data-privacy/south-koreas-new-crypto-aml-law-bans-trading-of-privacy-coins-monero-zcash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">banned</a> the trade of privacy coins like Monero altogether, following Japan’s <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/japans-fsa-bans-private-cryptocurrencie" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">move</a> to do so in June 2018.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This has to be a joke, right??? <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/monero?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#monero</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/xmr?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#xmr</a> <a href="https://t.co/zWUaUoEtww">pic.twitter.com/zWUaUoEtww</a></p>&mdash; Monero Memes (@MoneroMemes) <a href="https://twitter.com/MoneroMemes/status/1461440528655044615?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite an outcry of disappointment of Reddit and Twitter, the price of XMR was little affected by the news. After a 9% jump overnight, the coin stood at $251.20 on Saturday morning, which is roughly twice of what it was exactly one year ago. XMR hit an all-time high of $517.62 on May 7<sup>th</sup> this year.</p>



<p>Released later in the day was a <a href="https://www.monerotalk.live/jack-rhysider-of-darknet-diaries-talks-monero" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">podcast</a> by <em>Monero Talk</em> with featured guest Jack Rhysider, host of the ever-popular <em>Darknet Diaries</em> podcast. In the podcast, Rhysider discussed the importance of privacy and fungibility in cryptocurrency use and gave his advice for approaching it in the future.</p>



<p>“I do think there’s powers that be that don’t like crypto and want it to go away,” he said. “Regulating it, banning it, the whole KYC… Making sure things are regulated properly and stuff like that. I think we gotta play the rules or we’re gonna lose it all,” he added.</p>



<p>“It’s a balance in a lot of this space of trying to play by the rules of the governments of the world and also trying as hard as we can to keep it anonymous and private. Its tricky. I’m thinking some governments aren’t liking this, because whoever controls the money controls the power as well. It’s a shift of power at the same time, and I think that’s probably what they’re scared of the most, is how they are unable to control it.” – Jack Rhysider, host of <em>Darknet Diaries</em></p>



<p>Rhysider cited Monero’s relative difficulty of use and volatility as reasons why he thought the coin hadn’t reached wider mainstream adoption. He noted that times when user interfaces are difficult and still confusing reflect that society is still in the early stages when it comes to crypto use, and he sees great potential for it in the future.</p>



<p>“Being able to work in the crypto space without having to use a centralized exchange is starting to look really good as far as privacy goes,” he said as <em>Monero Talk</em> podcast guest. “I like to be able to work in this space without having to give my address and phone number and zip code and all that just to buy something online.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/">Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Darknet Diaries Podcast Records 100th Episode</title>
		<link>/darknet-diaries-podcast-records-100th-episode/</link>
					<comments>/darknet-diaries-podcast-records-100th-episode/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 07 Sep 2021 10:18:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Darknet Diaries]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=809</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A true crime podcast that delves into hacking, digital espionage and has brought more attention to the dark</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-podcast-records-100th-episode/">Darknet Diaries Podcast Records 100&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; Episode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A true crime podcast that delves into hacking, digital espionage and has brought more attention to the dark web in general, <a href="https://darknetdiaries.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Darknet Diaries</em></a> released its 100<sup>th</sup> episode last Tuesday, extending a run that started on Sept. 1, 2017. The most recent episode, entitled “NSO”, is an in-depth investigation into one of the world’s most infamous sellers of spyware to governments.</p>



<p>Episodes of Darknet Diaries are narrated by the pseudonymous Jack Rhysider, released every other week, and last between 30-60 minutes on average. Topics include little-explored avenues of cyber crime, such as carding, penetration testing, ransomware, and of course, the darknet. The podcast, which aims to present information at a level inclusive of both technical and non-technical audiences, has over 4,500 ratings on Apple Podcasts, with an average rating of 4.9.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ep 100: NSO &#8211; The NSO Group creates a spyware called Pegasus which gives someone access to the data on a mobile phone. They sell this spyware to government agencies around the world. How is it used and what kind of company is the N&#8230; <a href="https://t.co/CZwmjaFyX3">https://t.co/CZwmjaFyX3</a></p>&mdash; Jack Rhysider (@JackRhysider) <a href="https://twitter.com/JackRhysider/status/1433866172378791944?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 3, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>While <em>Darknet Diaries</em> itself is not strictly limited to the dark web in terms of story material, the subject of darknet markets is a semi-frequent topic of discussion. Episode 24, entitled “Operation Bayonet” and released in Oct. 2018, chronicles the downfall of Alexander Cazes, former admin of the famous <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> darknet market. The episode goes into detail on how Cazes was apprehended, providing a fresh narration of a somewhat older event.</p>



<p>Darknet Diaries can be found on several podcasting apps and media outlets, including Spotify, Apple Podcasts, Google Podcasts, Pocket Casts and Podcast Addict. According to stats kept by podcast, its episodes were downloaded over 15 million times in 2020. In March of that year, it was listed by <a href="https://www.forbes.com/sites/forbestechcouncil/2020/03/25/13-top-podcasts-for-tech-professionals/?sh=32cf46327597" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Forbes</em></a> as one of the top 13 podcasts for tech professionals.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Spent most of the trip home from Sault Ste Marie finally listening to <a href="https://twitter.com/DarknetDiaries?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@DarknetDiaries</a> and damn&#8230; <a href="https://twitter.com/JackRhysider?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@JackRhysider</a>, you&#39;ve done such an amazing job with this podcast. I&#39;ve learned something from every episode so far. Highly recommended if you haven&#39;t checked it out yet.</p>&mdash; Alex Taylor (@38percentsure) <a href="https://twitter.com/38percentsure/status/1434158738479493122?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 4, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>One of the podcast’s most popular episodes, which is bordering around half a million downloads, is titled “OxyMonster” and was released in Feb. 2020. The episode tells the story of a fentanyl vendor on the Dream marketplace who was finally caught by law enforcement due to a particularly bizarre lapse in OpSec.</p>



<p>In July 2018, the <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2019/07/18/arts/podcasts-tech-science.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>New York Times</em></a> described <em>Darknet Diaries</em> episodes as “startlingly short, condensing stories into 30 minutes that could easily justify a full hour,” but that “Rhysider’s hypnotic narration and deep expertise creates results that are never less than gripping.&#8221;</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-podcast-records-100th-episode/">Darknet Diaries Podcast Records 100&lt;sup&gt;th&lt;/sup&gt; Episode</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darknet-diaries-podcast-records-100th-episode/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:15:32 by W3 Total Cache
-->