<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>dread &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/dread/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>dread &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</title>
		<link>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/</link>
					<comments>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators on the <em>Dread</em> darknet forum. On March 26<sup>th</sup>, forum moderator <em>Shakybeats</em> <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ann</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">oun</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ced</a> they had removed moderation privileges for the World Market administrator on <em>Dread</em>, disabling their ability to continue posting and confirming that an impending exit scam was likely.</p>



<p>Warning signs that something at World Market was amiss had been present for weeks, going back to a cautionary <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/d01b3750e9320def61f7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> by a self-described former colleague of the World Market admin, written late last month. In the post, user <em>nightmaremarket</em> accused the market of preparing for an exit scam &#8212; a plan which its admin immediately denied.</p>



<p>On March 23<sup>rd</sup>, <em>Dread</em> user <em>dontlaugh</em> started a new <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">th</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ead</a> urging World Market users to take heed of “a number of red flags,” which most notably included a rollback to a previous version of the website. Other warning signs included a sudden jump in the cost of vendor bond – from $1,500 to $3,000 – and reports from several vendors that their payments were trapped in the market, with withdrawal requests being ignored.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="671" height="98" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1393" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-300x44.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /><figcaption><em>One of many posts responding to World Market user complaints on Dread.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In an effort to respond to mounting complaints, World Market admin and <em>Dread</em> user <em>makarov</em> wrote the following <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ab00d26a769f65030710" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">counter-post</a>, which was heavily downvoted, with its rationale being dismissed by most respondents:</p>



<p>“The time has come that the World Market team must close shop. The team tried to fix numerous technical issues over the past week but could not recover what has been lost. We have worked hard to be the best market and to serve the community.</p>



<p>As much as I care for everyone at World Market, I also care about the vendors and buyers, and it would not be fair to continue at this point.” – <em>Dread user makarov</em></p>



<p>Less than two days later, the post by <em>dontlaugh</em> was edited to include the following text: “UPDATE: I think we can call it. Either one of the admins fucked the other (who would have thunk it) or they both pulled this to squeeze out as much as possible from everyone,” thus signaling the end of the market’s functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="477" height="407" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1394" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png 477w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1-300x256.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 477px) 100vw, 477px" /><figcaption><em>World Market welcome message that is currently still being displayed.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>After the closures of White House Market and Dark0de, World Market was for a short while one of the biggest darknet markets in operation, hosting well over 30,000 listings at its peak. The market used the traditional account deposit system, making an exit scam especially lucrative for a market its size.</p>



<p>As of March 27<sup>th</sup>, the rolled-back version of World Market was still accessible and allowing those who had created older accounts to still login and even make deposits. However, many functions have been removed, making purchases or withdrawals impossible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</title>
		<link>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/</link>
					<comments>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 21:44:21 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Wall Street Market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1378</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 25-year-old US man was ordered to pay $2.3 million in Bitcoin proceeds late last week and sentenced</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/">Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 25-year-old US man was <a href="https://cryptoinsidermag.com/ecstasy-kingpin-from-brockton-forfeits-2-3m-in-bitcoin-to-massachusetts-law-enforcement/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ordered to pay $2.3 million</a> in Bitcoin proceeds late last week and sentenced to eight years in prison for his principal role in the EastSideHigh darknet market vendor operation. Binh Thanh Le, of Brockton, Massachusetts, opened for business under the vendor name on Wall Street Market in 2018, when he was only 22 years old.</p>



<p>Le, <a href="https://www.bostonherald.com/2022/03/12/darknet-ecstasy-kingpin-from-brockton-to-serve-8-years-in-prison-forfeit-2-3-million-in-bitcoin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">described</a> by local media as a darknet “kingpin,” managed to raise 59 BTC during his brief career on Wall Street Market with the help of two associates, selling Ecstasy, Xanax, and ketamine in bulk quantities. He was indicted in June 2019 for conspiracy to manufacture and distribute narcotics.</p>



<p>Federal agents managed to track Le down through a series of fictitious business names he used for drug transportation purposes, with the help of local postal inspectors. Agents also intercepted packages being delivered to the fake business addresses from international importers, arriving from Canada, Belgium, and the Netherlands.</p>



<p>The intercepted packages shared a common trait of being labeled as “Lego box(es) for kids.” While the packages did contain actual boxes for Lego toys, the toys had been removed and replaced with vacuum-sealed bags containing drugs to be repackaged and sold on Wall Street Market.</p>



<p>EastSideHigh’s disappearance from Wall Street Market and the Dread forum – two places where the vendor maintained consistent communication with their customers – coincided with <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ma/pr/three-brockton-men-indicted-selling-drugs-dark-web" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Le’s arrest</a>, which occurred on Mar 27<sup>th</sup>, 2019. On that day, Le unwittingly met with undercover officers in a Massachusetts hotel to perform a Bitcoin-for-cash exchange of $150,000.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="579" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-1024x579.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1380" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-1024x579.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-300x170.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111-768x434.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/111.jpg 1500w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p><em>Binh Thanh Le, next to two co-conspirators, headed to a hearing after their 2019 arrest. Source: The Patriot Ledger</em></p>



<p>“I imagine this kind of situation is so tempting for vendors,” wrote Dread user <em>TurboSnail</em> in reference to the BTC-for-cash setup, in a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/68dd001b20631f25d9f3/#c-5df9a56332b87a52e0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> dated almost two years ago, shortly after news broke of Le’s arrest. “Many have the contacts and knowledge to sell product, but then fall short when it comes to turning all that crypto into real world cash,” they added. “Then along comes MrFriendlyMoneyLaunderer who offers irl cash in exchange for a quiet chat at a local hotel lol.”</p>



<p>A co-conspirator believed to be part of the vendor operation was also arrested at the hotel where Le met with the undercover officers. In addition, an alleged third member was arrested at a storage facility associated with the operation, where law enforcement confiscated 6,200 grams of MDMA, 5,000 grams of ketamine, and more than 10,000 generic Xanax pills. The two co-conspirators have pleaded not guilty to related charges.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/">Wall Street Market “Kingpin” Sentenced to 8 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/wall-street-market-kingpin-sentenced-to-8-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DarkFox ‘Targeted By Scammers’ Says Admin</title>
		<link>/darkfox-targeted-by-scammers-says-admin/</link>
					<comments>/darkfox-targeted-by-scammers-says-admin/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 30 Dec 2021 13:19:55 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darkfox market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1048</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>DarkFox, a controversial and problem-laden darknet market that opened early last year, has been given a stern warning</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkfox-targeted-by-scammers-says-admin/">DarkFox ‘Targeted By Scammers’ Says Admin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/directory/listing/darkfox-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">DarkFox</a>, a controversial and problem-laden darknet market that opened early last year, has been given a stern warning by the community to shape up and sort its customer problems, or risk permanent exile. For many of the market’s users &#8211; scammed by way of non-delivered order &#8211; it is already too late.</p>



<p>Paris, admin of the <em>Dread</em> darknet forum, posted a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/171a786b76ee750254d3" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">lengthy warning</a> in the DarkFox market ‘subdread’ on Monday which suggested that the market had been compromised by scammers who had been flooding the ticket system for months with spam. This created an insurmountable backlog of tickets for the market’s thin staff to process, resulting in nearly all legitimate disputes going unanswered.</p>



<p>The result has been an ongoing wave of complaints lodged against the market, on Dread and elsewhere, about orders never received and disputes never processed, leading Paris to limit the market’s subdread functionality. This means all future posts in the subdread must be manually approved. Additionally, the market’s URL was removed from the forum, highlighting Dread’s utter loss of confidence in the operation.</p>



<p>In addition to the dispute backlog that has left scores of customers feeling ripped off, Paris’ complaints against DarkFox included a lack of recent communication from the admin and the fact that inactive vendors were still displayed as active on the market (along with their listings). Paris also noted the apparent ease with which scammers can impersonate legitimate vendors not on the market, acting as impostors and seemingly free to prey on new buyers with impunity.</p>



<p>“Let this be a growing fire under your ass,” wrote Paris to the DarkFox admin in a public post on <em>Dread</em>, in reference to his punishment issued to the market and calls to do a better job. “You can get the faith in you back if you do some actions and communicate what is happening. The silent treatment is only getting people more and more pissed at you.”</p>



<p>DarkFox has been the subject of criticism by the darknet market community for much of its existence, recently found to contain only fraudulent offerings for certain categories of services.</p>



<p>“Darkfox has proven to be an absolute garbage site,” begins one recent <a href="https://darknetone.com/market/darkfox-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">review</a> of the market on the clearnet. “I had a purchase that never arrived. Opened a ticket, no response. Opened another one, nothing. There is nobody there and the scammers know it.”</p>



<p>A look through other recent reviews shows the market has been subject to ticket system complaints for months &#8212; at least as early as March of this year.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkfox-targeted-by-scammers-says-admin/">DarkFox ‘Targeted By Scammers’ Says Admin</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darkfox-targeted-by-scammers-says-admin/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:22 by W3 Total Cache
-->