<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>monopoly market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/monopoly-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:31:12 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>monopoly market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</title>
		<link>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/</link>
					<comments>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 30 Jan 2022 10:31:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monopoly market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1301</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The administrator of darknet market link repository dark.fail tweeted an uncharacteristically certain warning about the fate of Monopoly</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/">Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The administrator of darknet market link repository dark.fail <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">twe</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ete</a><a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">d</a> an uncharacteristically certain warning about the fate of <a href="/directory/listing/monopoly-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Monopoly Market</a> yesterday, claiming that its servers had been seized by law enforcement and thus explaining why it had unexpectedly gone offline toward the end of Dec. 2021. Monopoly Market</p>



<p>“ALERT: Monopoly Market&#8217;s servers were seized,” reads a recently-placed message at the top of <a href="https://dark.fail/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">dark.fail</a>. “If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands,” the usually tight-lipped admin warned.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">ALERT: Monopoly Market&#39;s servers were seized by their host, very likely law enforcement action. This was one of the largest cryptomarkets on the darknet.<br><br>If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1487227934347866112?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 29, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Although the news quickly made its way to the <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/20305bd93499c392a0df" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>Dread</em></a> darknet forum, not everybody in the community was convinced dark.fail’s claims were accurate.</p>



<p>“Until there is proof this is just random fake news,” commented one <em>Dread</em> user on the subject. “Dark fail admin has 0 inside knowledge on the darknet markets scene, he just provides links to some darknet sites. Since he did not provide any source or proof this need to be classified as fake news until there is proof that it happened,” they added.</p>



<p>Other commentors from <em>Dread</em>, including moderator <em>crackheaddom101</em>, preferred to adopt an “assume the worst” mentality, warning former market users to prepare for potential fallout if dark.fail’s claims proved to be true:</p>



<p>“<em>ALERT: Monopoly Market&#8217;s servers were seized by their host, very likely law enforcement action. This was one of the largest cryptomarkets on the darknet. If you conducted blockchain/cyber research on this platform be aware that your transaction history may be in unknown hands…<br><br>Seems like they had their servers seized and most likely either will be given to LE or was requested by LE. Hopefully everyone used PGP and kept OPSEC very well <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f642.png" alt="🙂" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /></em></p>



<p><em>This is the only post i can find about this, Could be false or FUD or Exit scam strategy. Just stay careful.”</em></p>



<p>The Monopoly Market admin reported on <em>Dread</em> the site started experiencing problems around Dec. 28<sup>th</sup> of last year, sticking around to answer questions and berate accusers for a few days before disappearing completely in early January, along with the market. Former users remained in full speculation mode until yesterday’s tweet by dark.fail.</p>



<p>Focusing on the use of Monero and a wallet-less ordering system, Monopoly Market was a drugs-only market and considered to be one of the “safer” darknet markets to ever exist. It had been in operation since July 2019.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/">Dark.Fail Admin Claims Monopoly Market Servers Seized</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dark-fail-admin-claims-monopoly-market-servers-seized/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</title>
		<link>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/</link>
					<comments>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cartel market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monopoly market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The streak of graceful exits by some of the world’s most popular darknet markets has come to a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/">Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The streak of graceful exits by some of the world’s most popular darknet markets has come to a close. Hope has faded that either Monopoly Market or Cartel Marketplace, which <a href="https://www.securitynewspaper.com/2022/01/17/dark-web-sales-platforms-monopoly-market-and-cartel-market-shut-down-mysteriously/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">went offline within a few days of each other</a> just before the new year, will return and resume business as usual. Theories abounded in social media communities as to why the markets went down, with many assuming the possibilities of exit scam or seizure being the most likely.</p>



<p>Monopoly Market, the better-known and more celebrated of the two, was believed to be a top-notch operation in terms of its security and design. It was popular for its streamlined approach to the order purchasing process and introduction of novel features not employed elsewhere.</p>



<p>Orders placed on or before Dec 27 were processed, according to vendors on Monopoly Market; after that date, access to the market became stifled before disappearing completely. Scores of Monopoly users flocked to the market’s page on <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/d/Monopoly" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>Dread</em></a> to voice their concerns; many of which were met by scathing retorts from an extremely enraged admin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It seems I missed it over the New Year but Monopoly Market has been down for almost a week now. Admin claims it will be back, users are suggesting everything from exit scam to server seizure.</p>&mdash; Patrick Shortis (@Patrick_Shortis) <a href="https://twitter.com/Patrick_Shortis/status/1478033669994520577?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 3, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>After performing damage control that involved vague promises of a gradual return, <em>MonopolyOfficial</em>, the market’s admin account on <em>Dread</em>, fell silent, leading to new rounds of speculation and the forum’s <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/05281ad4c4ebb6a9adfc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">decision to close the thread</a>.</p>



<p>“Scam? busted? Overdosed? We may never know what happened to /u/MonopolyOfficial,” said <em>Dread</em> moderator Shakybeats about the missing admin. “We may never know what happened to him.”</p>



<p>Monopoly was one of the oldest darknet markets still in operation at the time of its shutdown, having been in operation since July 2019. It was hailed for being innovative as far as supporting direct payments and Monero was concerned. Cartel Marketplace was newer market, opening for business in the spring of 2020. Unlike Monopoly, it was plagued by technical and security problems over the course of its existence.</p>



<p>The two markets were vastly different in terms of the products they offered. Monopoly was a drugs-only darknet market that banned the sale of all digital goods; whereas Cartel was heavy on digital items and had earned a notorious reputation for selling stolen data. There is no known connection between the two markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/">Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:11:13 by W3 Total Cache
-->