<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>DNetSEO &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/author/bffsforever/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>DNetSEO &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over one ton of drugs was seized in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over one ton of drugs was <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/russian-police-say-caught-drug-gang-led-by-uk-1504121.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">seized</a> in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation into 26 individuals believed to have been operating a shop on the former Hydra darknet marketplace. The criminal group, led by Ukrainian nationals, organized the production of the drugs and their sale in Russia under the name “Murmur Shop,” which operated on Hydra between 2019 and 2021.</p>



<p>According to investigators, the group included 15 people from Ukraine, seven from Russia, two from Moldova, one from Tajikistan, and one from Belarus. While the leadership was based in Ukraine, Russian nationals were hired to help transport the drugs to <a href="https://aif.ru/society/law/v_mosgorsud_napravili_delo_mezhdunarodnoy_gruppy_iz_26_narkotorgovcev" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">more than 60 constituent entities</a> across the Russian Federation. Four clandestine drug laboratories in the Moscow, Vladimir and Ivanovo regions were also uncovered during the investigation.</p>



<p>“The leadership of the drug group and the management of its financial assets was carried out from the territory of Ukraine,” said Irina Volk, a spokeswoman for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs, on Thursday. “The recruitment of laboratory staff was also carried out there for the further dispatch to Russia. Applicants were forced to undergo polygraph tests,” she added.</p>



<p>In early April, Hydra’s servers were <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">s</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ei</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zed</a> in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement, knocking the world’s biggest darknet market offline in the process. Days earlier, the US Department of Justice had filed sanctions against Hydra and an online money exchanger known to be associated with the market. On April 11<sup>th</sup>, the Meshchansky Court of Moscow arrested Dmitry Pavlov, one of the alleged founders of the online drug platform.</p>



<p>In January, a group of Russian nationals were <a href="https://www.gazeta.ru/social/news/2022/01/20/17168629.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> for their roles in importing cocaine from Argentina, some of which had been hidden at the Russian embassy in Buenos Aires. The group’s mastermind was sentenced to 18 years in a penal colony while other members received sentences between 13 and 17 years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</title>
		<link>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/</link>
					<comments>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ross ulbricht]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silk road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recently unveiled court filing has revealed that Ross Ulbricht, the incarcerated 38-year-old founder of Silk Road, will</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/">Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A recently unveiled <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.368440/gov.uscourts.cand.368440.47.0_1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">court filing</a> has revealed that Ross Ulbricht, the incarcerated 38-year-old founder of <em>Silk Road</em>, will forfeit claims toward 69,370 Bitcoin seized by US federal investigators in exchange for the clearance of $183 million in restitution he owed as part of his 2015 sentencing.</p>



<p>The seized bitcoins, which formerly resided at <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/btc/address/1HQ3Go3ggs8pFnXuHVHRytPCq5fGG8Hbhx" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">1HQ3Go3ggs8pFnXuHVHRytPCq5fGG8Hbhx</a>, also include the unsplit Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV attached to the address private key and are currently valued at over $3 billion in total. As part of the agreement, Ulbricht and his family agreed to relinquish any possibility of ever obtaining the funds, regardless of whether he should ever be freed from prison.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">.<a href="https://twitter.com/RealRossU?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RealRossU</a> has forfeited 69,370 BTC, BCH, BTG, and BSV to the US Government. <a href="https://t.co/V4Hr7plliI">pic.twitter.com/V4Hr7plliI</a></p>&mdash; ₿itcoin Gandalf The Orange <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f7e7.png" alt="🟧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@BTCGandalf) <a href="https://twitter.com/BTCGandalf/status/1518642907259064327?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 25, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Blockchain sleuths noticed the coins – believed to have been hacked from Silk Road in 2013 – <a href="https://ciphertrace.com/nearly-1b-from-silk-road-move-for-first-time-since-2015/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">moved</a> for the first time in five years in November 2020, coinciding with a complaint filed with the US Department of Justice in which they state that the coins had been seized. The funds were reportedly <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ross-ulbricht-agrees-to-pay-u-s-govt/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">confiscated</a> from a “notorious hacker” who used Silk Road to launder their ill-gotten proceeds.</p>



<p>Launched in Feb. 2011, Silk Road was the world’s first darknet market, conceived and built by Ulbricht as a manifestation of his anti-regulatory and pro-libertarian ideals. Though it was shut down a little more than two and a half years later, his original creation inspired countless other markets to form, initiating a darknet- and cryptocurrency-based movement that continues to grow in worldwide popularity each year.</p>



<p>Ulbricht, who went by the moniker <em>Dread Pirate Roberts</em> online, was handed a life sentence for his roles as Silk Road architect and admin. Though he remains in prison, several movements have sprung up advocating for his release, such as the <a href="https://www.freerossdao.org/">FreeRossDAO</a>. He was most recently denied a pardon by former US President Donald Trump.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/">Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</title>
		<link>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/</link>
					<comments>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 23 Apr 2022 11:48:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1444</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Closing out what is perhaps the last public saga of the now-defunct Besa Mafia ‘hitman’ site ring, a Tampa Bay woman was <a href="https://www.tampabay.com/news/tampa/2022/04/20/tampa-woman-gets-6-years-in-prison-for-dark-web-murder-for-hire/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced to six and a half years</a> in prison on Wednesday for using one such darknet site to order the murder of her ex-boyfriend’s wife.</p>



<p>A US District Judge ordered DeAnna Marie Stinson, 51, to serve the time and pay $12,000 in restitution for attempting to hire a hitman through one of the well-known fake hitman sites on the dark web &#8212; whose operators had <a href="https://gizmodo.com/besa-mafia-alleged-ringleaders-arrested-1848769128" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">recently been apprehended</a> by Romanian authorities.</p>



<p>Stinson admitted to attempting to hire what she believed was a professional assassin from a Besa Mafia site in exchange for <a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">payments</a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> </a><a href="https://www.wtsp.com/article/news/crime/deanna-marie-stinson-failed-hitman/67-4a775075-c1fb-49ba-b1b3-3c8bbc8af683" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">totaling $12,307 in Bitcoin</a>. She also provided a photo of the intended victim, along with their name and address. The “assassin” turned out to be a US federal investigator who was likely tipped off to Stinson’s intentions by one of the site’s admins.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Tampa Accountant Sentenced to More Than Six Years in Federal Prison for Plotting a Murder-for-Hire: DeAnna Marie Stinson of Tampa has been sentenced to six years and six months in federal prison for murder-for-hire. <a href="https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv">https://t.co/ht91TN5RAv</a></p>&mdash; FBI Tampa (@FBITampa) <a href="https://twitter.com/FBITampa/status/1517179243406381065?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 21, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“I cited the old adage, ‘hell hath no fury like a woman scorned,’” said Federal Defender Alec Hall to the judge during Stinson’s sentencing, adding, “I think that’s what happened in this case.”</p>



<p>Stinson pleaded guilty to the charges in January.</p>



<p>Sprawling across a number of similar-looking darknet sites, the Besa Mafia operation has been known to exist since at least 2015, and famously <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">suffered a</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> dat</a><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">a breach</a> in May 2016 in which they were firmly outed as a scam. On the site which Stinson traversed, “death by shooting” started at a rate of $5,000, while a “beating” was listed for $2,000. At the top of the supposed services list was “death by sniper,” which was priced at $20,000.</p>



<p>The Besa Mafia admins were captured earlier this month as the result of a US-based investigation.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/">Florida Woman Gets 6+ Years For Fake Hitman Hire</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/florida-woman-gets-6-years-for-fake-hitman-hire/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 15:14:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1442</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of Hydra, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been arrested</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 30-year-old man described as the “co-founder” of <a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, formerly the world’s biggest darknet marketplace, has been <a href="https://www.mskagency.ru/materials/3204351" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Russia per reports from the Meshchansky District Court in Moscow. The report names Dmitry Pavlov – a Russian citizen – as arrested on charges pertaining to “illegal drug trafficking on an especially large scale.” He faces up to 20 years in prison if convicted on the charges.</p>



<p>The arrest, which took place on April 11<sup>th</sup>, occurred less than a <a href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">week after Hydra’s servers</a> were knocked offline in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. German police also managed to confiscate about $25 million in Bitcoin during their takedown of the market.</p>



<p>The US Department of Justice <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/pr/justice-department-investigation-leads-shutdown-largest-online-darknet-marketplace" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> its own charges against Pavlov on April 5<sup>th</sup>, which include conspiracy to distribute narcotics and conspiracy to commit money laundering. He is also <a href="https://www.justice.gov/opa/press-release/file/1490906/download" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">named</a> as a Hydra admin and provider of hosting services for the now-defunct darknet market, which had been in steady operation since 2015.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Russia has arrested the alleged co-founder of dark web platform Hydra a week after American and German authorities said they shut down what they called the world’s largest illegal darknet marketplace.</p>&mdash; Fuad Alakbarov ⁠⁠ (@DrAlakbarov) <a href="https://twitter.com/DrAlakbarov/status/1514901753392680964?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 15, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Pavlov <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/alleged-hydra-administrator-dmitry-pavlov-reportedly-arrested-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stated</a> on April 6<sup>th</sup> that he had only been informed of the charges against him via the media, and that he had not been contacted by US authorities. He also said the server provision business he ran, in which he leased servers to other businesses, was fully-licensed and registered with Roskomanadzor, the Russian communications bureau. Pavlov also denied allegations of being a Hydra admin, claiming he did not have administration duties on any website.</p>



<p>“We are a hosting company and have all the necessary communications licenses,” Pavlov told BBC’s Russian service in an interview last week. “We don’t administer any sites but only provide servers for rent as intermediaries.”</p>



<p>Cybersecurity experts who had been investigating Hydra told <em>The Moscow Times </em>that <a href="https://www.themoscowtimes.com/2022/04/15/russia-arrests-alleged-co-founder-of-worlds-largest-darknet-marketplace-a77363" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Russia had been monitoring the market since its inception</a>, and speculated that it was possible for Hydra to make a re-appearance under a different domain, hosted on different servers.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/">Hydra Co-Founder Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hydra-co-founder-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</title>
		<link>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/</link>
					<comments>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 10 Apr 2022 14:07:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1419</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Members of an “organized criminal group” suspected to be operating several assassin-for-hire scam sites on the dark web were <a href="https://diicot.ro/mass-media/3498-comunicat-de-presa-3-06-04-2022" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in Romania on April 6th, after years of steady operation. The arrests were performed at the behest of US authorities who had been investigating the sites and managed to link them to a group of Romanian citizens.</p>



<p>Seven house raids were performed in relation to the takedown, in the counties of Gorj and Hunedoara; the result of warrants issued against five suspects and four “witnesses.” The amount of financial damage directly linked to the sites’ operation was estimated to be around 500,000 EUR, although the total tally they collected over the years is likely to be far greater.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Yura (presumably), the owner of Besa Mafia, history&#39;s most profitably dark web murder-for-hire website has been arrested. I spent years corresponding with him about his business.</p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1512316762095710210?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 8, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Perhaps the most notorious type of darknet market, murder-for-hire sites have been a part of the dark web since just a year or two after the closure of the original <em>Silk Road</em> marketplace. However, it has been known for quite some time that just about <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/mg77bn/this-fake-hitman-site-is-the-most-elaborate-twisted-dark-web-scam-yet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">all of them are fake</a> &#8212; scam sites designed to separate vengeful parties from decent-to-large sums of Bitcoin.</p>



<p>The most famous of these sites was run by a group calling themselves the <a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Besa M</em></a><em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">a</a></em><a href="https://www.riskbasedsecurity.com/2016/05/12/besa-mafia-dark-web-hitman-for-hire-site-takes-a-hit/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>fia</em></a>, of which the five arrested suspects are presumed to comprise. Other sites operated by the group are thought to include <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/v7d8j3/the-alleged-scammers-behind-the-most-notorious-murder-for-hire-site-have-been-arrested" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><u><em>Camorra Hitman</em> and <em>#1 Hitman Marketplace</em></u></a>, along with a list of less-famous names.</p>



<p>Besides being complete scams, all these sites shared the common feature of purporting to link “real hitmen” with a client looking for violence to be performed upon a particular victim &#8212; whether it be a beating, stabbing, torture, or even murder. Prices for these services usually ranged between $5,000 and $20,000, payable in Bitcoin, but never resulted in the actual delivery of service. Instead, clients were likely to become the subject of a police investigation, and dozens of arrests have been performed over the years for charges related to this type of attempted murder.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Flowchart of Besa Mafia&#39;s Business Model For Fake Hitman Dark Web Scam <a href="https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY">https://t.co/Mx6gV4S3IY</a> <a href="https://t.co/CKsjvS6TZI">pic.twitter.com/CKsjvS6TZI</a></p>&mdash; Arnout de Vries (@ADeVries23) <a href="https://twitter.com/ADeVries23/status/733185111064236032?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">May 19, 2016</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>While <a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">real m</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">urder</a><a href="https://www.rferl.org/a/russia-hitmen-for-hire-darknet/31454299.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">-for-hire sites</a> have been found to exist on the dark web, they are not advertised in the transparent fashion of the <em>Besa Mafia</em> sites (which were usually found via darknet link lists) and are nearly impossible to stumble upon.</p>



<p>The arrests were the result of a joint operation between the US Homeland Security Investigations and the US Embassy in Bucharest, performed by police officers from Romania’s Service for Combating Cybercrime.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/">Fake Assassin Markets Operators Arrested in Romania</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/fake-assassin-markets-operators-arrested-in-romania/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</title>
		<link>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/</link>
					<comments>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 06 Apr 2022 08:27:09 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1414</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Hydra, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/directory/listing/hydra-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Hydra</a>, the world’s largest and longest-running darknet market has finally ceased operations, taken offline in a joint effort between German and US law enforcement. On Tuesday, April 5<sup>th</sup>, Federal police in Germany shut down servers hosting the market’s main URL on the dark web that were located within the country, seizing approximately $25 million in bitcoin in the process.</p>



<p>In a statement, federal police said they were also investigating unnamed individuals believed to be &#8220;operating criminal trading platforms on the internet on a commercial basis.”</p>



<p>Hydra was thought to have a userbase consisting of over 19,000 vendors, 2.5 million regular users, and 17 million registered clients overall. Blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis estimate that <a href="/hydra-activity-250-greater-than-all-other-darknet-markets-combined/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">roughly $3.4 billion in BTC transactions had transpired</a> at the market over its lifetime, with much of the proceeds collected by admins being passed on to legitimate cryptocurrency exchanges.</p>



<p>Though Hydra was long-believed to be operating out of Russia, yesterday’s reveal of its servers being hosted in Germany – along with other recently-uncovered factors – suggests this was never actually the case.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="960" height="535" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1415" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2.png 960w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-300x167.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-2-768x428.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 960px) 100vw, 960px" /><figcaption><em>Screenshot of the Hydra darknet marketplace taken during November 2021.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>In February, two Ukrainian-based individuals were named as “responsible for Hydra’s operations” based on an <a href="https://geminiadvisory.io/alleged-hydra-market-operators-identified-6/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">assessment</a> of recently-released information performed by the dark web intelligence-gathering company, Gemini Advisory. The information, initially posted by an anonymous individual behind the hydra.expert domain, was partially confirmed by Gemini and revealed that JavaScript found to be embedded in the marketplace contained the names of the two Hydra masterminds as file authors.</p>



<p>An <a href="https://archive.ph/cFQy6" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">archived version</a> of hydra.expert details the process by which the two Ukrainian nationals were identified, breaking down the JavaScript code supposedly uncovered from the market and detailing an investigation into the subdomains associated with a domain mentioned in it.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The United States is sanctioning the world’s largest darknet market for Russian speakers, Hydra, and the virtual currency exchange Garantex. Today’s action, coordinated with <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1ea.png" alt="🇩🇪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />, demonstrates our commitment to continue disrupting ransomware infrastructure and actors.</p>&mdash; Secretary Antony Blinken (@SecBlinken) <a href="https://twitter.com/SecBlinken/status/1511433500154478592?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 5, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The Russian-language market, founded in 2015, had also recently been <a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">placed unde</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r sanctio</a><a href="https://www.kommersant.ru/doc/5294429" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ns by the US</a> in an effort to cripple financial infrastructure used by cybercriminals associated with massive ransomware attacks that interrupted supply lines across much of the country throughout 2021. It suffered very little downtime during its nearly-seven years in operation, going offline only a few times; the most recent of which was during the early stages of the pandemic.</p>



<p>A Bitcoin-only market, Hydra limited services and sales to residents of countries comprising the former USSR. It made heavy use of the “dead drop” product delivery system through which buyers would dig up or uncover purchases (referred to as “treasures”) hidden at pre-specified locations, thus avoiding use of traditional postal delivery systems.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/">The End of a Dark Web Legacy: Hydra Goes Down</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/the-end-of-a-dark-web-legacy-hydra-goes-down/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</title>
		<link>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/</link>
					<comments>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2022 09:58:26 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1407</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Seven months after the return of DeSnake, one of the original AlphaBay’s two administrators, the new incarnation of</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Seven months after the <a href="/alphabay-is-back-says-former-admin-desnake/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">return of DeSnake</a>, one of the original <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s two administrators, the new incarnation of the infamous darknet market is once again on top of the competition &#8212; sans Hydra, the Russian-language darknet market which still dwarfs all others in sales volume. The distinction comes about as its closest competitor in size, World Market, has been largely <a href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">deemed no longer operational</a>, even if the site remains technically accessible.</p>



<p>The rise of the “new” <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> is not something that much of the darknet market community was expecting as many feared it was simply an extravagant “honeypot” operation designed to collect the credentials of buyers and vendors. For its first few months, the market remained relatively void of users and activity. However, with over half a year of steady operation under its belt and an ever-increasing base of users, these fears have largely subsided, and AlphaBay currently enjoys its greatest degree of popularity yet in this new manifestation.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">In 2017 the largest darknet market was seized, Alphabay &#8211; leading to the tragic suicide of its alleged admin Alex Cazes.<br><br>Recently its co-admin/fugitive DeSnake returned, relaunching the site in Alex&#39;s honor. With World&#39;s demise, Alphabay is close to reclaiming its throne as #1.</p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1506643215847411712?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 23, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>AlphaBay now hosts over 22,000 listings and is home 5,228 vendors and 340,000+ buyers, according to statistics maintained by the market. It is now a Monero (XMR)-only market and forces its users to operate under some of the strictest guidelines to ever be implemented by a darknet market. These include a no-weapons and no-fentanyl policy, short-timed finalization periods, and an advanced captcha system that has proved capable of preventing DDOS attacks from occurring.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="934" height="406" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1409" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1.png 934w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-300x130.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-1-768x334.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 934px) 100vw, 934px" /><figcaption>lphabay</figcaption></figure>



<p><em>After a slow re-start, activity at AlphaBay is now bustling.</em></p>



<p>The recent string of darknet market closures in 2022 has also helped AlphaBay’s propulsion to the top of the list. World Market, previously the largest (English-speaking) market by sales volume, has all but closed shop, as admins on Dread have repeatedly warned users against making new deposits to avoid losses in the likely event of an exit scam.</p>



<p>Within the past week, World Market added the following message to its main market page, although accounts registered within the last six months (sans brand new accounts) are still unable to log in to the market:</p>



<p>“<em>World Market is operational again, listing images will be restored soon, if you are missing a deposit open a ticket.”</em></p>



<p>AlphaBay also seems to be making some strides in its promises to delivery a decentralized darknet market – the first of its kind – that can theoretically continue to operate even if service provided by an operator is discontinued, for whatever reason. Upcoming tasks have been scheduled in the market’s <a href="http://alphabay522szl32u4ci5e3iokdsyth56ei7rwngr2wm7i5jo54j2eid.onion/roadmap" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">roadmap</a> for the project, and include building payment modules, multisig and escrow core functions, and a way for network operators to provide “initial decentralized infrastructure report.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/">AlphaBay Back on Top as Biggest English-Language Darknet Market</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/alphabay-back-on-top-as-biggest-english-language-darknet-market/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</title>
		<link>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/</link>
					<comments>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct deals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nature]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Darknet markets may serve larger roles economically by acting as catalysts for new trading relationships formed off-market, according</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/">Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Darknet markets may serve larger roles economically by acting as catalysts for new trading relationships formed off-market, according to results of a scientific study released yesterday, March 31<sup>st</sup>.</p>



<p>A new <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-07492-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a> published in <em>Nature</em>, one of the world’s pre-eminent scientific journals, concludes that user-to-user (U2U) cryptocurrency transactions consistently beat darknet market-based transactions in volume &#8212; a trend that has been in tact since the early days of Silk Road.</p>



<p>Researchers at the University of London, The Alan Touring Institute, and <a href="/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Chainalysis</a> analyzed 31 million Bitcoin transactions found to be associated with 40 darknet markets between 2011-2021 and found that volume between direct buyer-seller transactions exceeded that which flowed through the markets themselves, for all 40 of the markets analyzed.</p>



<p>Even though it is characteristic of darknet markets to expressly forbid their vendors from doing off-market deals with buyers, the report found that monthly trading volume between off-market U2U pairs consistently surpassed that of on-market trading volume. To put things in perspective, the researchers found that while $7.5 billion had flowed through the darknet markets analyzed over the last 10 years, the figure traded directly between buyers and sellers during this timeframe approached $30 billion, which is three-fold greater in total amount.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="645" height="488" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1405" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1.png 645w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-300x227.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 645px) 100vw, 645px" /></figure>



<p><em>Dynamics of single-market transaction relationships vs cross-market relationships. Source: Nature</em></p>



<p>The report detailed the process through which a certain percentage of buyers and sellers formed relationships on-market and then slowly moved business off-market, conducting deals directly among themselves. Several of these relationships were found to persist even after the darknet market on which they had formed closed, often exceeding the length of time for which markets were in operation. These “stable pairs” (as referenced in the report) accounted for only 1.7% of all U2U pairs identified yet accounted for 5% of the total $30 billion trading volume.</p>



<p>The report also found that U2U trades have been steadily increasing since the inception of darknet markets and the phenomenon seems to be resilient to any type of macroeconomic setback, only momentarily slowing down once: during the initial panic induced by COVID-19 in first half of 2020. It concludes that law enforcement efforts could possibly be better directed by analyzing the blockchain habits of individual sellers rather than that of whole market operations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/">Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</title>
		<link>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/</link>
					<comments>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators on the <em>Dread</em> darknet forum. On March 26<sup>th</sup>, forum moderator <em>Shakybeats</em> <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ann</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">oun</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ced</a> they had removed moderation privileges for the World Market administrator on <em>Dread</em>, disabling their ability to continue posting and confirming that an impending exit scam was likely.</p>



<p>Warning signs that something at World Market was amiss had been present for weeks, going back to a cautionary <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/d01b3750e9320def61f7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> by a self-described former colleague of the World Market admin, written late last month. In the post, user <em>nightmaremarket</em> accused the market of preparing for an exit scam &#8212; a plan which its admin immediately denied.</p>



<p>On March 23<sup>rd</sup>, <em>Dread</em> user <em>dontlaugh</em> started a new <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">th</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ead</a> urging World Market users to take heed of “a number of red flags,” which most notably included a rollback to a previous version of the website. Other warning signs included a sudden jump in the cost of vendor bond – from $1,500 to $3,000 – and reports from several vendors that their payments were trapped in the market, with withdrawal requests being ignored.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="671" height="98" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1393" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-300x44.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /><figcaption><em>One of many posts responding to World Market user complaints on Dread.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In an effort to respond to mounting complaints, World Market admin and <em>Dread</em> user <em>makarov</em> wrote the following <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ab00d26a769f65030710" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">counter-post</a>, which was heavily downvoted, with its rationale being dismissed by most respondents:</p>



<p>“The time has come that the World Market team must close shop. The team tried to fix numerous technical issues over the past week but could not recover what has been lost. We have worked hard to be the best market and to serve the community.</p>



<p>As much as I care for everyone at World Market, I also care about the vendors and buyers, and it would not be fair to continue at this point.” – <em>Dread user makarov</em></p>



<p>Less than two days later, the post by <em>dontlaugh</em> was edited to include the following text: “UPDATE: I think we can call it. Either one of the admins fucked the other (who would have thunk it) or they both pulled this to squeeze out as much as possible from everyone,” thus signaling the end of the market’s functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="477" height="407" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1394" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png 477w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1-300x256.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 477px) 100vw, 477px" /><figcaption><em>World Market welcome message that is currently still being displayed.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>After the closures of White House Market and Dark0de, World Market was for a short while one of the biggest darknet markets in operation, hosting well over 30,000 listings at its peak. The market used the traditional account deposit system, making an exit scam especially lucrative for a market its size.</p>



<p>As of March 27<sup>th</sup>, the rolled-back version of World Market was still accessible and allowing those who had created older accounts to still login and even make deposits. However, many functions have been removed, making purchases or withdrawals impossible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</title>
		<link>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/</link>
					<comments>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[empire market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OVO_sweatshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee indicted on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/24/nyregion/thomas-spieker-bitcoin-scheme.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">indicted</a> on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also funded a well-known darknet market vendor specializing in ketamine, according to charges recently filed by New York federal prosecutors.</p>



<p>In addition to converting BTC into cash for carding scammers, Nigerian “catfishers” and an “eastern European crime syndicate,” Thomas Spieker, 42, allegedly <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10650791/New-York-man-42-indicted-running-2-3M-cash-Bitcoin-money-laundering-scheme-crooks.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">provided $38,000 in laundered funds</a> to two people behind the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> darknet market vendor moniker, Zashan Khan and Cosma Siekierski. The vendor maintained a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/u/ovosweatshop" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">presence</a> on the <em>Dread</em> forum, racking up hundreds of positive reviews across multiple darknet markets during their 1-2 years in operation.</p>



<p>Investigators allege the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> vendor name was later taken over by John Humphrey and Fidello Palermo, both 51, who operated it out of a facility in Rochester, New York. The duo were arrested during a trip to Brooklyn where authorities found they were carrying 1.7 kg of ketamine powder/crystals and 140 vials of liquid ketamine.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="554" height="251" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1385" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg 554w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1-300x136.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 554px) 100vw, 554px" /></figure>



<p><em>John Humphrey, left, and Fidello Palermo, right, who allegedly assumed the popular New York ketamine vendor operation. Source: DailyMail.com</em></p>



<p>A total of seven people are being held in association with Spieker’s actions and face a large assortment of charges, ranging from conspiracy to commit money laundering to illegal drug charges.</p>



<p>According to his <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-spieker-60749062" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">LinkedIn profile</a>, Spieker was an Equity Derivates Specialist at Goldman Sachs from Feb 2001 to Mar 2003, founding a hip hop and club music promotion business named S!CK Productions in Nov 2010. His interest in music production and the club scene goes back to the year 2000.</p>



<p>The vendor name stems from a clothing line started by musician Drake, with ‘OVO’ standing for “October’s Very Own.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="718" height="495" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1386" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png 718w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-300x207.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 718px) 100vw, 718px" /></figure>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop vendor profile on the (now defunct) Empire Market. Source: The New York Times</em></p>



<p>Although Empire Market exit scammed in late August 2020, <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> was quick to set up replacement stores on White House Market and Dark Market within a matter of weeks. The quality of their operation apparently degraded over the following year, with customers complaining on <em>Dread</em> of receiving watered-down product and being victims of selective scamming by the vendor.</p>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop</em> also provided pills listed as Xanax and MDMA that received widely varying reviews, although this product took a back seat to their more consistent ketamine-vending operations.</p>



<p>All seven parties arrested and facing trial have pled not guilty to the charges against them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:57:39 by W3 Total Cache
-->