<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>silk road &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/silk-road/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:12:49 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>silk road &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</title>
		<link>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/</link>
					<comments>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 26 Apr 2022 12:12:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ross ulbricht]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silk road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1446</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recently unveiled court filing has revealed that Ross Ulbricht, the incarcerated 38-year-old founder of Silk Road, will</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/">Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A recently unveiled <a href="https://storage.courtlistener.com/recap/gov.uscourts.cand.368440/gov.uscourts.cand.368440.47.0_1.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">court filing</a> has revealed that Ross Ulbricht, the incarcerated 38-year-old founder of <em>Silk Road</em>, will forfeit claims toward 69,370 Bitcoin seized by US federal investigators in exchange for the clearance of $183 million in restitution he owed as part of his 2015 sentencing.</p>



<p>The seized bitcoins, which formerly resided at <a href="https://www.blockchain.com/btc/address/1HQ3Go3ggs8pFnXuHVHRytPCq5fGG8Hbhx" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">1HQ3Go3ggs8pFnXuHVHRytPCq5fGG8Hbhx</a>, also include the unsplit Bitcoin Cash and Bitcoin SV attached to the address private key and are currently valued at over $3 billion in total. As part of the agreement, Ulbricht and his family agreed to relinquish any possibility of ever obtaining the funds, regardless of whether he should ever be freed from prison.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">.<a href="https://twitter.com/RealRossU?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@RealRossU</a> has forfeited 69,370 BTC, BCH, BTG, and BSV to the US Government. <a href="https://t.co/V4Hr7plliI">pic.twitter.com/V4Hr7plliI</a></p>&mdash; ₿itcoin Gandalf The Orange <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f7e7.png" alt="🟧" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@BTCGandalf) <a href="https://twitter.com/BTCGandalf/status/1518642907259064327?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">April 25, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Blockchain sleuths noticed the coins – believed to have been hacked from Silk Road in 2013 – <a href="https://ciphertrace.com/nearly-1b-from-silk-road-move-for-first-time-since-2015/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">moved</a> for the first time in five years in November 2020, coinciding with a complaint filed with the US Department of Justice in which they state that the coins had been seized. The funds were reportedly <a href="https://bitcoinist.com/ross-ulbricht-agrees-to-pay-u-s-govt/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">confiscated</a> from a “notorious hacker” who used Silk Road to launder their ill-gotten proceeds.</p>



<p>Launched in Feb. 2011, Silk Road was the world’s first darknet market, conceived and built by Ulbricht as a manifestation of his anti-regulatory and pro-libertarian ideals. Though it was shut down a little more than two and a half years later, his original creation inspired countless other markets to form, initiating a darknet- and cryptocurrency-based movement that continues to grow in worldwide popularity each year.</p>



<p>Ulbricht, who went by the moniker <em>Dread Pirate Roberts</em> online, was handed a life sentence for his roles as Silk Road architect and admin. Though he remains in prison, several movements have sprung up advocating for his release, such as the <a href="https://www.freerossdao.org/">FreeRossDAO</a>. He was most recently denied a pardon by former US President Donald Trump.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/">Ross Ulbricht Cleared of $183 Million in Silk Road Fines</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ross-ulbricht-cleared-of-183-million-in-silk-road-fines/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Ulbricht Moved to Solitary Confinement After Bitcoin Conference ‘Appearance’</title>
		<link>/ulbricht-moved-to-solitary-confinement-after-bitcoin-conference-appearance/</link>
					<comments>/ulbricht-moved-to-solitary-confinement-after-bitcoin-conference-appearance/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Jun 2021 11:58:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ross ulbricht]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silk road]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=617</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The ‘Free Ross’ movement faces a setback, unwinding momentum built by Ulbricht’s recent heart-wrenching speech. Days after recording</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ulbricht-moved-to-solitary-confinement-after-bitcoin-conference-appearance/">Ulbricht Moved to Solitary Confinement After Bitcoin Conference ‘Appearance’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>The ‘Free Ross’ movement faces a setback, unwinding momentum built by Ulbricht’s recent heart-wrenching speech.</em></p>



<p>Days after <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=3V_SkLxgQjQ" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recording a talk from prison</a> for the 2021 Bitcoin Conference in Miami, darknet market pioneer Ross Ulbricht was reportedly moved from his regular cell to the Special Housing Unit, otherwise known as the SHU, or solitary confinement. Ulbricht, currently serving a term of double life in prison plus forty years for operating <em>Silk Road</em>, had agreed to speak with <em>Bitcoin Magazine</em> over the telephone, relaying a message to be presented later at the conference.</p>



<p>The news of Ulbricht’s transfer was first <a href="https://twitter.com/Free_Ross/status/1402279349714227201" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">relayed</a> by the <em>Free Ross</em> Twitter account, which is run by Lyn Ulbricht, Ross’ mother. It was not immediately clear why Ulbricht was transferred to solitary confinement, although Ulbricht himself mentioned that he was putting himself at risk by making the phone call.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Ross has been put in the SHU (aka &quot;the hole&quot;) after a recorded interview he did over the phone with <a href="https://twitter.com/BitcoinMagazine?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@BitcoinMagazine</a> was broadcasted at <a href="https://twitter.com/TheBitcoinConf?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@TheBitcoinConf</a> this weekend.<br><br>Please keep Ross in your thoughts &amp; prayers. <br><br>You can hear Ross speak here:<a href="https://t.co/Lk8CwvsKKj">https://t.co/Lk8CwvsKKj</a></p>&mdash; Free_Ross (@Free_Ross) <a href="https://twitter.com/Free_Ross/status/1402279349714227201?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 8, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>During the speech broadcast in Miami, Ulbricht talked about having previously spent time in the SHU for as long as four months. “Let me start by telling you about the hole,” he said a few minutes into the recording. “I once spent four months straight in the hole… The hole can make you or break you and there was a time when it broke me.”</p>



<p>While some speculated on Twitter that Ulbricht was being punished for speaking out against the prison, the justice department or the unfairness of his sentencing, others <a href="https://twitter.com/BillBlake2018/status/1402440577388580869" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pointed out</a> that prisons have rules preventing prisoners from talking to people not already on their “approved” list. This is a plausible explanation of what occurred given that the phone had been passed off from somebody else to the interviewer at <em>Bitcoin Magazine</em>.</p>



<p>Regardless, the recent punishment was generally viewed as a senseless and cruel act by those in the Bitcoin community, with one person going so far as to <a href="https://twitter.com/Alexandra933/status/1402365374834745346" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">describe</a> it as “a complete travesty of justice.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">arguably the least dangerous person in there and he gets the hole for an interview ok dude</p>&mdash; do it 4 bankroll (@901XMR) <a href="https://twitter.com/901XMR/status/1402397530718154752?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 8, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Ulbricht launched <em>Silk Road</em> – the first darknet market and the standard for countless others to follow – in February 2011 and operated it until it he was apprehended by law enforcement in October 2013. Despite an outpouring of support from the Bitcoin community, Ulbricht lost appeals to his sentence in 2017 and 2018, most recently being denied clemency by Donald Trump in 2020.</p>



<p>The theme of Ulbricht’s recording, initially played back to conference-goers on June 5<sup>th</sup>, centered around freedom, or the lack thereof. Several times during the emotionally-charged talk he repeated the phrase, “I want you to understand what it means to lose your freedom,” describing in harsh detail what it is like to live in prison with a life sentence.</p>



<p>“The irony is that I made Silk Road in the first place because I thought I was furthering the things I cared about. Freedom. Privacy. Equality. But by making Silk Road I wound up in a place where those things don&#8217;t exist.”</p>



<p>He also expressed remorse for the pain and suffering he caused others, asking that the community be compassionate and not forget his plight, or the plight of other non-violent offenders held in the prison system.</p>



<p>“These prisons are full of people who don&#8217;t deserve this… We need your help. We need you to care. We need you to look at the stark contrast between the freedom of bitcoin on the one hand and what it means to be locked in a cage until you die.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ulbricht-moved-to-solitary-confinement-after-bitcoin-conference-appearance/">Ulbricht Moved to Solitary Confinement After Bitcoin Conference ‘Appearance’</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ulbricht-moved-to-solitary-confinement-after-bitcoin-conference-appearance/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:08:13 by W3 Total Cache
-->