<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>exchange &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/exchange/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 19:31:03 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>exchange &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</title>
		<link>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/</link>
					<comments>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 20 Nov 2021 19:31:00 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Darknet Diaries]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[kraken]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=960</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An email from crypto exchange Kraken to UK customers was posted on Reddit yesterday, revealing the exchange’s plans</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/">Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An email from crypto exchange Kraken to UK customers was <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/CryptoCurrency/comments/qwww81/kraken_are_now_delisting_xmr_monero_from_their/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">posted</a> on Reddit yesterday, revealing the exchange’s plans to delist Monero (XMR) from coins accessible for trade in the region. Kraken claims they were forced to suspend listing of the privacy coin to remain “in compliance with UK regulations.” This also includes the gradual reduction and closure of all XMR margin positions.</p>



<p>Kraken is currently the second biggest exchange for Monero, processing about $5 &#8211; $6 million in trades daily. Binance remains the largest exchange for XMR, offering both BTC and USDT pairings, though non-KYC exchange services built into wallets like Exodus and Cake Wallet have been rising in popularity. In Nov. 2020, South Korea <a href="https://www.cpomagazine.com/data-privacy/south-koreas-new-crypto-aml-law-bans-trading-of-privacy-coins-monero-zcash/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">banned</a> the trade of privacy coins like Monero altogether, following Japan’s <a href="https://www.investopedia.com/news/japans-fsa-bans-private-cryptocurrencie" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">move</a> to do so in June 2018.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">This has to be a joke, right??? <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/monero?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#monero</a> <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/xmr?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#xmr</a> <a href="https://t.co/zWUaUoEtww">pic.twitter.com/zWUaUoEtww</a></p>&mdash; Monero Memes (@MoneroMemes) <a href="https://twitter.com/MoneroMemes/status/1461440528655044615?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite an outcry of disappointment of Reddit and Twitter, the price of XMR was little affected by the news. After a 9% jump overnight, the coin stood at $251.20 on Saturday morning, which is roughly twice of what it was exactly one year ago. XMR hit an all-time high of $517.62 on May 7<sup>th</sup> this year.</p>



<p>Released later in the day was a <a href="https://www.monerotalk.live/jack-rhysider-of-darknet-diaries-talks-monero" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">podcast</a> by <em>Monero Talk</em> with featured guest Jack Rhysider, host of the ever-popular <em>Darknet Diaries</em> podcast. In the podcast, Rhysider discussed the importance of privacy and fungibility in cryptocurrency use and gave his advice for approaching it in the future.</p>



<p>“I do think there’s powers that be that don’t like crypto and want it to go away,” he said. “Regulating it, banning it, the whole KYC… Making sure things are regulated properly and stuff like that. I think we gotta play the rules or we’re gonna lose it all,” he added.</p>



<p>“It’s a balance in a lot of this space of trying to play by the rules of the governments of the world and also trying as hard as we can to keep it anonymous and private. Its tricky. I’m thinking some governments aren’t liking this, because whoever controls the money controls the power as well. It’s a shift of power at the same time, and I think that’s probably what they’re scared of the most, is how they are unable to control it.” – Jack Rhysider, host of <em>Darknet Diaries</em></p>



<p>Rhysider cited Monero’s relative difficulty of use and volatility as reasons why he thought the coin hadn’t reached wider mainstream adoption. He noted that times when user interfaces are difficult and still confusing reflect that society is still in the early stages when it comes to crypto use, and he sees great potential for it in the future.</p>



<p>“Being able to work in the crypto space without having to use a centralized exchange is starting to look really good as far as privacy goes,” he said as <em>Monero Talk</em> podcast guest. “I like to be able to work in this space without having to give my address and phone number and zip code and all that just to buy something online.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/">Darknet Diaries Host Gives Thoughts on XMR as Kraken Delists</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darknet-diaries-host-gives-thoughts-on-xmr-as-kraken-delists/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</title>
		<link>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/</link>
					<comments>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 18:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[money laundering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday added 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/policy-issues/financial-sanctions/recent-actions/20210921" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">added</a> 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred from engaging in business with companies operating in the country. Sanctions placed by the U.S. government primarily effect Suex, a Czechoslovakia-based over-the-counter cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">b</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">lieved</a> to have handled hundreds of millions of dollars in cryptocurrency obtained from illicit sources.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="489" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-832" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-300x143.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-768x367.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11.jpg 1418w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Suex employees at Suex office location at 12 Federation East Tower, Moscow City, Moscow</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The sanctions are the result of the Biden administration’s <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-target-crypto-ransomware-payments-with-sanctions-11631885336" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pledge</a> to disrupt the network of exchanges which process the conversion of cryptocurrency obtained via malware ransom payments. Biden had asked for Russia’s cooperation in dismantling the financial services support for ransomware groups like REvil, which was responsible for the Colonial Pipeline attack in May.</p>



<p>According to Paul Abbate, FBI deputy director, “there is no indication that the Russian government has taken action to crack down on ransomware actors,” prompting the U.S. to move to sanctions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Great move today by the <a href="https://twitter.com/USTreasury?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@USTreasury</a> to sanction a Suex, a Moscow-based crypto exchange, one of the top money laundering outlets for cybercrime in the world. <br><br>Actions like these are a key component in a more aggressive strategy against ransomware<a href="https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy">https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy</a> <a href="https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3">https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3</a></p>&mdash; Dmitri Alperovitch (@DAlperovitch) <a href="https://twitter.com/DAlperovitch/status/1440371668786896898?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 21, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite the initial praise by several in the cybersecurity industry, the Treasury Department’s move to selectively block crypto addresses also provoked negative response from Bitcoin and privacy advocates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="566" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-833" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-300x166.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-768x424.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1536x849.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1.jpg 1839w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>“Repeat after me: stop trying to use the financial system in order to prosecute crimes after the fact,” exclaimed computer scientist and professor Emin Gun Sirer in a <a href="https://twitter.com/el33th4xor/status/1439193943183351810" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">tweet</a>. “The root cause of ransomware attacks is the weak state of computer security, not the mechanism used for payment.”</p>



<p>The Suex website, though still functioning, is now stripped of its ability to utilize the Visa and Mastercard payment processors much of its business is reliant upon, effectively dismantling its ability to do business. The company’s <a href="https://suex.io/terms-of-use" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">terms and conditions</a> indicate it adheres to rather common AML and KYC standards, requiring provision of personal identification for transactions over $500 in value.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="539" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-834" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-300x158.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-768x404.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1536x808.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Future sanctions are also expected to single out specific targets but the extent to which this measure will be employed for cryptocurrency addresses is not yet known.</p>



<p>In Nov. 2018, the Treasury dept. <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/sm556" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">blacklisted</a> two Bitcoin addresses belonging to Iranian nationals implicated in the laundering of millions in terrorist-designated funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:12:45 by W3 Total Cache
-->