<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>darknet market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/darknet-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:50:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>darknet market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</title>
		<link>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/</link>
					<comments>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug User Liberation Front]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A pair of Vancouver residents are publicly raising funds to buy drugs from the dark web with the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/">Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A pair of Vancouver residents are publicly raising funds to <a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy drugs fro</a><a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">m the</a><a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> dark web</a> with the intention of reducing the shocking number of overdose fatalities that is plaguing their city. Jeremy Kalicum, 26, and Eris Nyx, 31, believe that they can introduce an &#8220;accessible, reliable and safe&#8221; way for addicts to get their drugs by testing products purchased from the darknet and then distributing them to those most in need, reducing overdoses in the process.</p>



<p>The two founded the Drug User Liberation Front (DULF) in response to personally witnessing the growing epidemic of drug deaths in their neighborhood. Though seemingly shocking, DULF’s activities are generally seen as positive and are even encouraged by the local community.</p>



<p>Kalicum and Nyx stated that they only use Canada-based darknet markets to procure their substances &#8211; which include methamphetamine, heroin, and cocaine &#8211; testing them to ensure they are satisfactorily pure and do not contain lethal adulterants such as fentanyl or its analogs.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img/></figure>



<p><em>Not legal, but close &#8212; and pure. Tested and repackaged methamphetamine bought from a darknet market to be distributed by DULF. Source: CTV News</em></p>



<p>The Canadian government created the <a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/health-canada/services/opioids/responding-canada-opioid-crisis/safer-supply.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Safer Supply program</a> as a way of “addressing Canada’s overdose crisis,” recognizing that the problem could not be solved through mere abolition of drug use. The program is independently administered through a network of registered providers, like Nyx and Kalicum. Some programs require a diagnosis of substance abuse disorder for individuals to participate; others do not.</p>



<p>Drugs are provided by DULF only every so often (usually at rallies) and to those that have registered with the Vancouver Area Network of Drug Users (VANDU).</p>



<p>As far as the legality of their operation is concerned, Kalicum and Nyx realize what they are doing is illegal but hope to soon make inroads with the government to legitimize its status.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;Groups like DULF and VANDU understand better than governments do&quot; &#8211; Guy Felicella.<br><br>&quot;They’re giving people the substances they want along with information about what they’re consuming. <br><br>&quot;They’ve empowered substance users to make real, informed choices.&quot;<a href="https://t.co/IVAsTOsWTU">https://t.co/IVAsTOsWTU</a></p>&mdash; PHS (@PHScss) <a href="https://twitter.com/PHScss/status/1500565639093792778?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 6, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>&#8220;We have submitted a very well researched request to the federal government asking for exemptions to the Controlled Drugs and Substances Act to continue to act as a consumer protection initiative,” Nix said in an interview with reporters from <em>CTV News</em>. Though they have yet to receive an official response from the capitol, they are undeterred in their mission, willing to face whatever consequences it might entail.</p>



<p>“<em>The one thing we know is if people get drugs that are labelled &#8211; that have predictable content, and they know precisely what they are taking &#8211; then they will not die.” </em>– Eris Nyx, Drug User Liberation Front</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/">Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Stolen Check Sales Ramping Up Across the Dark Web</title>
		<link>/stolen-check-sales-ramping-up-across-the-dark-web/</link>
					<comments>/stolen-check-sales-ramping-up-across-the-dark-web/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 09:12:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Stolen Checks]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1364</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Mail theft is becoming an increasing problem across inner-cities in America, where checks are now being stolen out</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stolen-check-sales-ramping-up-across-the-dark-web/">Stolen Check Sales Ramping Up Across the Dark Web</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Mail theft is becoming an increasing problem across inner-cities in America, where checks are now being stolen out of postal boxes and sold on the dark web, according to reporters at <a href="https://www.nbcphiladelphia.com/investigators/consumer/mailed-checks-being-stolen-and-found-on-dark-web/3170486/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>NBC10 Philadelphia</em></a>.</p>



<p>One particular postal collection box in the city of Philadelphia seemed to have been a primary target for thieves who are selling checks on the darknet so the buyer can either alter the payee or create new checks based on the information they contain. In some cases, the checks were never cashed; in others where they were &#8212; the “pay to” recipient having been changed.</p>



<p>The leaders of one Philadelphia church, after discovering they had been victims of this type of mail theft, performed an audit to discover many checks had been written in their name and cashed out by fraudulent recipients.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="773" height="400" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1366" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.jpg 773w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-300x155.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-768x397.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 773px) 100vw, 773px" /></figure>



<p><em>Two checks found for sale on a darknet market, purchased by a consumer group and returned to their owners. Source: NBC10 Philadelphia</em></p>



<p>The number of stolen checks for sale on the darknet increased 100% between December of 2021 and January of 2022, according to David Maimon, Director the Evidence-Based Research Group at Georgia State University. Maimon’s team monitors 60 markets and other sites on the dark web, where he found personal checks go for an average of $150 and business checks as much as $250. He also noted that Arrow Keys – used by the US Postal Service as a ‘skeleton key’ to unlock mail receptacles across much of America – sell for as much as $7,000 on the darknet.</p>



<p>Although electronic checks and other payment methods are becoming increasingly popular, US citizens still <a href="https://www.billgo.com/blog/think-check-fraud-is-passe-think-again" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">mail out over 2.3 billion checks per year</a>, according to digital payments providers at <em>BillGO</em>.</p>



<p>To minimize the chances of checks and other mail being stolen, the US Postmaster General recommends only depositing mail into postal collection boxes before the last collection time of the day, or else to go to a post office itself to send the mail.</p>



<p>A quick search for relevant terms on the darknet market search engine <em>Recon</em> revealed no actual personal or business checks being listed for sale as such, but sometimes customer address and bank routing number information (key components of a check) were included as part of “fullz” packages, used primarily for identity theft.</p>



<p>Found for sale across many darknet markets are mail and check-cashing fraud “how-to” guides, which go for as little as $2.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/stolen-check-sales-ramping-up-across-the-dark-web/">Stolen Check Sales Ramping Up Across the Dark Web</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/stolen-check-sales-ramping-up-across-the-dark-web/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Darknet Market Community Struggling to Retain Faith After Dark0de Closure</title>
		<link>/darknet-market-community-struggling-to-retain-faith-after-dark0de-closure/</link>
					<comments>/darknet-market-community-struggling-to-retain-faith-after-dark0de-closure/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 11:02:03 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market admin]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1343</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>This year’s spate of darknet market closures has left much of the community feeling hopeless and turning to</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-market-community-struggling-to-retain-faith-after-dark0de-closure/">Darknet Market Community Struggling to Retain Faith After Dark0de Closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>This year’s spate of darknet market closures has left much of the community feeling hopeless and turning to social media to vent their frustrations over the dissolving trust they once had for such operations. Most recently, Dark0de – once considered to be one of the best darknet markets – pulled a <a href="/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">rather sudden exit scam</a>, taking all user funds held in their system along with them.</p>



<p>In addition to Dark0de, there have been at least three other major darknet market closures this year, leading some to ponder if there was perhaps a better way to go about implementing and running them; ideally removing the risk of closure. A <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/t4xm68/tired_of_exit_scams_why_a_fully_decentralized/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">post</a> in the r/darknet subreddit by u/lorenzlams addressing these questions managed to draw over 100 net upvotes and 116 comments within its first 20 hours, spurring a heated (though heavily moderated) conversation.</p>



<p>“It should be totally possible to build a fully decentralized and open market protocol, working on any of the existing L1 blockchain networks, smart contract based, etc,” wrote u/lorenzlams. “I&#8217;m surprised this doesn&#8217;t exist yet,” they added.</p>



<p>Several thread respondents in the Reddit thread pointed to <a href="https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/OpenBazaar" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">OpenBazaar</a> as a prototype for decentralized market management; the project itself initially created as a “proof-of-concept” to tackle the idea of a distributed darknet market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="727" height="284" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1344" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1.png 727w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-300x117.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 727px) 100vw, 727px" /></figure>



<p>Other respondents pointed out the need for some sort of a moderation team to prevent scams &#8212; an integral component of any darknet market that is somewhat dependent on centralization. Another problem to be faced by decentralized markets is the issue of fund management, which is not just potentially risky but a turnoff to average users, as well.</p>



<p>“I don’t know much about crypto tech but anyone involved in fueling a blockchain solely based on the illegal drug industry would be arrested I’m sure,” wrote u/hardwire_to_eat in response to the above-mentioned thread. “Escrow makes people feel much safer.”</p>



<p>A dive into claims made by market admins during the early stages of their market reveals that <a href="https://darknetlive.com/post/markets-lie/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">nearly all of them lie about their intentions</a>. Provided as evidence in the linked article were empty promises made the admins of Samsara Market, Nightmare Market, Dark0de, Kingdom Market, and Icarus &#8212; all of which ended up exit scamming between one month and two years after opening.</p>



<p>Despite the string of exit scams this year, some markets (such as White House Market and Cannazon) do manage to perform “graceful exits,” giving their users a warning of impending closure and providing them with ample time to withdraw their funds before shutting their servers down.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-market-community-struggling-to-retain-faith-after-dark0de-closure/">Darknet Market Community Struggling to Retain Faith After Dark0de Closure</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darknet-market-community-struggling-to-retain-faith-after-dark0de-closure/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</title>
		<link>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/</link>
					<comments>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Feb 2022 09:14:53 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dark0de reborn]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1337</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>After a week of delayed withdrawals and other issues suggesting an exit scam was likely, Dark0de – one</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/">Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>After a week of delayed withdrawals and other issues suggesting an exit scam was likely, Dark0de – one of the biggest and most popular darknet markets to ever exist – <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/3b03396226d17850311b" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">went offline</a> on Feb 24<sup>th</sup> without warning, taking user funds trapped in escrow along with it. There was no announcement made by the market admins as to what had happened or why the site was no longer available, but activity preceding the closure suggests it was a willful and coordinated effort to scam buyers and vendors.</p>



<p>“At this stage the facts are that onions are down and the dark0de admin /u/dark0dereborn has deleted their dread presence and scrubbed some posts/comments,” wrote Dread member <em>dontlaugh</em> on Thursday in a new thread in the <em>DarkNetMarkets</em> sub-Dread. “Not looking great for all involved as it would at this stage appear to be an ungraceful exit,” they added.</p>



<p>The post triggered a massive wave of comments from frustrated users, which had nearly exceeded 300 in count within its first 24 hours.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="733" height="467" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1339" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de.jpg 733w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/dark0de-300x191.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 733px) 100vw, 733px" /></figure>



<p><em>The famous welcome screen for Dark0de featured original, colorful artwork, giving it some rare personality that set it apart from competitors.</em></p>



<p>While most of Dark0de’s existence was uneventful and smooth for buyers and vendors, some users reported running into deposit and withdrawal issues as early as Dec 2021. On the Dread forum, one Dark0de user reported a XMR deposit requiring over 300 confirmations before funds were credited to their account. Other users commented on the increasing lack of professionalism exhibited by the market’s admins during its last few months.</p>



<p>“They would just make up half-arsed excuses and stall by insisting you prove something they should already be able to do,” said user <em>PaperHat</em> on Dread. “If not crooked, you can&#8217;t trust that level of incompetence either. Sometimes you can just tell someone is a compulsive liar from the way they talk and I got that sense from the admin,” they added.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Dark0de had a great collection of vendors, and I wish all of the vendors well in their new endeavors. I wish dark0de would have exited normally, but it is what it is. <br>May The Markets Live On Forever. <a href="https://t.co/NsRCSQXmMD">pic.twitter.com/NsRCSQXmMD</a></p>&mdash; uɐpʇou@ ✸ <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1e6.png" alt="🇺🇦" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@notdan) <a href="https://twitter.com/notdan/status/1496838344482779137?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 24, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Dark0de is the fourth major darknet market to go down this year, with the other three being Cartel Market, Monopoly Market and CanadaHQ. All three are believed to have been seized by law enforcement. The market closures to occur this year stand in stark contrast to the comparatively “graceful exits” of White House Market and Cannazon; both of which provided their customers with a warning and ample time to withdraw their funds.</p>



<p>Dark0de was founded in the first half of 2020 and hailed for its comparatively wide range of features, which included support for Monero, Bitcoin multisig transactions, and Direct Pay, which allowed users to send payment to a designated address rather than from a market account balance. These and other features earned it a massive user base in the roughly two years of its existence. There were over 40,000 listings on the market at the time of its closure.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/">Dark0de Exit Scam Confirmed</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/dark0de-exit-scam-confirmed/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cybercriminals Choosing DeFi Over Darknet For Cashouts</title>
		<link>/cybercriminals-choosing-defi-over-darknet-for-cashouts/</link>
					<comments>/cybercriminals-choosing-defi-over-darknet-for-cashouts/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 27 Jan 2022 10:28:50 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[defi]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1288</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The share of ‘illicit’ crypto funds moving through darknet market continues to decrease, according to blockchain analysts at</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cybercriminals-choosing-defi-over-darknet-for-cashouts/">Cybercriminals Choosing DeFi Over Darknet For Cashouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The share of ‘illicit’ crypto funds moving through <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> continues to decrease, according to blockchain analysts at <em>Chainalysis</em> in a recent <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-crypto-crime-report-preview-cryptocurrency-money-laundering/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a>. Rising in its place are DeFi protocols which accounted for 14% of funds deemed by the report’s researchers to come from illicit sources in 2021, representing a nearly-2,000% percent increase from the previous year.</p>



<p>The researchers also found funds emanating from <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> operations tended to be far less centralized and more distributed among wallets than most other categories of illicit funds. They said this was due to the more independent nature of darknet market vendors and operators, whereas proceeds from Ponzi schemes and ransomware attacks tended to flow back into a single or small number of wallets.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Money laundering activity remains heavily concentrated to a shockingly small group of criminal facilitators. In 2021, 54% of funds sent from illicit addresses – approx. $2.5 billion – went to 583 service deposit addresses. <a href="https://t.co/76xoOK1sRh">https://t.co/76xoOK1sRh</a> <a href="https://t.co/k5pFzrZKxZ">https://t.co/k5pFzrZKxZ</a> <a href="https://t.co/Ji3YIWBIy9">pic.twitter.com/Ji3YIWBIy9</a></p>&mdash; Chainalysis (@chainalysis) <a href="https://twitter.com/chainalysis/status/1486422407766233092?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 26, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“While billions of dollars’ worth of cryptocurrency moves from illicit addresses every year, most of it ends up at a surprisingly small group of services,” concluded <em>Chainalysis</em>. “Many of (these services) appear purpose-built for money laundering based on their transaction histories,” they wrote, further suggesting such services were candidates for federal blacklisting.</p>



<p><em>Chainalysis</em> clarified their definition of ‘illicit’ in the report to include “cryptocurrency-native crime,” specifically mentioning darknet market sales and ransomware attack proceeds as examples. They noted that 2021 was the first year where less than half of such funds were sent to centralized exchanges, which were also displaced by increased favor for DeFi platforms.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="961" height="434" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1291" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2.png 961w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2-300x135.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-2-768x347.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 961px) 100vw, 961px" /><figcaption><em>Trends in popularity of cashout methods for illicit funds. Source: Chainalysis</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The researchers also provided comparisons in money laundering between fiat currency and crypto, noting that while up to 5% of all fiat funds go through money laundering services each year, this figure for crypto funds is only 0.05%, or 100-fold smaller. For as many benefits and conveniences crypto poses for those hoping to avoid the attention of the law, <em>Chainalysis</em> counters the viability of its adoption by the darknet with the following insight:</p>



<p>“<em>The biggest difference between fiat and cryptocurrency-based money laundering is that, due to the inherent transparency of blockchains, we can more easily trace how criminals move cryptocurrency between wallets and services in their efforts to convert their funds into cash.”</em></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cybercriminals-choosing-defi-over-darknet-for-cashouts/">Cybercriminals Choosing DeFi Over Darknet For Cashouts</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/cybercriminals-choosing-defi-over-darknet-for-cashouts/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</title>
		<link>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/</link>
					<comments>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 19 Jan 2022 12:41:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cartel market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[monopoly market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1101</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The streak of graceful exits by some of the world’s most popular darknet markets has come to a</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/">Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The streak of graceful exits by some of the world’s most popular darknet markets has come to a close. Hope has faded that either Monopoly Market or Cartel Marketplace, which <a href="https://www.securitynewspaper.com/2022/01/17/dark-web-sales-platforms-monopoly-market-and-cartel-market-shut-down-mysteriously/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">went offline within a few days of each other</a> just before the new year, will return and resume business as usual. Theories abounded in social media communities as to why the markets went down, with many assuming the possibilities of exit scam or seizure being the most likely.</p>



<p>Monopoly Market, the better-known and more celebrated of the two, was believed to be a top-notch operation in terms of its security and design. It was popular for its streamlined approach to the order purchasing process and introduction of novel features not employed elsewhere.</p>



<p>Orders placed on or before Dec 27 were processed, according to vendors on Monopoly Market; after that date, access to the market became stifled before disappearing completely. Scores of Monopoly users flocked to the market’s page on <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/d/Monopoly" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>Dread</em></a> to voice their concerns; many of which were met by scathing retorts from an extremely enraged admin.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It seems I missed it over the New Year but Monopoly Market has been down for almost a week now. Admin claims it will be back, users are suggesting everything from exit scam to server seizure.</p>&mdash; Patrick Shortis (@Patrick_Shortis) <a href="https://twitter.com/Patrick_Shortis/status/1478033669994520577?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 3, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>After performing damage control that involved vague promises of a gradual return, <em>MonopolyOfficial</em>, the market’s admin account on <em>Dread</em>, fell silent, leading to new rounds of speculation and the forum’s <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/05281ad4c4ebb6a9adfc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">decision to close the thread</a>.</p>



<p>“Scam? busted? Overdosed? We may never know what happened to /u/MonopolyOfficial,” said <em>Dread</em> moderator Shakybeats about the missing admin. “We may never know what happened to him.”</p>



<p>Monopoly was one of the oldest darknet markets still in operation at the time of its shutdown, having been in operation since July 2019. It was hailed for being innovative as far as supporting direct payments and Monero was concerned. Cartel Marketplace was newer market, opening for business in the spring of 2020. Unlike Monopoly, it was plagued by technical and security problems over the course of its existence.</p>



<p>The two markets were vastly different in terms of the products they offered. Monopoly was a drugs-only darknet market that banned the sale of all digital goods; whereas Cartel was heavy on digital items and had earned a notorious reputation for selling stolen data. There is no known connection between the two markets.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/">Monopoly and Cartel Markets Not Coming Back</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/monopoly-and-cartel-markets-not-coming-back/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>List of Darknet Markets Growing, Admins Undeterred by Arrests of Peers</title>
		<link>/list-of-darknet-markets-growing-admins-undeterred-by-arrests-of-peers/</link>
					<comments>/list-of-darknet-markets-growing-admins-undeterred-by-arrests-of-peers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 26 Nov 2021 23:48:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=983</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The darknet market economy appears to be unphased by ramped up efforts of law enforcement to bring it</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/list-of-darknet-markets-growing-admins-undeterred-by-arrests-of-peers/">List of Darknet Markets Growing, Admins Undeterred by Arrests of Peers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The darknet market economy appears to be unphased by ramped up efforts of law enforcement to bring it down. One month after the U.S. Department of Justice announced the results of <a href="/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Operation Dark HunTor</a> – a multinational sting that netted the arrest of some 150 individuals – the number of notable darknet markets currently in operation has increased to what could be a record high. This holds true even after taking into consideration the recent retirements of White House Market and Cannazon.</p>



<p>A series of interviews with market admins performed by news outlet <em>Sputnik</em> supports the idea that <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/feature-darknet-market-operators-undeterred-1408361.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">admins and vendors are largely undeterred by takedowns</a>; the majority of them attributing lapses in OpSec (“human error”) to the downfall of their peers. The interviews paint a picture of market admins being confident in their practices and assuming law enforcement to remain reliant on classic techniques rather than employing new exploits or exotic tracing methods.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="966" height="465" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-4.png" alt="" class="wp-image-985" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-4.png 966w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-4-300x144.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-4-768x370.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 966px) 100vw, 966px" /></figure>



<p><em>The list of markets maintained by Recon, the dark market indexing service.</em></p>



<p>In general, admins saw the <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> phenomenon as unstoppable and only capable of increasing in growth and popularity in the future.</p>



<p>&#8220;At the end of the day every bust only creates more markets,” an admin identified as Gibson from Versus Market told <em>Sputnik</em>.</p>



<p>“<em>For every market they shut down a few new markets rise. (It’s) a battle they can&#8217;t win. Look at how many markets there are right now. Last time I checked it was more than 20 and there are new market popping up all the time.” – </em>Gibson, Versus admin</p>



<p>According to stats kept by <a href="http://recon222tttn4ob7ujdhbn3s4gjre7netvzybuvbq2bcqwltkiqinhad.onion/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Recon</a>, there are currently 29,100 vendors offering 25,400 listings across 15 different markets. The list of active markets indexed by Recon includes AlphaBay, CannaHome, Versus, Monopoly, Dark0de, DarkFox, Cartel Marketplace, ASAP, Cypher, Tor2Door, ToRReZ, World Market, Bohemia, Archetyp, and Incognito.</p>



<p>During the Dark HunTor raids, 150 alleged darknet market vendors and associates were arrested in the US, UK, Australia, Bulgaria, France, Germany, Italy, the Netherlands, and Switzerland. The raids resulted in the confiscation of a combined $31+ million in crypto funds and hundreds of pounds of various drugs, as well. Dark HunTor drew from information gleaned from the <a href="https://www.europol.europa.eu/newsroom/news/darkmarket-worlds-largest-illegal-dark-web-marketplace-taken-down" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">January takedown of DarkMarket</a>, which was the biggest darknet market at the time.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/list-of-darknet-markets-growing-admins-undeterred-by-arrests-of-peers/">List of Darknet Markets Growing, Admins Undeterred by Arrests of Peers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/list-of-darknet-markets-growing-admins-undeterred-by-arrests-of-peers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cannazon Closure Follows White House Market Example</title>
		<link>/cannazon-closure-follows-white-house-market-example/</link>
					<comments>/cannazon-closure-follows-white-house-market-example/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 24 Nov 2021 17:45:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cannazon]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=977</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the darknet’s most well-known markets for marijuana and related products announced its impending closure on Tuesday.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannazon-closure-follows-white-house-market-example/">Cannazon Closure Follows White House Market Example</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the darknet’s most well-known markets for marijuana and related products announced its impending closure on Tuesday. <a href="/directory/listing/cannazon-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Cannazon</a>, which had been in operation since 2018, was considered to be one of the premiere darknet markets for cannabis products across Europe and the UK. The closure was announced on <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/a093b7eaa7a98bd83cc0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Dread</a> where the market had maintained a presence for years.</p>



<p>The top of the main market screen currently offers the following message:</p>



<p>“We are retiring. No exit scam. All orders finalized. All vendors got their money.”</p>



<p>Below this is a PGP-signed messaged dated November 23<sup>rd</sup> going into an explanation of the closure, which managed to catch many users off guard. “Everyone knew that this day would come,” reads the message. “No market will be here forever. We are officially retiring.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="607" height="160" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3.png" alt="" class="wp-image-979" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3.png 607w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-3-300x79.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 607px) 100vw, 607px" /></figure>



<p>Cannazon suffered a spate of DDOS attacks during the last few months which, at times, left the market down for over 24 hours at a time. The most recent attack, which concluded just nine days ago, left the market partially offline, with some components inaccessible to users. All but one market URL was usable, and the market’s community began to suspect plans of an exit scam were afoot. Rather than restore the market to its full functionality, the Cannazon admins apparently decided the time to quit was right, following in the footsteps of White House Market’s graceful August exit.</p>



<p>In the week preceding closure, Cannazon had over 4,000 product listings across hundreds of vendors, with thousands of buyers active at least monthly.</p>



<p>Complete with how-to manuals, harm reduction guides and a helpful staff, Cannazon set standards for future darknet markets, supporting both Bitcoin (BTC) and Monero (XMR), offering multisig escrow for BTC payments, and allowing users to browse the market without having to log in. Their user-friendliness and site design even earned the praise of security researchers familiar with the darknet market scene.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Cannazon is a cannabis-only market and has the friendliest user guides I&#39;ve seen. Will their narrow approach draw less heat? Bitcoin and Monero are accepted. (none of these tweets are endorsements, this is for researchers only) <a href="https://t.co/Rznj2EQoGZ">pic.twitter.com/Rznj2EQoGZ</a></p>&mdash; dark.fail (@DarkDotFail) <a href="https://twitter.com/DarkDotFail/status/1299445257864503296?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">August 28, 2020</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“Since our first days it was pretty clear for us that we will never do an exit scam like some other markets,” read the PGP-signed message posted on Cannazon. “The massive DDOS attack was a very good chance to lower the number of orders and we decided to keep the market partially offline afterwards,” it explained, concluding with upbeat wishes for the future:</p>



<p>“We hope that every one of you finds some good alternative for buying or selling cannabis products. Moreover, we hope that other markets will follow this path and consider retiring gracefully.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cannazon-closure-follows-white-house-market-example/">Cannazon Closure Follows White House Market Example</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/cannazon-closure-follows-white-house-market-example/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</title>
		<link>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/</link>
					<comments>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silkroad]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A British man who allegedly masterminded the development of Silk Road 2.0 was ordered to forfeit $670,000 in</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/">Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A British man who allegedly masterminded the development of <em>Silk Road 2.0</em> was <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/alexandria/article/silk-road-boss-told-to-hand-over-670-000-in-btc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ordered</a> to forfeit $670,000 in Bitcoin on Wednesday. The order is the result of a financial investigation conducted while suspected admin Thomas White, 26, remains behind bars. White, who went by the online nickname Cthulhu, plead guilty to charges stemming from his admin activities in 2019, for which he was handed a sentence of five and a half years.</p>



<p>The order comes a few days shy of the seventh anniversary of the <a href="https://www.wired.com/2013/11/silk-road/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">takedown</a> of the original <em>Silk Road</em>, of which White was an elevated member. England’s National Crime Agency <a href="https://nationalcybersecuritynews.today/british-administrator-for-darknet-market-silk-road-ordered-to-forfeit-490000-in-bitcoin-science-tech-news-computerhacking-hacking/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">described</a> White as “a well-regarded member of the original Silk Road hierarchy,” using his position of influence in the group and community to establish his own market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Serious Organised Crime evolves at pace, our response must keep up! Meticulous investigation took down the criminal Dark Web marketplace Silk Road 2.0, now our <br>investigation leads to the confiscation of nearly £0.5m in cryptocurency, the ill gotten gains of this criminal. <a href="https://t.co/kpkF4Sa5vV">https://t.co/kpkF4Sa5vV</a></p>&mdash; Matt Horne Deputy Director Investigations (@MattHorneNCA) <a href="https://twitter.com/MattHorneNCA/status/1455596581105848329?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 2, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Though investigators remain unsure of the total profits accrued by White as <em>Silk Road 2.0</em> administrator, it is known that he received a commission between 1% and 5% of each sale, without around $96 million in goods traded under his leadership. This amounts to tens of thousands of users.</p>



<p>White had been enrolled in an accounting degree program at a Liverpool university before dropping out to work for <em>Silk Road</em>. He managed to re-open the market under its “2.0” version within a month of the shutdown of the original. The National Crime Agency noted that although he was unemployed at the time, White put up over $11,000 to rent a “plush apartment on Liverpool’s city waterfront” while suspected of operating his market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">7 years ago today&#8230; Silk Road 2.0 was seized, exactly one year after it opened. Soon after, we discovered there had been a Homeland Security officer on staff the whole time <a href="https://t.co/JmxZUL2cuL">pic.twitter.com/JmxZUL2cuL</a></p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1457090624889384962?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 6, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The investigation into White’s finances on the blockchain estimated his fortune to be somewhere between $1.5 and $2 million.</p>



<p>Ross Ulbricht, who was sentenced in 2013 for charges related to his role in constructing and operating <em>Silk Road</em>, continues to serve a life term without the possibility of parole.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/">Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</title>
		<link>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/</link>
					<comments>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darkmarket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the largest darknet market vendor sting operations in recent history saw the arrest of 150 vendors</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/">DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the largest darknet market vendor sting operations in recent history saw the arrest of 150 vendors associated with the now-defunct DarkMarket on Monday, attracting <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/coordinated-bust-of-dark-web-dealers-yields-150-arrests-in-u-s-europe-11635263760" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">massive attention</a> from the world’s biggest news media outlets. The <a href="https://www.dw.com/en/europol-investigation-busts-150-high-value-darknet-vendors/a-59625287" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">internationally-coordinated raid</a>, which involved law enforcement efforts from nine countries, also netted around 234 kilograms in drugs, 45 guns, and more than $31.6 million in cash.</p>



<p>Dubbed ‘Operation Dark Huntor,’ the raid attracted media attention globally, hitting front pages of newspapers in the affected countries, which include the US, UK, Germany, Australia, Bulgaria, France, Italy, the Netherlands, and Switzerland. Out of these countries, the US saw the most arrests at 65, followed by 47 in Germany and 24 in the UK. One of the biggest distribution hubs identified in the operation was said to be located in Houston, Texas.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">One of&#39;biggest global crackdowns&#39;on dark web:<br>DarkHunTOR operation launched after the Jan 2021 dismantling by <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1ea.png" alt="🇩🇪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> of DarkMarket,one of the leading cyber black marketplaces<br><br>150 arrests<br>UK:65<br>Germany:47<br>UK:24<br>Italy:4<br>Netherlands:4<br>Several&quot;high-value targets&quot;<a href="https://t.co/wXn4rjIqaU">https://t.co/wXn4rjIqaU</a></p>&mdash; Mila (@Milatrud11) <a href="https://twitter.com/Milatrud11/status/1453070132406886416?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 26, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>A well-produced <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VUhzK2cY_PY" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">video</a> posted on the FBI’s official YouTube account claims to contain footage of arrests related to the operation while offering a stern warning to darknet market vendors.</p>



<p>“The FBI’s Joint Criminal Opioid and Darknet Enforcement (JCODE) team was established in 2018 to peel back perceived anonymity of dark web drug dealers, leading to arrests like these,” reads text in the video as scenes depicting arrests unfold. “Targets in JCODE enforcement operations buys and sell illegal drugs on dark web markets…</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="671" height="321" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-906" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5.jpg 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5-300x144.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /></figure>



<p><em>Screenshot from FBI YouTube video explaining US authority actions in Monday’s raid.</em></p>



<p>DarkMarket, which was <a href="https://www.dw.com/en/largest-illegal-darknet-marketplace-darkmarket-taken-offline/a-56200737" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">taken offline in January</a> after its operator was arrested in Germany, was considered to be “the biggest darknet market” at the time. The market’s takedown was also the result of a months-long multi-national criminal investigation, involving law enforcement from seven countries, coordinated by the DEA, FBI, and Europol. The 150 vendors arrested in yesterday’s raid represent roughly 6% of the 2,400 total vendors at DarkMarket at the time of its closure.</p>



<p>Among the approximately 516 pounds of drugs confiscated by authorities during the raid were 25,000 ecstasy pills and thousands of pills containing amphetamine (Adderall), alprazolam (Xanax), and oxycodone (OxyContin). A US deputy attorney general stated that over 90% of confiscated pills in the country during the raid contained “counterfeit opioids,” such as fentanyl.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/">DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:55:56 by W3 Total Cache
-->