<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>russia &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/russia/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>russia &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over one ton of drugs was seized in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over one ton of drugs was <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/russian-police-say-caught-drug-gang-led-by-uk-1504121.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">seized</a> in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation into 26 individuals believed to have been operating a shop on the former Hydra darknet marketplace. The criminal group, led by Ukrainian nationals, organized the production of the drugs and their sale in Russia under the name “Murmur Shop,” which operated on Hydra between 2019 and 2021.</p>



<p>According to investigators, the group included 15 people from Ukraine, seven from Russia, two from Moldova, one from Tajikistan, and one from Belarus. While the leadership was based in Ukraine, Russian nationals were hired to help transport the drugs to <a href="https://aif.ru/society/law/v_mosgorsud_napravili_delo_mezhdunarodnoy_gruppy_iz_26_narkotorgovcev" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">more than 60 constituent entities</a> across the Russian Federation. Four clandestine drug laboratories in the Moscow, Vladimir and Ivanovo regions were also uncovered during the investigation.</p>



<p>“The leadership of the drug group and the management of its financial assets was carried out from the territory of Ukraine,” said Irina Volk, a spokeswoman for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs, on Thursday. “The recruitment of laboratory staff was also carried out there for the further dispatch to Russia. Applicants were forced to undergo polygraph tests,” she added.</p>



<p>In early April, Hydra’s servers were <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">s</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ei</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zed</a> in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement, knocking the world’s biggest darknet market offline in the process. Days earlier, the US Department of Justice had filed sanctions against Hydra and an online money exchanger known to be associated with the market. On April 11<sup>th</sup>, the Meshchansky Court of Moscow arrested Dmitry Pavlov, one of the alleged founders of the online drug platform.</p>



<p>In January, a group of Russian nationals were <a href="https://www.gazeta.ru/social/news/2022/01/20/17168629.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> for their roles in importing cocaine from Argentina, some of which had been hidden at the Russian embassy in Buenos Aires. The group’s mastermind was sentenced to 18 years in a penal colony while other members received sentences between 13 and 17 years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Hackers and Ransom Launderers Operating Out Of Famed Moscow Skyscraper</title>
		<link>/hackers-and-ransom-launderers-operating-out-of-famed-moscow-skyscraper/</link>
					<comments>/hackers-and-ransom-launderers-operating-out-of-famed-moscow-skyscraper/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Dec 2021 13:12:34 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[EvilCorp]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Federation Tower]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1041</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Expanding on a report by the New York Times earlier this month, further investigation efforts reveal that Moscow’s</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hackers-and-ransom-launderers-operating-out-of-famed-moscow-skyscraper/">Hackers and Ransom Launderers Operating Out Of Famed Moscow Skyscraper</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Expanding on a <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2021/12/06/world/europe/ransomware-russia-bitcoin.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a> by the <em>New York Times</em> earlier this month, further investigation efforts reveal that Moscow’s Federation Tower East is home to a <a href="https://central.asia-news.com/en_GB/articles/cnmi_ca/features/2021/12/21/feature-01" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">surprising concentration of cybercriminals</a> and their money laundering enablers.</p>



<p>One of the tallest and most prestigious high rises in the world, the Federation Tower East (Vostok) is home to many of Russia’s elites, with some residential units going for over $30 million. They are joined by an odd mixture of individuals wanted and sanctioned by the US government for a wide assortment of computer-based crimes.</p>



<p>Among the businesses registered as operating in the Federation Tower East are Suex and EggChange – two crypto exchangers that had previously been sanctioned by the US Treasury Department for their role in cashing out ransomware payments collected from US companies (such as Colonial Pipeline).</p>



<p>The tower is also <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/technology-59297187" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">home to suspected members of EvilCorp</a>, one of Russia’s biggest and oldest hacking groups which has been under the eye of US law enforcement since 2010. Maksim Yakubets, the alleged leader of the group, is accused of extorting or stealing more than $100 million in hacks that affected 40 countries.­­­ Both he and EvilCorp associate Igor Turashev have offices in the Federation Tower, with multiple companies registered under their name(s).</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1f7-1f1fa.png" alt="🇷🇺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><br>&quot;Nor is Igor Turashev, 40, keeping a low profile.<br><br>Using public records, my colleague&#8230;found 3 companies registered in his name.<br><br>All have offices in Moscow&#39;s prestigious *Federation Tower*&#8230;&quot;<br><br>Evil Corp: &#39;My hunt for the world&#39;s most wanted hackers&#39;<a href="https://t.co/GHDYkk8imx">https://t.co/GHDYkk8imx</a></p>&mdash; Sisu Within <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1fa-1f1f8.png" alt="🇺🇸" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e6-1f1fa.png" alt="🇦🇺" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e8.png" alt="🇨" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e6-1f1ec.png" alt="🇦🇬" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e7-1f1f3.png" alt="🇧🇳" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1ff.png" alt="🇿" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@sisu_sanity) <a href="https://twitter.com/sisu_sanity/status/1461245068417851395?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 18, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Another exchange found to have processed a significant amount of Bitcoin from the Hydra darknet marketplace, Buy-bitcoin.pro, also has an office in the tower, along with the similarly-described CashBank.</p>



<p>According to Massachusetts-based cybersecurity firm Recorded Future, there are about 50 cryptocurrency exchanges in Moscow City, the financial district of the capital, that engage in some form of illicit transactions.</p>



<p>The US Treasury Department&#8217;s Financial Crimes Enforcement Network (FinCEN) estimated that approximately $590 million in crypto ransoms were paid out to attackers in the first six months of 2021 – a figure that is 42% larger than the amount paid across the entirety of 2020.</p>



<p>Russia, which recently <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/russian-parliament-sets-up-working-group-on-cryptocurrency-regulations/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">set up a working group</a> to tackle the gaps in cryptocurrency regulation, began the partial regulation of cryptocurrency in January this year, after the earlier passage of law pertaining to how the country would treat “digital financial assets.”</p>



<p>In a meeting with President Biden last summer, President Putin dismissed the idea that ransomware cybercriminals plaguing the US were based out of Russia, although he also pledged to remain open to cooperative efforts in helping to resolve the issue.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/hackers-and-ransom-launderers-operating-out-of-famed-moscow-skyscraper/">Hackers and Ransom Launderers Operating Out Of Famed Moscow Skyscraper</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/hackers-and-ransom-launderers-operating-out-of-famed-moscow-skyscraper/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Russia Attempts to Ban Darknet Access, Fails</title>
		<link>/russia-attempts-to-ban-darknet-access-fails/</link>
					<comments>/russia-attempts-to-ban-darknet-access-fails/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Dec 2021 12:50:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tor]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1029</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A court decision last week effectively banned public access to the darknet across Russia, leaving many in the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russia-attempts-to-ban-darknet-access-fails/">Russia Attempts to Ban Darknet Access, Fails</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A court decision last week effectively <a href="https://www.cpomagazine.com/data-privacy/russia-prevents-access-to-tor-network-at-federal-level-as-kremlin-ramps-up-campaign-of-internet-control/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">banned</a> public access to the darknet across Russia, leaving many in the country perplexed at why the government would decide to make such a move now. The decision puts Russia on a course that is being compared to that of China, where websites critical of those in power can be easily restricted.</p>



<p>On Dec. 1<sup>st</sup>, major internet providers across Russia started <a href="https://blog.torproject.org/tor-censorship-in-russia/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">blocking access to the Tor network</a>, with the government officially banning the main Tor Project website on Dec. 7<sup>th</sup>. The Tor Project has confirmed via independent researchers that default Tor bridges are also being made inaccessible by some Russian internet providers, and that their availability is ever-decreasing.</p>



<p>According to statistics kept at the Tor Project, Russia has the <a href="https://metrics.torproject.org/userstats-relay-table.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">second biggest base of Tor users</a> in the world, with about 15% of all Tor traffic originating from the country as of Dec. 1<sup>st</sup>. As of Dec 15<sup>th</sup>, however, this figure has only decreased to 14%, which suggests that most Russian Tor users are able to circumnavigate the ban.</p>



<p>Among the problems experienced by Russians attempting to access the Tor network are repeated connection resets, which <em>Wired</em> magazine <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/russia-block-tor-censorship" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">suggests</a> are due to the use of state-executed “deep packet inspection” (DPI), capable of “sniffing traffic” for blacklisted destinations.</p>



<p>“In practice what they would do is define a rule in the configuration of their firewall to drop all traffic toward a certain destination,” Arturo Filasto, an engineer at the Open Observatory of Network Interference told <em>Wired</em>. “In certain configurations they may choose to implement the block by actively terminating the connection by injecting a reset packet.”</p>



<p>The Tor Project stresses that new bridges will continually have to be created for network access to remain open in Russia. After making a plea to the community, they quickly surpassed their goal of creating 200 new obfs4 bridges. Those in Russia who want to access the project’s homepage on the clear web can still do so through a <a href="https://tor.eff.org/">mirror</a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/russia-attempts-to-ban-darknet-access-fails/">Russia Attempts to Ban Darknet Access, Fails</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/russia-attempts-to-ban-darknet-access-fails/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</title>
		<link>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/</link>
					<comments>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 18:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Russian man believed to be operating cryptocurrency exchanges associated with the laundering of ransomware proceeds was “practically</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/">Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A Russian man believed to be operating cryptocurrency exchanges associated with the laundering of ransomware proceeds was “<a href="https://sputniknews.com/20211113/russias-dubnikov-practically-kidnapped-by-fbi-in-mexico-sent-to-amsterdam---attorney-1090699499.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">practically kidnapped</a>” by the United States after landing in the Netherlands, according to his attorney. The news, broken by <em>Sputnik International</em>, comes 13 days after the arrest of Denis Dubnikov, who is being indicted on money laundering charges. Dubnikov is co-owner of the Eggchange and Coyote Crypto exchange platforms and was on a vacation to Mexico before he was denied entry to the country.</p>



<p>An earlier report <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/dubnikov-arrested-in-connecton-to-heist/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">claimed</a> Dubnikov was arrested for his connection to a 2018 cryptocurrency theft.</p>



<p>The arrest was pre-empted by blockchain analysis of ransomware payments received by the Ryuk group, which is <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-accuses-russian-of-money-laundering-for-ryuk-ransomware-gang-11636741333" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">estimated</a> to have taken in over $100 million in such payments last year. Having formed in 2018, Ryuk has been on the short list of cybersecurity targets since the group started attacking hospitals in 2019, demanding ransomware payments for the decryption of essential data and restoration of systems.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="519" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-1024x519.png" alt="" class="wp-image-934" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-1024x519.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-300x152.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-768x389.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Screenshot of the Eggchange cryptocurrency exchange operated by Dubnikov.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>According to Arkady Bukh, the accused’s U.S.-based lawyer, Dubnikov didn’t realize the cryptocurrency funds he had been receiving were in any way tied to ransomware payments. Furthermore, Dubnikov was assured he had been performing exchange operations within the bounds of Russian regulation, stating that he “had no knowledge or idea about the criminal acts of clients.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Mexico has not let (Dubnikov) enter the country,” Bukh told <em>Sputnik</em>. “The US intelligence services have put him on a plane to the Netherlands and sent him there having paid for his ticket. In other words, he was kidnapped in fact,” he said, adding that he believed the FBI was behind the arrest.</p>



<p>Because the US does not have an extradition agreement with Mexico, US law enforcement were unable to arrest Dubnikov on Mexican soil, choosing instead to re-route his destination away from Moscow and to a country with an extradition agreement: the Netherlands. It is not clear if Dubnikov knew the plane ticked he had was purchased by US law enforcement, who were waiting to arrest him upon landing in Amsterdam.</p>



<p>Dubnikov is the second Russian national apprehended internationally by US law enforcement for cryptocurrency-related crimes while on vacation. In 2017, BTC-E exchange founder Alexander Vinnik was <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50821547" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> while vacationing in Greece, wanted on similar charges of money laundering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/">Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</title>
		<link>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/</link>
					<comments>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 23 Sep 2021 18:35:57 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[bitcoin]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exchange]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[money laundering]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=831</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday added 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The U.S. Treasury Department on Tuesday <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/policy-issues/financial-sanctions/recent-actions/20210921" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">added</a> 24 new entries to its list of foreign-owned cryptocurrency addresses barred from engaging in business with companies operating in the country. Sanctions placed by the U.S. government primarily effect Suex, a Czechoslovakia-based over-the-counter cryptocurrency exchange <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">b</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-suex-september-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">lieved</a> to have handled hundreds of millions of dollars in cryptocurrency obtained from illicit sources.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="489" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-832" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-1024x489.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-300x143.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11-768x367.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/11.jpg 1418w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Suex employees at Suex office location at 12 Federation East Tower, Moscow City, Moscow</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The sanctions are the result of the Biden administration’s <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-to-target-crypto-ransomware-payments-with-sanctions-11631885336" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pledge</a> to disrupt the network of exchanges which process the conversion of cryptocurrency obtained via malware ransom payments. Biden had asked for Russia’s cooperation in dismantling the financial services support for ransomware groups like REvil, which was responsible for the Colonial Pipeline attack in May.</p>



<p>According to Paul Abbate, FBI deputy director, “there is no indication that the Russian government has taken action to crack down on ransomware actors,” prompting the U.S. to move to sanctions.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Great move today by the <a href="https://twitter.com/USTreasury?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">@USTreasury</a> to sanction a Suex, a Moscow-based crypto exchange, one of the top money laundering outlets for cybercrime in the world. <br><br>Actions like these are a key component in a more aggressive strategy against ransomware<a href="https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy">https://t.co/NYO1KENVgy</a> <a href="https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3">https://t.co/XYBBYF09F3</a></p>&mdash; Dmitri Alperovitch (@DAlperovitch) <a href="https://twitter.com/DAlperovitch/status/1440371668786896898?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 21, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Despite the initial praise by several in the cybersecurity industry, the Treasury Department’s move to selectively block crypto addresses also provoked negative response from Bitcoin and privacy advocates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="566" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-833" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1024x566.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-300x166.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-768x424.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1-1536x849.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1.jpg 1839w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>“Repeat after me: stop trying to use the financial system in order to prosecute crimes after the fact,” exclaimed computer scientist and professor Emin Gun Sirer in a <a href="https://twitter.com/el33th4xor/status/1439193943183351810" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">tweet</a>. “The root cause of ransomware attacks is the weak state of computer security, not the mechanism used for payment.”</p>



<p>The Suex website, though still functioning, is now stripped of its ability to utilize the Visa and Mastercard payment processors much of its business is reliant upon, effectively dismantling its ability to do business. The company’s <a href="https://suex.io/terms-of-use" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">terms and conditions</a> indicate it adheres to rather common AML and KYC standards, requiring provision of personal identification for transactions over $500 in value.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="539" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-834" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x539.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-300x158.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-768x404.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1536x808.jpg 1536w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3.jpg 2048w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Future sanctions are also expected to single out specific targets but the extent to which this measure will be employed for cryptocurrency addresses is not yet known.</p>



<p>In Nov. 2018, the Treasury dept. <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/sm556" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">blacklisted</a> two Bitcoin addresses belonging to Iranian nationals implicated in the laundering of millions in terrorist-designated funding.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/">U.S. Expands Crypto Address Blacklist in Fight Against Ransomware</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/u-s-expands-crypto-address-blacklist-in-fight-against-ransomware/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</title>
		<link>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 13 Sep 2021 10:06:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hitman]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=820</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 38-year-old Russian man was arrested on Sept. 8 for allegedly running an actual ‘hitman-for-hire’ service on the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/">Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 38-year-old Russian man was <a href="https://www.svoboda.org/a/sud-v-moskve-arestoval-podozrevaemogo-v-sozdanii-sayta-dlya-nayomnyh-ubiyts-v-darknete/31453709.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrested</a> on Sept. 8 for allegedly running an actual ‘hitman-for-hire’ service on the darknet which led to the deaths of at least two people. Sergei Magdanov was apprehended by law enforcement at the behest of a Moscow court in his home city of Izhevsk, accused of creating and running a darknet site where he accepted cryptocurrency and digital cash to arrange murder for his customers.</p>



<p>In addition to his site administration duties, authorities allege Magdanov also acted as assassin.</p>



<p>Magdanov’s takedown was the result of a multi-agency effort which included the Ministry of Internal Affairs and Investigative Committee of Russia, which uncovered what local media refers to as <a href="https://ren.tv/news/v-rossii/877666-politsiia-zaderzhala-podozrevaemogo-v-organizatsii-ubiistv-cherez-darknet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">especially grave crimes</a>. In addition to murder charges, Magdanov will face charges related to murder conspiracy as well as weapons and ammunition sales.</p>



<p>Magdanov was first identified by law enforcement as a <a href="https://ren.tv/news/kriminal/877875-zhertvoi-vladeltsa-magazina-ubiits-cherez-darknet-stal-narkodiler" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">potential suspect</a> in the murder of a young married couple last year, when a 25-year-old man and a 29-year-old-woman were found dead near a stream with their hands tied and mouths taped, shot execution style. The man, who had a criminal history tied to selling synthetic drugs online, was thought to be targeted due to his status as a drug dealer, possibly by rival dealers.</p>



<p>During a raid on his home and safehouse, authorities found Magdanov was in possession of around 500 bank cards, 1000 SIM cards, and “a large amount of cash.” Also seized was computer equipment, mobile phones, and electronic data carriers.</p>



<p>Most assassination or “hitman-for-hire” sites on the dark web have long been <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2020/03/04/technology/can-you-hire-a-hit-man-online.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">exposed as scams</a>. The majority of such sites are believed to be run by a single organization or individual who may be responsible for indirectly passing on tips about would-be customers to law enforcement. Sites like Magdanov’s &#8211; which authorities purport offered the real deal &#8211; remain an extremely rare finding.</p>



<p>As part of a Sept. 9 <a href="https://ren.tv/news/v-rossii/877854-sud-arestoval-na-2-mesiatsa-podozrevaemogo-v-ubiistvakh-cherez-darknet" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ruling</a>, Magdanov will be detained as a “preventative measure” for at least two months for his pending trial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/">Real Darknet Assassination Site Owner Captured in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/real-darknet-assassination-site-owner-captured-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:56:55 by W3 Total Cache
-->