<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>vendor bust &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/vendor-bust/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:53:01 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>vendor bust &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</title>
		<link>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/</link>
					<comments>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 29 Apr 2022 13:52:58 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hydra market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1449</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over one ton of drugs was seized in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over one ton of drugs was <a href="https://www.urdupoint.com/en/world/russian-police-say-caught-drug-gang-led-by-uk-1504121.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">seized</a> in Russia earlier this week as the result of an investigation into 26 individuals believed to have been operating a shop on the former Hydra darknet marketplace. The criminal group, led by Ukrainian nationals, organized the production of the drugs and their sale in Russia under the name “Murmur Shop,” which operated on Hydra between 2019 and 2021.</p>



<p>According to investigators, the group included 15 people from Ukraine, seven from Russia, two from Moldova, one from Tajikistan, and one from Belarus. While the leadership was based in Ukraine, Russian nationals were hired to help transport the drugs to <a href="https://aif.ru/society/law/v_mosgorsud_napravili_delo_mezhdunarodnoy_gruppy_iz_26_narkotorgovcev" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">more than 60 constituent entities</a> across the Russian Federation. Four clandestine drug laboratories in the Moscow, Vladimir and Ivanovo regions were also uncovered during the investigation.</p>



<p>“The leadership of the drug group and the management of its financial assets was carried out from the territory of Ukraine,” said Irina Volk, a spokeswoman for the Russian Ministry of Internal Affairs, on Thursday. “The recruitment of laboratory staff was also carried out there for the further dispatch to Russia. Applicants were forced to undergo polygraph tests,” she added.</p>



<p>In early April, Hydra’s servers were <a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">s</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ei</a><a href="https://www.cnbc.com/2022/04/05/darknet-hydra-market-site-seized-and-shut-down-doj-says.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">zed</a> in Germany as the result of a joint effort between German and US law enforcement, knocking the world’s biggest darknet market offline in the process. Days earlier, the US Department of Justice had filed sanctions against Hydra and an online money exchanger known to be associated with the market. On April 11<sup>th</sup>, the Meshchansky Court of Moscow arrested Dmitry Pavlov, one of the alleged founders of the online drug platform.</p>



<p>In January, a group of Russian nationals were <a href="https://www.gazeta.ru/social/news/2022/01/20/17168629.shtml" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sentenced</a> for their roles in importing cocaine from Argentina, some of which had been hidden at the Russian embassy in Buenos Aires. The group’s mastermind was sentenced to 18 years in a penal colony while other members received sentences between 13 and 17 years.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/">Group Behind Former Hydra Shop Arrested in Russia</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/group-behind-former-hydra-shop-arrested-in-russia/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</title>
		<link>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/</link>
					<comments>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 25 Mar 2022 12:37:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[empire market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[OVO_sweatshop]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1384</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee indicted on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A former Goldman Sachs employee <a href="https://www.nytimes.com/2022/03/24/nyregion/thomas-spieker-bitcoin-scheme.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">indicted</a> on laundering over $2.3 million in Bitcoin for various scamming operations also funded a well-known darknet market vendor specializing in ketamine, according to charges recently filed by New York federal prosecutors.</p>



<p>In addition to converting BTC into cash for carding scammers, Nigerian “catfishers” and an “eastern European crime syndicate,” Thomas Spieker, 42, allegedly <a href="https://www.dailymail.co.uk/news/article-10650791/New-York-man-42-indicted-running-2-3M-cash-Bitcoin-money-laundering-scheme-crooks.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">provided $38,000 in laundered funds</a> to two people behind the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> darknet market vendor moniker, Zashan Khan and Cosma Siekierski. The vendor maintained a <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/u/ovosweatshop" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">presence</a> on the <em>Dread</em> forum, racking up hundreds of positive reviews across multiple darknet markets during their 1-2 years in operation.</p>



<p>Investigators allege the <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> vendor name was later taken over by John Humphrey and Fidello Palermo, both 51, who operated it out of a facility in Rochester, New York. The duo were arrested during a trip to Brooklyn where authorities found they were carrying 1.7 kg of ketamine powder/crystals and 140 vials of liquid ketamine.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="554" height="251" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1385" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1.jpg 554w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-1-300x136.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 554px) 100vw, 554px" /></figure>



<p><em>John Humphrey, left, and Fidello Palermo, right, who allegedly assumed the popular New York ketamine vendor operation. Source: DailyMail.com</em></p>



<p>A total of seven people are being held in association with Spieker’s actions and face a large assortment of charges, ranging from conspiracy to commit money laundering to illegal drug charges.</p>



<p>According to his <a href="https://www.linkedin.com/in/thomas-spieker-60749062" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">LinkedIn profile</a>, Spieker was an Equity Derivates Specialist at Goldman Sachs from Feb 2001 to Mar 2003, founding a hip hop and club music promotion business named S!CK Productions in Nov 2010. His interest in music production and the club scene goes back to the year 2000.</p>



<p>The vendor name stems from a clothing line started by musician Drake, with ‘OVO’ standing for “October’s Very Own.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="718" height="495" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1386" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2.png 718w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-300x207.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 718px) 100vw, 718px" /></figure>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop vendor profile on the (now defunct) Empire Market. Source: The New York Times</em></p>



<p>Although Empire Market exit scammed in late August 2020, <em>OVO_sweatshop</em> was quick to set up replacement stores on White House Market and Dark Market within a matter of weeks. The quality of their operation apparently degraded over the following year, with customers complaining on <em>Dread</em> of receiving watered-down product and being victims of selective scamming by the vendor.</p>



<p><em>OVO_sweatshop</em> also provided pills listed as Xanax and MDMA that received widely varying reviews, although this product took a back seat to their more consistent ketamine-vending operations.</p>



<p>All seven parties arrested and facing trial have pled not guilty to the charges against them.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/">Top US Ketamine Vendor Had Ties to Ex-Wall Street Employee Accused of Money Laundering</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/top-us-ketamine-vendor-had-ties-to-ex-wall-street-employee-accused-of-money-laundering/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</title>
		<link>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/</link>
					<comments>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Feb 2022 09:41:18 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1313</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 57-year-old Kentucky woman will spend 15 months in prison for helping her son to launder proceeds from</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/">Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 57-year-old Kentucky woman will spend 15 months in prison for helping her son to launder proceeds from a <a href="/directory/listing/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> vending operation. Cara Leann Naber <a href="https://www.courier-journal.com/story/news/crime/2022/02/04/oldham-county-woman-sentenced-prison-laundering-sons-drug-money/6663021001/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">was sentenced</a> in front of a US District Judge on Wednesday for charges pertaining to conspiracy to launder drug trafficking proceeds and structuring bank transactions to evade federal cash transaction reporting requirements.</p>



<p>Her son, 22-year-old John Frank Naber, was <a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arres</a><a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">t</a><a href="https://www.wdrb.com/news/louisville-man-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web-sentenced-to-11-years-in/article_7ae68f12-5b32-11eb-ab39-47e74e584dd3.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ed</a> on drug trafficking charges in Feb 2019 and sentenced to 11 years in prison. Cara Naber’s <a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plea a</a><a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">gre</a><a href="https://www.oldhamera.com/content/goshen-woman-pleads-guilty-federal-money-laundering-charges" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ement</a> offered the following explanation of how she had helped her son obfuscate funds from drug purchases:</p>



<p>“<em>By depositing cash proceeds in both safety deposit boxes and in traditional bank accounts not in John Frank Naber III’s name, transferring money between various bank accounts to layer funds, and using drug proceeds to purchase Bitcoin, and by other means, defendants John Frank Naber II and Cara Leann Naber acted in concert to conceal or disguise the nature, the location, the source, the ownership, or the control of the proceeds of unlawful activity.”</em></p>



<p>The criminal complaint filed by prosecutors claims Cara Naber moved over $150,000 in drug sales proceeds between banks in 2018, attempting to create transactional layers to partially legitimize some of the funds. The attempt to launder the funds was quickly discovered after the arrest of her son.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="400" height="225" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1315" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.jpg 400w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1-300x169.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 400px) 100vw, 400px" /><figcaption><em>John Naber III mugshot. Source: wdrb.com</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>John Naber allegedly sold cocaine, meth, and marijuana-derived products not only over <a href="/directory/listing/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet markets</a> but via hand-delivered orders, as well. Prosecutors claim Naber’s best-selling product was “fake Adderall pills” which he would manufacturer from the home of his parents, with a pill press and an inert, orange powder.</p>



<p>The principal ingredient in the fake Adderall pills was methamphetamine, according to investigators, who found approximately 1,000 grams of the substance during the Feb 2019 raid on family property in Oldham County, Kentucky. Investigators also recovered a large quantity of cash, the seed phrase to a cryptocurrency wallet, premeasured and bagged amounts of MDMA, and a digital scale.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/">Money Laundering Mom Gets 15 Months</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/money-laundering-mom-gets-15-months/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</title>
		<link>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/</link>
					<comments>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 02 Feb 2022 11:05:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1303</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A recent court appearance by Kamil Balicki, a 32-year-old man living in Northern Ireland, shed some light on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/">Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A recent court <a href="https://www.northernirelandworld.com/news/people/dark-web-online-drugs-shop-linked-to-ballymena-address-court-told-3550893" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">appearance</a> by Kamil Balicki, a 32-year-old man living in Northern Ireland, shed some light on the takedown of one of the biggest independent darknet market operators in the UK. The native of Poland <a href="https://courtnewsni.co.uk/man-32-appears-at-court-in-ballymena-accused-of-attempting-to-import-heroin/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">attended</a> a remote hearing on Jan. 18<sup>th</sup> and was aided by a Polish interpreter. He is charged with attempting to import heroin and the possession of cocaine, amphetamine, and cannabis with the intent to supply, using a self-created shop on the dark web to do so.</p>



<p>Prosecutors allege Balicki began his career as a darknet market vendor in May 2020, operating his independent market from his Ballymena address up until January 17<sup>th</sup> of this year, when he was arrested.</p>



<p>Police were tipped off about Balicki’s operations in October 2020 after Border Force officers stopped two heat-sealed envelopes containing 123 grams of heroin from reaching his home address. The heroin was being imported from the Netherlands for local resale via his site on the dark web, according to “cyber-investigators” working the case.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">A &#39;DARK web&#39; online &#39;shopping site&#39; advertising heroin, cocaine and cannabis was allegedly linked to a property in Ballymena, a court in the town was told. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/CourtCorner?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#CourtCorner</a></p>&mdash; CourtNewsNI (@CourtNewsNI) <a href="https://twitter.com/CourtNewsNI/status/1488542144721731584?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">February 1, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Police described Balicki’s enterprise as an “online shopping site on the dark web which was openly advertising heroin, cocaine, as well as cannabis”. The site purported to have accumulated 270 “positive feedbacks” from supposed customers, suggesting it was fairly popular in the area.</p>



<p>Confiscated during his arrest were 40-50 grams of heroin, 30-40 grams of cocaine, and 30 grams of marijuana. Police also confiscated mixing bowls, an assortment of unidentified powders, electronic devices, and a large quantity of cash.</p>



<p>Balicki, a factory worker with no prior criminal record, was denied bail and will be remanded in custody in Maghaberry Prison until the case resumes on Feb. 10<sup>th</sup>.</p>



<p>Ballymena, in County Antrim, has appeared as the center of darknet market-related news in the past. In April 2017, a 14-year-old boy was <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arr</a><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">e</a><a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/uk-northern-ireland-39538330" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sted</a> in the town for attempting to buy a sub-machine gun and several thousand rounds of ammunition off the internet.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/">Independent Darknet Market Operator Busted in Northern Ireland</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/independent-darknet-market-operator-busted-in-northern-ireland/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Vendor Who Hid Drugs In Candles Sentenced to 13+ Years</title>
		<link>/vendor-who-hid-drugs-in-candles-sentenced-to-13-years/</link>
					<comments>/vendor-who-hid-drugs-in-candles-sentenced-to-13-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 12 Jan 2022 14:57:42 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1093</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A 26-year-old Arizona man was sentenced to 160 months in federal prison yesterday for selling crystal meth, cocaine,</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendor-who-hid-drugs-in-candles-sentenced-to-13-years/">Vendor Who Hid Drugs In Candles Sentenced to 13+ Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A 26-year-old Arizona man was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-sdfl/pr/dark-web-drug-trafficker-sentenced-160-months-federal-prison" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">sentenced</a> to 160 months in federal prison yesterday for selling crystal meth, cocaine, and fentanyl-laced Percocet pills on at least three darknet markets. Jose Rodolfo Barraza Flores was alleged by prosecutors to have sold these drugs, among others, between 2018 and 2020 on <a href="/directory/listing/white-house-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">White House Market</a>, Empire Market, and Yellow Brick Market.</p>



<p>According to a statement released by the US Justice Department, Barraza Flores used wax candles to hide the contents of his orders, placing a wrapped order in a candle and melting wax to conceal it within. The vendor is said to have packaged the orders from an Arizona trailer.</p>



<p>Barraza Flores was apprehended by authorities at home in December 2020 and pleaded guilty to the charges against him in October of last year. The charges were filed from a district court in Florida, a state where many of the vendor’s suspected customers were located and that has been in the grips of an <a href="https://www.orlandosentinel.com/news/os-ne-opioid-deaths-soar-central-florida-20211130-adaeopbpnbeixns72rewhco2pi-story.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">epidemic of fentanyl overdoses</a>.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Most common fentapill (a pill laced with fentanyl) looks like a blue 30-milligram dose of oxycodone with the label M-30. it’s also common to find fentapills that look like Xanax, Hydrocodone, or Percocet. <a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/onepillcankill?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#onepillcankill</a> <br>If you need pain medicine or anxiety please see your doc!</p>&mdash; <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1f8-1f1f4.png" alt="🇸🇴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />C.HEAL.A<img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1f8-1f1f4.png" alt="🇸🇴" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> (@k_6og) <a href="https://twitter.com/k_6og/status/1419857023601102870?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">July 27, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Pills laced with fentanyl, which also include fake Xanax and Adderall pills, have become an increasing medical and social issue across much of the US, leading to <a href="https://twitter.com/Jaffe8Jaffe/status/1469423771001884672" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">severe cases of addiction</a> and numerous deaths attributed to accidental overdose. Drug overdose deaths in the US hit an all-time high in 2020 according to a <a href="https://www.hsph.harvard.edu/news/hsph-in-the-news/drug-overdose-deaths-hit-record-high/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">study</a> performed by Harvard University.</p>



<p>Barraza Flores <a href="https://ecorp.azcc.gov/BusinessSearch/BusinessInfo?entityNumber=23069745" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">registered</a> a company for a rap group named <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UClBbVNLAzmOZsuXrIklBlyQ" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Elevadoz</a> in June 2020, naming himself as ‘member and manager.’</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendor-who-hid-drugs-in-candles-sentenced-to-13-years/">Vendor Who Hid Drugs In Candles Sentenced to 13+ Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/vendor-who-hid-drugs-in-candles-sentenced-to-13-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Cabaret Dancer Part of Multimillion Dollar Vendor Trio</title>
		<link>/cabaret-dancer-part-of-multimillion-dollar-vendor-trio/</link>
					<comments>/cabaret-dancer-part-of-multimillion-dollar-vendor-trio/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 02 Jan 2022 14:54:23 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[australia]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1053</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>An Australian trio is being accused of using darknet markets to sell approximately $25,000 a day in drugs</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cabaret-dancer-part-of-multimillion-dollar-vendor-trio/">Cabaret Dancer Part of Multimillion Dollar Vendor Trio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>An Australian trio is being accused of using darknet markets to sell approximately $25,000 a day in drugs to customers throughout their country. Erin Gold (32), Thomas Booker (27) and Ryan Suri-Tucker (24) are believed by prosecutors to be the team behind the <em>Underline Cost</em> vendor moniker. Under that name, authorities allege the trio arranged for the sale of millions of dollars of several different drugs, including cocaine, MDMA, marijuana, and LSD.</p>



<p>The trio came under suspicion after a package from Luxembourg containing 8,000 LSD tabs destined for an associated address was seized by customs in southern Australia. A phone number on the package was later found to be registered to a mailbox through which Booker regularly sent packages of drugs destined for the dark web. Police also made purchases from listings offered by <em>Underline Cost</em> and matched fingerprints found on the packages to two of the individuals.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="576" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1-1024x576.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1056" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1-1024x576.jpg 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1-300x169.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1-768x432.jpg 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1.jpg 1280w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Erin Gold in a photo promoting her burlesque troupe. Source: Adelaide Now</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>Both Gold and Booker seemed to be rather public figures in Adelaide, posing for multiple pictures with each other across the years; some of which <a href="https://amp.adelaidenow.com.au/coronavirus/pubs-open-but-dday-looms-for-hoteliers/news-story/e52a49f2e2279b5cef1e3c5bf8373a3c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">appeared</a> in the same publication that broke the story of their arrest, over a year later. Gold had a particularly public career as part of a burlesque dancer group based out of the area, <a href="https://www.perthnow.com.au/news/sa/adelaide-cabaret-fringe-program-launch-ng-26220f8cb3b50280659f5e22a716fb0a" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">performing regularly</a> at the Adelaide Cabaret Fringe.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="420" height="293" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1057" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/2.png 420w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/2-300x209.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 420px) 100vw, 420px" /><figcaption><em>Booker, left, and Gold, right, posing for a Dec. 2020 local news article. Source: Adelaide Now</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The two male suspects &#8211; Booker and Suri-Tucker &#8211; were first arrested in November while “sitting at a desk piled with drugs,” in the middle of processing orders for their vendor operation, which was based out of a property in the King’s Park region of Adelaide. Gold was arrested while at work during her primary job as an accountant. Booker is said to have worked as a police officer until 2016.</p>



<p>In addition to large stashes of different drugs, police also confiscated $350,000 in cash from the three, later locating an additional $460,000 in a trustee lockbox.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/cabaret-dancer-part-of-multimillion-dollar-vendor-trio/">Cabaret Dancer Part of Multimillion Dollar Vendor Trio</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/cabaret-dancer-part-of-multimillion-dollar-vendor-trio/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</title>
		<link>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/</link>
					<comments>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 17:21:24 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darkmarket]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=904</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the largest darknet market vendor sting operations in recent history saw the arrest of 150 vendors</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/">DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the largest darknet market vendor sting operations in recent history saw the arrest of 150 vendors associated with the now-defunct DarkMarket on Monday, attracting <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/coordinated-bust-of-dark-web-dealers-yields-150-arrests-in-u-s-europe-11635263760" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">massive attention</a> from the world’s biggest news media outlets. The <a href="https://www.dw.com/en/europol-investigation-busts-150-high-value-darknet-vendors/a-59625287" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">internationally-coordinated raid</a>, which involved law enforcement efforts from nine countries, also netted around 234 kilograms in drugs, 45 guns, and more than $31.6 million in cash.</p>



<p>Dubbed ‘Operation Dark Huntor,’ the raid attracted media attention globally, hitting front pages of newspapers in the affected countries, which include the US, UK, Germany, Australia, Bulgaria, France, Italy, the Netherlands, and Switzerland. Out of these countries, the US saw the most arrests at 65, followed by 47 in Germany and 24 in the UK. One of the biggest distribution hubs identified in the operation was said to be located in Houston, Texas.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">One of&#39;biggest global crackdowns&#39;on dark web:<br>DarkHunTOR operation launched after the Jan 2021 dismantling by <img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f1e9-1f1ea.png" alt="🇩🇪" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" /> of DarkMarket,one of the leading cyber black marketplaces<br><br>150 arrests<br>UK:65<br>Germany:47<br>UK:24<br>Italy:4<br>Netherlands:4<br>Several&quot;high-value targets&quot;<a href="https://t.co/wXn4rjIqaU">https://t.co/wXn4rjIqaU</a></p>&mdash; Mila (@Milatrud11) <a href="https://twitter.com/Milatrud11/status/1453070132406886416?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 26, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>A well-produced <a href="https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=VUhzK2cY_PY" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">video</a> posted on the FBI’s official YouTube account claims to contain footage of arrests related to the operation while offering a stern warning to darknet market vendors.</p>



<p>“The FBI’s Joint Criminal Opioid and Darknet Enforcement (JCODE) team was established in 2018 to peel back perceived anonymity of dark web drug dealers, leading to arrests like these,” reads text in the video as scenes depicting arrests unfold. “Targets in JCODE enforcement operations buys and sell illegal drugs on dark web markets…</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="671" height="321" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-906" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5.jpg 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-5-300x144.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /></figure>



<p><em>Screenshot from FBI YouTube video explaining US authority actions in Monday’s raid.</em></p>



<p>DarkMarket, which was <a href="https://www.dw.com/en/largest-illegal-darknet-marketplace-darkmarket-taken-offline/a-56200737" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">taken offline in January</a> after its operator was arrested in Germany, was considered to be “the biggest darknet market” at the time. The market’s takedown was also the result of a months-long multi-national criminal investigation, involving law enforcement from seven countries, coordinated by the DEA, FBI, and Europol. The 150 vendors arrested in yesterday’s raid represent roughly 6% of the 2,400 total vendors at DarkMarket at the time of its closure.</p>



<p>Among the approximately 516 pounds of drugs confiscated by authorities during the raid were 25,000 ecstasy pills and thousands of pills containing amphetamine (Adderall), alprazolam (Xanax), and oxycodone (OxyContin). A US deputy attorney general stated that over 90% of confiscated pills in the country during the raid contained “counterfeit opioids,” such as fentanyl.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/">DarkMarket Vendor Takedown Nets 150 Arrests, Covered by Global Media</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darkmarket-vendor-takedown-nets-150-arrests-covered-by-global-media/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</title>
		<link>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/</link>
					<comments>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 20 Oct 2021 20:00:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=895</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A federal judge ruled on Monday that a 30-year-old Michigan man will spend seven years behind bars for</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/">US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A federal judge <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdpa/pr/judge-sentences-michigan-man-7-years-prison-hacking-upmc-hr-databases-and-stealing" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ruled</a> on Monday that a 30-year-old Michigan man will spend seven years behind bars for stealing personal information from 65,000 healthcare workers and selling it on the darknet. Justin Sean Johnson, who went by the vendor names “TheDearthStar” and “DearthyStar”, was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-wdpa/pr/michigan-man-arrested-2014-hack-upmc-hr-databases-and-theft-employees-personal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> in June 2020 on charges of conspiracy, wire fraud and aggravated identity theft stemming from the 2014 hack of University of Pittsburgh Medical Center (UPMC). He plead guilty to those charges.</p>



<p>During several database breaches starting in late 2013 and continuing through early 2014, Johnson hacked into the UPMC databases several times undetected, collecting tens of thousands of records containing names, Social Security numbers, addresses and salary information. He then packaged the data for sale on the AlphaBay and Evolution markets where it was quickly purchased and used to file thousands of fraudulent tax returns.</p>



<p>Much of the stolen personal information was collected from UPMC employee W2 tax forms in quick bursts over a short period in January and February 2014.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="666" height="272" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-897" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.jpg 666w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-300x123.jpg 300w" sizes="(max-width: 666px) 100vw, 666px" /><figcaption><em>TheDearthyStar item listing on AlphaBay in 2014. Source: Bleeping Computer</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In all, the Johnson’s customers managed to collect approximately $1.7 million in fraudulent tax refunds from the IRS. Most of this money was used to purchase Amazon gift cards that were spent on products sent to Venezuela through a Miami-based reshipping company.</p>



<p>The UPMC is Pennsylvania’s largest healthcare provider, employing close to 90,000 workers; all of which were thought to be at least partly affected by the breach.</p>



<p>Between 2014 and 2017, Johnson also stole 90,000 sets of personal information from other sources, which was then also sold on various darknet forums for the purposes of identity theft or bank fraud.</p>



<p>He was sentenced on Monday to 60 months in prison for conspiracy to defraud the United States and 24 months for aggravated identity theft.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/">US Tax Data Vendor on Evolution and AlphaBay Sentenced to 7 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/us-tax-data-vendor-on-evolution-and-alphabay-sentenced-to-7-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Master Coupon Forger Sentenced to 12 Years</title>
		<link>/master-coupon-forger-sentenced-to-12-years/</link>
					<comments>/master-coupon-forger-sentenced-to-12-years/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 16 Sep 2021 10:46:07 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=824</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Virginia woman will spend 12 years behind bars for masterminding one of the biggest coupon frauds ever</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/master-coupon-forger-sentenced-to-12-years/">Master Coupon Forger Sentenced to 12 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A Virginia woman will spend 12 years behind bars for masterminding one of the biggest coupon frauds ever investigated by law enforcement.</p>



<p>Under the moniker “MasterChef,” Lori Ann Talens, 41, allegedly ran a large-scale coupon forgery operation between 2018 and 2020, accepting payments for her high-quality fakes in the form of Bitcoin and PayPal. Talens’ forgeries were described as nearly perfect imitations, complete with glossy paper, corporate logos and working barcodes.</p>



<p>The scam masterminded by Talens is estimated to have caused $31.8 million in damages to over 100 victims; most of which are businesses that were the subject of the coupon fraud.</p>



<p>An avid coupon collector for years prior, Talens first joined coupon collector groups on Facebook where she began to develop her forgery skills. She was eventually informed about the existence of the darknet by a trusted group member and convinced to move her sales operations there, lured by the idea of expanding business.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="800" height="500" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-826" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1.jpg 800w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-300x188.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-768x480.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 800px) 100vw, 800px" /></figure>



<p><em>Photo of Lori Ann Talens. Source: David B. Hollingsworth</em></p>



<p>In a letter to the court, Talens <a href="https://www.pilotonline.com/news/crime/vp-nw-talens-sentencing-20210915-gs5vsagv3zcklkxuexi4p6rwya-story.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">admitted</a> to being “blinded by (her) own greed.” Her husband, Pacifico Talens Jr., was sentenced in August to seven years and three months for his contribution the scam.</p>



<p>While searching a computer seized during a raid on the couples’ home, investigators found 13,000 templates for “separate and distinct counterfeit coupon designs.” Cross-referencing the templates with known counterfeit coupons revealed that approximately $31.82 million worth of damage had been done to retailers and manufacturers because of the scam.</p>



<p>Also obtained during the seizure was $1 million in fake coupons, waiting to be mailed.</p>



<p>Prosecutors described the operation as “one of the biggest counterfeit coupon schemes in history” in sentencing documents, stating that Talens utilized “the internet, social media, and expertise she learned from her experience in the retail world” to perfect her craft.</p>



<p>“Her skill was such that the coupons she created were virtually indistinguishable from genuine coupons and took counterfeit coupon experts to positively confirm them as counterfeit,” prosecutors added.</p>



<p>Talens allegedly employed her husband Pacifico as a delivery driver who would often drive orders of coupons to postal centers at her behest. He would also test out the quality of the forged coupons on local franchises to make sure they were suitable for use.</p>



<p>Both Pacifico and Lori Ann Talens had already plead guilty to unrelated mail fraud charges in April after they were accused of abusing food stamp benefits.</p>



<p>Per court ruling, the couple will have to pay back a minimum $500 per month in restitution until the entire $31.8 million in damages has been paid off.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/master-coupon-forger-sentenced-to-12-years/">Master Coupon Forger Sentenced to 12 Years</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/master-coupon-forger-sentenced-to-12-years/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Empire and Wall Street Market Vendor Held Since 2019 Pleads Guilty</title>
		<link>/empire-and-wall-street-market-vendor-held-since-2019-pleads-guilty/</link>
					<comments>/empire-and-wall-street-market-vendor-held-since-2019-pleads-guilty/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 10 Sep 2021 10:54:48 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=818</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A former darknet market vendor in the U.S. changed his plea to guilty yesterday nearly two years after</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-and-wall-street-market-vendor-held-since-2019-pleads-guilty/">Empire and Wall Street Market Vendor Held Since 2019 Pleads Guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A former darknet market vendor in the U.S. changed his plea to guilty yesterday nearly two years after being busted for his dealings on Empire Market and Wall Street Market. According to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-edny/pr/dark-web-narcotics-traffickers-plead-guilty-conspiracy-distribute-illegal-drugs" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">federal prosecutors</a>, Gilberto Melgarejo – along with his partner Brooke Gray – operated vendor accounts under the name “THEQUEENSHIVE” which they used to sell a variety of narcotics, referring to the products in their listings as “The Queen’s Honey.” Gray entered a guilty plea of her own on Aug. 10, 2021.</p>



<p>Among the items sold by the pair between March and September 2019 were meth, fentanyl, heroin, LSD and ecstasy, which they marketed as “the highest quality product at the best price on the market.” In all, around 90 orders were processed under the moniker “THEQUEENSHIVE”, several of them going to undercover DEA agents.</p>



<p>Vendor operations took place in a non-descript apartment building in Albuquerque, New Mexico, where market orders were packaged and readied for delivery by the pair, who are both in their 20s. Neighbors <a href="https://www.krqe.com/news/crime/feds-bust-pair-accused-of-selling-drugs-on-the-dark-web/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">interviewed</a> by local media at the time said they never noticed anything out of the ordinary, other than Melgaro’s apartment seemed to have “a lot of activity.”</p>



<p>Bitcoin obtained from the vendor sales was then sold for PayPal cash handled by a fake account which investigators traced back to Melgarejo. On two occasions, traffic cameras caught Melgarejo’s vehicle headed to postal counters at local gas stations to distribute customer orders. In yesterday’s <a href="https://www.dea.gov/press-releases/2021/09/09/dark-web-narcotics-traffickers-plead-guilty-conspiracy-distribute-illegal" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">press release</a>, the DEA referred to their decision to use local USPS counters as “a futile effort to evade detection.”</p>



<p>By Nov. 9, 2019, prosecutors had compiled enough evidence against the duo to file a criminal <a href="https://www.courtlistener.com/docket/16574688/united-states-v-melgarejo/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">complaint</a>, leading to their arrest the following week.</p>



<p>Melgarejo faces a maximum punishment of a lifetime prison sentence – an outcome possibly hoped to be avoided with yesterday’s plea change.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/empire-and-wall-street-market-vendor-held-since-2019-pleads-guilty/">Empire and Wall Street Market Vendor Held Since 2019 Pleads Guilty</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/empire-and-wall-street-market-vendor-held-since-2019-pleads-guilty/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:56:11 by W3 Total Cache
-->