<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>ransomware &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/ransomware/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 18:02:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>ransomware &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</title>
		<link>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/</link>
					<comments>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 14 Nov 2021 18:02:43 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[russia]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=932</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A Russian man believed to be operating cryptocurrency exchanges associated with the laundering of ransomware proceeds was “practically</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/">Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A Russian man believed to be operating cryptocurrency exchanges associated with the laundering of ransomware proceeds was “<a href="https://sputniknews.com/20211113/russias-dubnikov-practically-kidnapped-by-fbi-in-mexico-sent-to-amsterdam---attorney-1090699499.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">practically kidnapped</a>” by the United States after landing in the Netherlands, according to his attorney. The news, broken by <em>Sputnik International</em>, comes 13 days after the arrest of Denis Dubnikov, who is being indicted on money laundering charges. Dubnikov is co-owner of the Eggchange and Coyote Crypto exchange platforms and was on a vacation to Mexico before he was denied entry to the country.</p>



<p>An earlier report <a href="https://www.cryptopolitan.com/dubnikov-arrested-in-connecton-to-heist/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">claimed</a> Dubnikov was arrested for his connection to a 2018 cryptocurrency theft.</p>



<p>The arrest was pre-empted by blockchain analysis of ransomware payments received by the Ryuk group, which is <a href="https://www.wsj.com/articles/u-s-accuses-russian-of-money-laundering-for-ryuk-ransomware-gang-11636741333" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">estimated</a> to have taken in over $100 million in such payments last year. Having formed in 2018, Ryuk has been on the short list of cybersecurity targets since the group started attacking hospitals in 2019, demanding ransomware payments for the decryption of essential data and restoration of systems.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img width="1024" height="519" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-1024x519.png" alt="" class="wp-image-934" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-1024x519.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-300x152.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2-768x389.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-2.png 1080w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption><em>Screenshot of the Eggchange cryptocurrency exchange operated by Dubnikov.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>According to Arkady Bukh, the accused’s U.S.-based lawyer, Dubnikov didn’t realize the cryptocurrency funds he had been receiving were in any way tied to ransomware payments. Furthermore, Dubnikov was assured he had been performing exchange operations within the bounds of Russian regulation, stating that he “had no knowledge or idea about the criminal acts of clients.”</p>



<p>&#8220;Mexico has not let (Dubnikov) enter the country,” Bukh told <em>Sputnik</em>. “The US intelligence services have put him on a plane to the Netherlands and sent him there having paid for his ticket. In other words, he was kidnapped in fact,” he said, adding that he believed the FBI was behind the arrest.</p>



<p>Because the US does not have an extradition agreement with Mexico, US law enforcement were unable to arrest Dubnikov on Mexican soil, choosing instead to re-route his destination away from Moscow and to a country with an extradition agreement: the Netherlands. It is not clear if Dubnikov knew the plane ticked he had was purchased by US law enforcement, who were waiting to arrest him upon landing in Amsterdam.</p>



<p>Dubnikov is the second Russian national apprehended internationally by US law enforcement for cryptocurrency-related crimes while on vacation. In 2017, BTC-E exchange founder Alexander Vinnik was <a href="https://www.bbc.com/news/world-europe-50821547" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">arrested</a> while vacationing in Greece, wanted on similar charges of money laundering.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/">Crypto Exchange Operator “Kidnapped” by FBI</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/crypto-exchange-operator-kidnapped-by-fbi/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>U.S. Blacklists More Crypto Addresses, Places $10M Reward for REvil Info</title>
		<link>/u-s-blacklists-more-crypto-addresses-places-10m-reward-for-revil-info/</link>
					<comments>/u-s-blacklists-more-crypto-addresses-places-10m-reward-for-revil-info/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 10 Nov 2021 15:41:27 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chatex]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ransomware]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=926</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Another cryptocurrency exchange identified as processing millions in ransomware payments was sanctioned by the U.S. Treasury Department on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-blacklists-more-crypto-addresses-places-10m-reward-for-revil-info/">U.S. Blacklists More Crypto Addresses, Places $10M Reward for REvil Info</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Another cryptocurrency exchange identified as processing millions in ransomware payments was <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0471" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sanctioned</a> by the U.S. Treasury Department on Monday, resulting in the blacklisting of 59 cryptocurrency addresses known to be involved in such transactions. The action was taken after blockchain forensics experts at Chainalysis managed to <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/ofac-sanction-chatex-revil-sodinokibi-november-2021" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">trace ransomware payments</a> through addresses known to be associated with the exchange.</p>



<p>Further research by Chainalysis demonstrates that Chatex had processed around $77.5 million in Bitcoin (BTC) since its inception in September 2018, with at least $17 million coming from “illicit sources” such as the Hydra darknet marketplace.</p>



<p>A FinCEN Ransomware Advisory update included an <a href="https://home.treasury.gov/news/press-releases/jy0471" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">announcement</a> from the Department of State of a reward up to $10,000,000 “for information leading to the identification or location of any individual(s) who hold a key leadership position in the Sodinokibi/REvil ransomware variant transnational organized crime group.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr"><img src="https://s.w.org/images/core/emoji/13.1.0/72x72/1f622.png" alt="😢" class="wp-smiley" style="height: 1em; max-height: 1em;" />It&#39;s been a joyful ride&#8230; <br><br>Thanks to every member of the Chatex Community. We truly appreciate your trust and support.</p>&mdash; Chatex (@Chatex_bot) <a href="https://twitter.com/Chatex_bot/status/1458076229601464325?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 9, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“Ransomware groups and criminal organizations have targeted American businesses and public institutions of all sizes and across sectors, seeking to undermine the backbone of our economy,” said Deputy Secretary of the Treasury Wally Adeyemo in a press release. Two cybercriminals, one Russian and one Ukrainian, were also sanctioned for their positions in setting up ransomware attacks on U.S. companies.</p>



<p>Among yesterday’s sanctioned crypto addresses are exchange addresses for Bitcoin, Ethereum Bitcoin Cash, USDT, XRP, Litecoin, Dash and Monero. Per order of the sanction, businesses and individuals operating under U.S. law are forbidden from transacting with the listed addresses.</p>



<p>The owner of Chatex, Egor Petukhovsky, is also the owner of Suex, the first crypto exchange to be <a href="https://www.coindesk.com/business/2021/09/24/egor-petukhovsky-ceo-of-us-sanctioned-suex-says-he-will-go-to-court/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">sanctioned</a> by the Treasury department in September. As a result of the sanction, 25 crypto addresses were blacklisted, most consisting of exchange deposit addresses.</p>



<p>Before their <a href="https://chatex.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">website</a> was recently changed, Chatex described itself as “the second largest crypto wallet and p2p exchange in-app platform for Telegram.” They also mentioned that they had recently become a “full-fledged cryptobank,” offering an array of cryptocurrency-related cashout services. The company completed a <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/currencies/chatex/ico/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">token sale</a> in September in which $40,000 was raised, and was still in the process of raising additional funds at the time of the sanction.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/u-s-blacklists-more-crypto-addresses-places-10m-reward-for-revil-info/">U.S. Blacklists More Crypto Addresses, Places $10M Reward for REvil Info</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/u-s-blacklists-more-crypto-addresses-places-10m-reward-for-revil-info/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>REvil Ransomware Network Dealt Fatal Blow</title>
		<link>/revil-ransomware-network-dealt-fatal-blow/</link>
					<comments>/revil-ransomware-network-dealt-fatal-blow/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 15 Jul 2021 09:39:33 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyberattack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[ransomware]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[revil]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=687</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Was it Putin, the U.S., or rivals that took down what is likely to be the most well-known</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revil-ransomware-network-dealt-fatal-blow/">REvil Ransomware Network Dealt Fatal Blow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Was it Putin, the U.S., or rivals that took down what is likely to be the most well-known ransomware group of all-time? Or was the time for REvil to exit the stage just right?</em></p>



<p>The notorious REvil ransomware network, allegedly responsible for over 360 ransomware attacks during the last two years, had its <a href="https://www.govinfosecurity.com/revils-infrastructure-goes-offline-a-17061" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">online presence removed completely</a> yesterday, through actions and actors that are completely unknown.</p>



<p>The components taken down from the dark web include REvil’s portals for data leaks, extortion attempts and resulting payments. It also includes the public-facing centerpiece for REvil, the <em>Happy Blog</em> website. <em>Happy Blog</em> is where REvil posted the latest details of their successful efforts, frequently bragging about their most recent exploits and issuing threats to potential future victims.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1013" height="305" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-689" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1.png 1013w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-300x90.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/1-768x231.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 1013px) 100vw, 1013px" /><figcaption>Happy Blog screenshot courtesy of GovInfoSecurity.</figcaption></figure>



<p>In one of the last posts on <em>Happy Blog</em>, REvil claimed to have <a href="https://www.bloomberg.com/news/articles/2021-07-10/kaseya-failed-to-address-security-before-hack-ex-employees-say" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">infected over a million systems</a> belonging to international IT vendor Kaseya Ltd. In the post, REvil asks for a whopping $70 million ransom &#8211; payable in Bitcoin &#8211; in exchange for a “publicly decryptor (sp.) that decrypts files of all victims.”</p>



<p>After a meeting with Russian President Putin on July 9, U.S. President Biden <a href="https://twitter.com/martinmatishak/status/1413572561527574528/photo/1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">stated</a> that a line of communication had been opened between the two countries that would be dedicated to cyberattack-related affairs.</p>



<p>“I made it very clear to him that the United States expects when a ransomware operation is coming from his soil, even though it&#8217;s not sponsored by the state, we expect them to act if we give them enough information to act on who that is,&#8221; said Biden.</p>



<p>It is not known if Biden’s meeting with Putin contributed to the sudden disappearance of REvil’s presence on the darknet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="443" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2-1024x443.png" alt="" class="wp-image-690" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2-1024x443.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2-300x130.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2-768x332.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/07/2.png 1312w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>The result of visiting the former URL of Happy Blog, REvil’s primary darknet portal.</figcaption></figure>



<p>Security researchers note that malware/ransom operations like REvil often disband and re-appear under a new name to escape an increasingly negative reputation.</p>



<p>As almost no information about what caused the knockout is available, it is possible that the individuals behind the REvil banner have not been taken into custody and will simply re-emerge when the moment is right.</p>



<p>Next time, however, the light exposed on their movements will likely be all the brighter, as the internationally-coordinated crackdown on ransomware groups continues.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/revil-ransomware-network-dealt-fatal-blow/">REvil Ransomware Network Dealt Fatal Blow</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/revil-ransomware-network-dealt-fatal-blow/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:13:52 by W3 Total Cache
-->