<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Drug User Liberation Front &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/drug-user-liberation-front/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:50:16 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>Drug User Liberation Front &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</title>
		<link>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/</link>
					<comments>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 14 Mar 2022 11:50:13 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[canada]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Drug User Liberation Front]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1373</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A pair of Vancouver residents are publicly raising funds to buy drugs from the dark web with the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/">Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A pair of Vancouver residents are publicly raising funds to <a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">buy drugs fro</a><a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">m the</a><a href="https://www.ctvnews.ca/canada/drugs-the-dark-web-and-distributing-safe-supply-in-hopes-of-saving-lives-1.5817880" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"> dark web</a> with the intention of reducing the shocking number of overdose fatalities that is plaguing their city. Jeremy Kalicum, 26, and Eris Nyx, 31, believe that they can introduce an &#8220;accessible, reliable and safe&#8221; way for addicts to get their drugs by testing products purchased from the darknet and then distributing them to those most in need, reducing overdoses in the process.</p>



<p>The two founded the Drug User Liberation Front (DULF) in response to personally witnessing the growing epidemic of drug deaths in their neighborhood. Though seemingly shocking, DULF’s activities are generally seen as positive and are even encouraged by the local community.</p>



<p>Kalicum and Nyx stated that they only use Canada-based darknet markets to procure their substances &#8211; which include methamphetamine, heroin, and cocaine &#8211; testing them to ensure they are satisfactorily pure and do not contain lethal adulterants such as fentanyl or its analogs.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image"><img/></figure>



<p><em>Not legal, but close &#8212; and pure. Tested and repackaged methamphetamine bought from a darknet market to be distributed by DULF. Source: CTV News</em></p>



<p>The Canadian government created the <a href="https://www.canada.ca/en/health-canada/services/opioids/responding-canada-opioid-crisis/safer-supply.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Safer Supply program</a> as a way of “addressing Canada’s overdose crisis,” recognizing that the problem could not be solved through mere abolition of drug use. The program is independently administered through a network of registered providers, like Nyx and Kalicum. Some programs require a diagnosis of substance abuse disorder for individuals to participate; others do not.</p>



<p>Drugs are provided by DULF only every so often (usually at rallies) and to those that have registered with the Vancouver Area Network of Drug Users (VANDU).</p>



<p>As far as the legality of their operation is concerned, Kalicum and Nyx realize what they are doing is illegal but hope to soon make inroads with the government to legitimize its status.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">&quot;Groups like DULF and VANDU understand better than governments do&quot; &#8211; Guy Felicella.<br><br>&quot;They’re giving people the substances they want along with information about what they’re consuming. <br><br>&quot;They’ve empowered substance users to make real, informed choices.&quot;<a href="https://t.co/IVAsTOsWTU">https://t.co/IVAsTOsWTU</a></p>&mdash; PHS (@PHScss) <a href="https://twitter.com/PHScss/status/1500565639093792778?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 6, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>&#8220;We have submitted a very well researched request to the federal government asking for exemptions to the Controlled Drugs and Substances Act to continue to act as a consumer protection initiative,” Nix said in an interview with reporters from <em>CTV News</em>. Though they have yet to receive an official response from the capitol, they are undeterred in their mission, willing to face whatever consequences it might entail.</p>



<p>“<em>The one thing we know is if people get drugs that are labelled &#8211; that have predictable content, and they know precisely what they are taking &#8211; then they will not die.” </em>– Eris Nyx, Drug User Liberation Front</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/">Canadian Duo Turns to Darknet Markets to Provide Local Addicts with Safer Supply</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/canadian-duo-turns-to-darknet-markets-to-provide-local-addicts-with-safer-supply/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:11:46 by W3 Total Cache
-->