<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>yellowbrick market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/yellowbrick-market/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 09:05:45 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>yellowbrick market &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Ex Pharmacy Tech Admits to Selling Prescriptions on the Darknet</title>
		<link>/ex-pharmacy-tech-admits-to-selling-prescriptions-on-the-darknet/</link>
					<comments>/ex-pharmacy-tech-admits-to-selling-prescriptions-on-the-darknet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Thu, 05 Aug 2021 09:05:41 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[vendor bust]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[yellowbrick market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=740</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The pill vendor’s career only lasted seven months before it was ended by a traffic camera. A former</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ex-pharmacy-tech-admits-to-selling-prescriptions-on-the-darknet/">Ex Pharmacy Tech Admits to Selling Prescriptions on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>The pill vendor’s career only lasted seven months before it was ended by a traffic camera.</em></p>



<p>A former Yellow Brick market vendor <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-edva/pr/darknet-drug-vendor-pleads-guilty-distributing-illicit-prescription-drugs" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">plead guilty</a> yesterday to charges related to the distribution of controlled substances. The U.S. Attorney’s Office for the Eastern District of Virginia alleges that Cullen Roberts, a 23-year-old ex-pharmacy technician, sold prescription opiates and benzodiazepines under the account name “Pillpusher” on the darknet, from April through October 2020.</p>



<p>Prosecutors allege that Roberts shipped packages containing prescription narcotics to Yellow Brick customers from a local post office in Georgia to customers located throughout the United States. Among the drugs listed by Pillpusher at Yellow Brick were Xanax, Tramadol, and oxymorphone, a high-power opioid that he described as “the closest you will get to heaven.”</p>



<p>The FBI had been investigating Roberts as early as July 2020, less than four months into his career as a vendor. Unbeknownst to him, orders he filled as Pillpusher were also sent to undercover agents, which were then used to track him to his base of operations.</p>



<p>While wanted by the FBI, the license plate of Roberts’ car was <a href="https://www.cbs46.com/news/metro-atlanta-city-camera-helps-nab-man-wanted-by-the-fbi/article_ec585d68-4153-11eb-877f-8b5f3309252e.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">pinged by an Atlanta city traffic camera</a>, which alerted Atlanta police to his location. Police officers then performed a traffic stop and managed to arrest Roberts, who had also been wanted on separate charges of terroristic threatening.</p>



<p>A raid on Roberts’ home conducted shortly afterward found 100 oxycodone pills, 50 oxymorphone pills, and 10 Xanax pills. His arrest was <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-edva/pr/darknet-drug-vendor-arrested-distributing-illicit-prescription-drugs" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">announced</a> by the Department of Justice on Dec. 2, 2020.</p>



<p>According to a local news publication, Roberts was <a href="https://www.ajc.com/news/fbi-arrests-duluth-man-accused-of-selling-opioids-on-the-darknet/H3GBDL7MA5COTMO5ZPUJ4XY3BA/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">employed by CVS</a>, a nationwide pharmacy, up until his pharmacy tech license expired in June 2019. It is not known if Roberts sold drugs pilfered from the pharmacy during his time of employment.</p>



<p>Roberts is scheduled to be sentenced in November. If convicted, he faces a maximum sentence of 20 years in prison.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/ex-pharmacy-tech-admits-to-selling-prescriptions-on-the-darknet/">Ex Pharmacy Tech Admits to Selling Prescriptions on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/ex-pharmacy-tech-admits-to-selling-prescriptions-on-the-darknet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:14:22 by W3 Total Cache
-->