<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>lsd &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/lsd/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 11:09:09 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>lsd &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</title>
		<link>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/</link>
					<comments>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 11:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lsd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The country’s narcotics bureau ramped up efforts against the drug in recent weeks, hoping to break the supply</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/">India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>The country’s narcotics bureau ramped up efforts against the drug in recent weeks, hoping to break the supply chain for distributors servicing demand from tourists and college students.</em></p>



<p>Yesterday’s <a href="https://www.freepressjournal.in/mumbai/thane-three-college-students-held-with-1466-lsd-paper-worth-rs-102-cr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrest</a> of three college students and seizure of 1466 sheets of blotter acid in India is the latest incident to make the news in the country’s ongoing takedown of LSD sales. The Mumbai-based students are accused of being part of an international drug smuggling ring after police determined they had bought large quantities of the drug from a darknet market.</p>



<p>Just last week, India’s Narcotics Control Bureau <a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cities/mumbai-news/man-held-by-ncb-mumbai-for-providing-bitcoin-to-peddlers-for-drug-purchase-101623900590378.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrested a man who facilitated the sales of LSD through the darknet</a>. Known by his online moniker “Crypto King,” the man is thought to be responsible for arranging the purchase of thousands of doses of LSD by local resellers and various criminal enterprises. He accomplished this by acting as an intermediary between darknet market vendors and buyers who want to pay with cash.</p>



<p>According to the NCB, &#8220;His modus operandi was to receive cash and provide bitcoins on marginal profits by using his wallet that was used to purchase drugs from the Darknet.”</p>



<p>The NCB first became aware of Crypto King after a November 2020 raid in Mumbai yielded 40 tabs of European-manufactured LSD. The LSD was later determined to have been brought into the country by Crypto King in an order placed over the darknet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">sochne ki baat:- He had multiple btc wallets of forms like..to sirf wazirx ka nam q likha gya, baki ka naam kidhar hai? Suspicious game of defaming.<br>Or europe &amp; poland se India me laya kaise gya LSD, wo bhi wazirx se download kar lia kya? Smone playing dirty game..<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/wazirXwarriors?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#wazirXwarriors</a> <a href="https://t.co/9a0tas05w6">pic.twitter.com/9a0tas05w6</a></p>&mdash; Vijay Gir (@imvijaygir) <a href="https://twitter.com/imvijaygir/status/1405834826742046723?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 18, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>LSD, along with cannabis, were not formally illegalized in India until 1985. A popular tourist destination, the country’s Goa region has a long-standing association with the psychedelic counterculture movement. In March 2021, it was <a href="https://www.heraldgoa.in/Goa/LSD-resurfaces-as-party-drug-in-Goa/172264" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> that a resurgence in the popularity of LSD was underway in the area, heavily fueled by imports of high-quality Netherlands-made product.</p>



<p>In April, a tip-off led the NCB to <a href="https://www.news18.com/news/india/ncb-recovers-lsd-concealed-in-hitlers-biography-in-mumbai-3636689.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recover a copy of Adolf Hitler’s biography in which 80 tabs of LSD had been concealed</a>. The book had been flagged by the local postal service as suspicious. Later investigation revealed the drugs has been purchased on the darknet from a European vendor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/">India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:13:58 by W3 Total Cache
-->