<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>exit scam &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/exit-scam/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:18 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>exit scam &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</title>
		<link>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/</link>
					<comments>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 27 Mar 2022 11:10:15 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[dread]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[world market]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1391</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>One of the biggest and most controversial darknet markets has all but exit scammed, according to senior moderators on the <em>Dread</em> darknet forum. On March 26<sup>th</sup>, forum moderator <em>Shakybeats</em> <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ann</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">oun</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/363121f01ae216a101dc/#c-668d8ff2a6c73c1fe5" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ced</a> they had removed moderation privileges for the World Market administrator on <em>Dread</em>, disabling their ability to continue posting and confirming that an impending exit scam was likely.</p>



<p>Warning signs that something at World Market was amiss had been present for weeks, going back to a cautionary <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/d01b3750e9320def61f7" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">post</a> by a self-described former colleague of the World Market admin, written late last month. In the post, user <em>nightmaremarket</em> accused the market of preparing for an exit scam &#8212; a plan which its admin immediately denied.</p>



<p>On March 23<sup>rd</sup>, <em>Dread</em> user <em>dontlaugh</em> started a new <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">th</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">r</a><a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/154410154cad6b98a1aa" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ead</a> urging World Market users to take heed of “a number of red flags,” which most notably included a rollback to a previous version of the website. Other warning signs included a sudden jump in the cost of vendor bond – from $1,500 to $3,000 – and reports from several vendors that their payments were trapped in the market, with withdrawal requests being ignored.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="671" height="98" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1393" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1.png 671w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/1-1-300x44.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 671px) 100vw, 671px" /><figcaption><em>One of many posts responding to World Market user complaints on Dread.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>In an effort to respond to mounting complaints, World Market admin and <em>Dread</em> user <em>makarov</em> wrote the following <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/ab00d26a769f65030710" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">counter-post</a>, which was heavily downvoted, with its rationale being dismissed by most respondents:</p>



<p>“The time has come that the World Market team must close shop. The team tried to fix numerous technical issues over the past week but could not recover what has been lost. We have worked hard to be the best market and to serve the community.</p>



<p>As much as I care for everyone at World Market, I also care about the vendors and buyers, and it would not be fair to continue at this point.” – <em>Dread user makarov</em></p>



<p>Less than two days later, the post by <em>dontlaugh</em> was edited to include the following text: “UPDATE: I think we can call it. Either one of the admins fucked the other (who would have thunk it) or they both pulled this to squeeze out as much as possible from everyone,” thus signaling the end of the market’s functionality.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="477" height="407" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1394" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1.png 477w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/03/2-1-300x256.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 477px) 100vw, 477px" /><figcaption><em>World Market welcome message that is currently still being displayed.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>After the closures of White House Market and Dark0de, World Market was for a short while one of the biggest darknet markets in operation, hosting well over 30,000 listings at its peak. The market used the traditional account deposit system, making an exit scam especially lucrative for a market its size.</p>



<p>As of March 27<sup>th</sup>, the rolled-back version of World Market was still accessible and allowing those who had created older accounts to still login and even make deposits. However, many functions have been removed, making purchases or withdrawals impossible.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/">Another One Bites the Dust? World Market On Verge of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/another-one-bites-the-dust-world-market-on-verge-of-exit-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Tor2Door Cashout Problems Spark Fears of Exit Scam</title>
		<link>/tor2door-cashout-problems-spark-fears-of-exit-scam/</link>
					<comments>/tor2door-cashout-problems-spark-fears-of-exit-scam/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 04 Oct 2021 18:47:10 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[tor2door]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=863</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A now-deleted post by Dread admin Paris announced the market had likely exit scammed; a conclusion based on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tor2door-cashout-problems-spark-fears-of-exit-scam/">Tor2Door Cashout Problems Spark Fears of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A now-deleted <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1444791206840393730/photo/2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">post</a> by Dread admin Paris announced the market had likely exit scammed; a conclusion based on the fact the Tor2Door admin had been ignoring concerns regarding withdrawals for over a week. Paris went so far as to revoke the market admin’s access to the Tor2Door subdread, noting he wanted to prevent scam accusations from being deleted. The market otherwise remained available and functional, leaving room for the possibility of a technical problem.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="438" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/tor1-1024x438.png" alt="" class="wp-image-867" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/tor1-1024x438.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/tor1-300x128.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/tor1-768x329.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/tor1.png 1393w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /><figcaption>Paris correction post</figcaption></figure>



<p>“FWIW I received $350 in BTC 5 days ago from the market,” wrote one verified Tor2Door vendor on Dread. “Seems like it&#8217;s mostly, if not entirely, XMR that&#8217;s being withheld which could lend credence to the exchange gone wrong theory. Fishy as all fuck though.”</p>



<p>Within a few hours of the post by Paris, the Tor2Door admin apologized and began addressing concerns of vendors on Dread. The admin, going by the forum name <em>needsadesigner</em>, <a href="https://twitter.com/ixonae/status/1444876298074013696/photo/2" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> a “flaw” in their “exchange system,” which they were currently attempting to resolve. Shortly thereafter, another vendor <a href="https://pbs.twimg.com/media/FA06R-hUYAMgpFp?format=png&amp;name=4096x4096" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">commented</a> that the market had released a portion of their funds as a sign of good faith, helping to put fears to rest they had exit scammed.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Earlier today Paris, one of the Dread Forum&#39;s admin, posted (deleted since) that Tor2Door was probably in the process of scam-exiting. It now seems that this was not the case 1/3<a href="https://t.co/1ZRJYxwssc">https://t.co/1ZRJYxwssc</a></p>&mdash; Ixonae (@ixonae) <a href="https://twitter.com/ixonae/status/1444876293091172360?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">October 4, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The explanations of what had happened seemed to satisfy Paris, who removed his warning about Tor2Door and reinstated subdread rights for the market’s page to its admin. Reports from other vendors receiving partial repayments have been posted to Dread within recent hours, confirming that the market’s issues now appear to be more-or-less under control.</p>



<p>“Shaking the bush worked, i got a hold of /u/needsadesigner and he has been talking to me,” wrote another verified Tor2Door vendor. “He has stated that the communication failure is unfortunate, but they’re working to prove they are still here. They have agreed to send me 1k right now to show their good faith.”</p>



<p>Tor2Door opened in June 2020, getting its first mentions among the community as the <a href="https://twitter.com/RakeshKrish12/status/1273158671988555776" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">go-to option of choice</a> for buyers and vendors of the exit scamming BitBazaar market. It currently has about 7,500 listings with the majority being in the Drugs &amp; Chemicals and Digital Products categories. The market accepts Bitcoin and Monero and uses the traditional account wallet system for payments.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/tor2door-cashout-problems-spark-fears-of-exit-scam/">Tor2Door Cashout Problems Spark Fears of Exit Scam</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/tor2door-cashout-problems-spark-fears-of-exit-scam/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Televend Reported Compromised, Exit Scam Possible</title>
		<link>/televend-reported-compromised-exit-scam-possible/</link>
					<comments>/televend-reported-compromised-exit-scam-possible/#comments</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 24 Sep 2021 10:11:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=837</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Multiple vendors of Televend, the Telegram-based drug market, are reporting being locked out of their vendor panels on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/televend-reported-compromised-exit-scam-possible/">Televend Reported Compromised, Exit Scam Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Multiple vendors of Televend, the Telegram-based drug market, are <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/5d9aeb7c31d76f217dca?p=1" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reporting</a> being locked out of their vendor panels on the platform. According to posts on the Dread darknet forum, they are unable to access critical components of Televend and considering the platform to be compromised, warning all users to stay away. This comes after reports that Bitcoin deposit addresses for customer orders were being altered to addresses not belonging to them, or not generated using the vendor’s Bitcoin xpub.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="285" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-1-1024x285.png" alt="" class="wp-image-838" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-1-1024x285.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-1-300x84.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-1-768x214.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/1-1.png 1476w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Televend has been <a href="https://news.bitcoin.com/televends-complex-system-of-telegram-drug-bots-swell-as-german-police-seize-9-telegram-drug-channels/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">described</a> by many as complex, risky, and far from immune when it comes to attention from law enforcement. It is hailed by its users for its consistency and lack of downtime – problems that frequently plague the hidden services-based darknet markets.</p>



<p>“This is a warning to any/all vendors and buyers who may have been active on Televend or purchasing through a Televend vendor bot,” said HugBunter, long-time Dread admin and author of the warning thread. “Wipe your data and clean house, you literally hold incriminating evidence on your cell phone you fucking idiots.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">It is said that some vendors saw their crypto addresses replaced on their bots (Televend is a &quot;Fully automated Vendor shop bot powered by Telegram for Direct-Dealers&quot;), and a user reported that the admin panel now require JavaScript to be enabled <a href="https://t.co/FlrYrAITSI">https://t.co/FlrYrAITSI</a></p>&mdash; Ixonae (@ixonae) <a href="https://twitter.com/ixonae/status/1441286551376314372?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">September 24, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Though incredibly popular, Televend did not offer the security of traditional darknet markets in that it still relied upon Telegram – a centralized entity – to maintain its operation. In Oct. 2020, Televend admins <a href="https://www.ibtimes.com/what-televend-telegram-robot-drug-dealer-sells-narcotics-bitcoin-3061935" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">estimated</a> the platform had about 200,000 customers spread out across over a dozen countries.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-gallery columns-1 is-cropped"><ul class="blocks-gallery-grid"><li class="blocks-gallery-item"><figure><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="155" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1024x155.png" alt="" data-id="839" data-full-url="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1.png" data-link="/?attachment_id=839" class="wp-image-839" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-1024x155.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-300x45.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1-768x116.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/2-1.png 1491w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure></li></ul></figure>



<p>After awareness of Televend’s existence regularly permeated the mainstream media in late 2020, Telegram deleted everything associated with the platform from their servers, including bots and vendor accounts. This posed to be but a minor inconvenience for the admins, who had Televend back up and running again within a matter of days.</p>



<p>Two weeks ago, however, Televend users <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/Telegram/comments/plj356/telegram_has_started_deleting_bots/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">noticed</a> bots were starting to be deleted again. Around the same time, suspicions began to arise as not only had one of its administrators been “MIA,” but was apparently acting as a vendor on the platform as well.</p>



<p>“I confirm today telegram stole 160 euros from 2 customers, the money was paid but did not arrive in my wallet,” reported one vendor on Dread. “The wallet addresses were changed, in the control panel all is still ok and wallets are generated correctly but customers get different addresses to pay.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="1024" height="448" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x448.png" alt="" class="wp-image-840" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-1024x448.png 1024w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-300x131.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3-768x336.png 768w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/09/3.png 1486w" sizes="(max-width: 1024px) 100vw, 1024px" /></figure>



<p>Shortly afterward, vendor control panels were disabled, only to be soon re-enabled but this time curiously demanding JavaScript be disabled for access.</p>



<p>Speculative theories about what had just happened to Televend were rampant on Dread, running the gamut from exit scam to hacked to busted by law enforcement. According to HugBunter, the sudden closure and supposed re-opening “definitely doesn&#8217;t fit the usual exit scam criteria, but that wouldn&#8217;t be a first.”</p>



<p>Other Dread posters weren’t so sure. “Interesting new way of exit scam,” said one member. “They disable the admin panel for the sellers, change the wallet address to their wallets and leave the<br>bots doing their job. And until telegram will delete all these bots, that will take a while.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/televend-reported-compromised-exit-scam-possible/">Televend Reported Compromised, Exit Scam Possible</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/televend-reported-compromised-exit-scam-possible/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>1</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Rapture Market Closes It’s Doors Over Hack</title>
		<link>/rapture-market-hacked/</link>
					<comments>/rapture-market-hacked/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Tue, 20 Nov 2018 15:08:20 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[exit scam]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=64</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Over the past several weeks DNM users have been unable to access the popular Darknet Market known as</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rapture-market-hacked/">Rapture Market Closes It’s Doors Over Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Over the past several weeks DNM users have been unable to access the popular <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>Darknet Market</strong></a> known as <strong><a href="https://web.archive.org/web/20190417014820//rapture-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">R</a></strong><a href="/rapture-market/"><strong>apture Market</strong></a>. Visiting any of the official Rapture Market links loads nothing beyond the generic “Down for Maintenance” page.</p>



<p>With little news emerging from the site admin’s, there has been plenty of speculation and FUD across&nbsp;various forums in regards to Rapture Market’s status.</p>



<p>2 weeks ago a post was made in Dread which offered some hopes of seeing a reemergence of the market in the near future. However, that glimmer of a return for <a href="/rapture-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>Rapture Market</strong></a> has been silenced given a recent post by Rapture Market’s Head of Staff, <strong>LegalAmigo</strong>.</p>



<pre class="wp-block-preformatted">-----BEGIN PGP SIGNED MESSAGE-----
Hash: SHA256
Dear Rapture users &amp; fellow Dread members.
It is with deep regret that we have to make this announcement.
We believe Rapture has come to an end.
We have not heard from LetsWork &amp; have spent many messages trying to establish contact or status updates on the market.
This is because of an exploit which allowed an attacker to steal 8 Bitcoins out of the wallet, out of the total 11.
The day this happened we were speaking with LetsWork trying to think of possible resolutions, and the last 3 coins were moved from the market server for what we assumed was safer storage.
We were told that there was investors in the market who would replace the funds, and that he was waiting on the coins to do so.
There were some back &amp; forth messages which were fruitless to the state of the market or the future and it has now been 7 days since any of the Amigo team has received contact from LetsWork.
There is still a possibility the market could come back but we are no longer holding up false hope &amp; we felt 7 days was a fair figure to call game set match. It is not fun to write this statement, as I am sure it is not fun for any of our users to read it also, especially anybody who lost coins or money which they rely on.
This is no hate intended towards LetsWork, as it was clear to us all along he is not the owner of the market, just a gate to said person, and we feel the situation is most likely out of his hands. We believe the investors hold the cards here but it is a shame to receive no contact from LetsWork.
The Amigo team would like send all our users our best wishes, we hope you are not greatly affected by your losses. We hope you understand we took our jobs for the sole reason of providing the best market support possible. We always did our best to settle your disputes and resolve your tickets. We can assure you we have no great take from this either and I am sure you can see by the amount of Bitcoin stolen we were not being paid much at all and we ourselves are now out of a job.
LetsWork, if you are reading this we wish you all the best, and hope the market can come back with peoples funds at some point.
-----BEGIN PGP SIGNATURE-----
iQEzBAEBCAAdFiEEjBbkt0TnvyzlSSkYB7BcmsJPmTIFAlvwBhgACgkQB7BcmsJP
mTLrZQgAkkkt/E1naK3//59YodwBXhsoohTMvLLtBqIYIcf2bI/DXBWD4t5pgPfg
unCqMUx3XG7bTB8w+bhJLhfD1YJCRSMxdVeYPhFmK4jewZog4IY5GMANa4E19OZH
6sLb2TGsZwbvoXN2mc0zXXFDJPSp05dtLTxhNpPlO1CABilxY/0B5E9gpJaBnJqN
DL+Tk553V4p8pFqtoY10p7b5qoo4OCM2+3NzkxwqiWoabfL28FCLyODfLTVCv+dn
MR0vQBXggEFIwIlYCJ5s4Dtw3O+Rmsebjb0HajjXuaB2ccquvF33/g5G2iKqET1e
jtqvtubZmtrzOAJGG1YgJmwT9ZSsgQ==
=ClJb
-----END PGP SIGNATURE-----</pre>



<p><em>Source:</em> <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/fbed51814bf5a246d75d" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/fbed51814bf5a246d75d</a></p>



<div class="wp-block-image"><figure class="aligncenter"><img src="https://web.archive.org/web/20190417014820im_//wp-content/uploads/2018/11/Rapture-Market-Dread-Post-1024x519.jpg" alt="Rapture Market Hacked" class="wp-image-3440"/></figure></div>



<p>Given the most recent post on the status of <a href="/rapture-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>Rapture Market</strong></a>, it appears any chance of a return is very unlikely.&nbsp; We are now removing Rapture Market from our <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>List of Darknet Markets</strong></a>. If any additional information becomes public we will post it on our Rapture Market page as we will continue to follow the story on this popular <a href="https://darknetmarkets.com/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><strong>Darknet Market</strong></a>.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/rapture-market-hacked/">Rapture Market Closes It’s Doors Over Hack</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/rapture-market-hacked/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:14 by W3 Total Cache
-->