<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>darknet &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/darknet/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:56:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>darknet &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>US Senate Targets Darknet Drug Dealers in New Bill</title>
		<link>/us-senate-targets-darknet-drug-dealers-in-new-bill/</link>
					<comments>/us-senate-targets-darknet-drug-dealers-in-new-bill/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 11 Mar 2022 09:56:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Uncategorized]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[US Senate]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1370</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The United States is ramping up its efforts to combat an opioid addiction crisis by introducing a legislative</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-senate-targets-darknet-drug-dealers-in-new-bill/">US Senate Targets Darknet Drug Dealers in New Bill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The United States is ramping up its efforts to combat an opioid addiction crisis by <a href="https://apnews.com/article/new-hampshire-john-cornyn-maggie-hassan-congress-db31d8f3d0ed0a28bafd37e82e62612c" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">introducing a legislative bill</a> specifically targeting drug dealers on <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet markets</a>. The bill, titled the Dark Web Interdiction Act, would increase penalties for dealers convicted of selling any type of illegal drug over the dark web. It was crafted by Senators Maggie Hassan of New Hampshire and John Cornyn of Texas and introduced to the senate on Wednesday, Mar 9.</p>



<p>If passed into law, the Dark Web Interdiction Act would also direct the Department of Justice, Homeland Security and Treasury to provide a report to Congress “detailing the use of cryptocurrency on the dark web.” In addition, it would give recommendations to Congress on how to best approach the use of cryptocurrency as it pertains to opioid sales on the darknet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">The dark web has become a hotspot for illegal sales of fentanyl and other deadly drugs that are fueling the opioid crisis.<br><br>This week Senator Cornyn and I introduced a bill to crack down on these illegal marketplaces and increase penalties for dealers. <a href="https://t.co/ahZvesSMMJ">https://t.co/ahZvesSMMJ</a></p>&mdash; Sen. Maggie Hassan (@SenatorHassan) <a href="https://twitter.com/SenatorHassan/status/1501932037401284614?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">March 10, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>“Drug dealers are using the dark corners of the internet to sell deadly drugs that are fueling the substance misuse crisis in New Hampshire and across the country,” wrote Hassan in a <a href="https://www.facebook.com/SenatorHassan" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Facebook</a> post announcing the introduction of the bill.</p>



<p>“<em>I am teaming up with Republican Senator John Cornyn of Texas to crack down on those caught trafficking drugs on the dark web, target international fentanyl trafficking from China and Mexico, and strengthen our overall efforts to disrupt and dismantle these illegal marketplaces.” – Senator Maggie Hassan, New Hampshire</em></p>



<p>Hassan, Cornyn, and Senator Dianne Feinstein first <a href="https://www.hassan.senate.gov/imo/media/doc/Letter%20to%20DOJ%20FBI%20re%20Dark%20Web%20Opioid%20Trafficking-FINAL.9.14.20.pdf" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">requested information</a> pertaining to the government’s current efforts to crack down on darknet market drug sales in September 2020. In a letter to Attorney General William Barr, the subcommittee specifically mentioned dark web sales of fentanyl as their primary concern, along with other highly-powerful opioids.</p>



<p>“Tens of thousands of Americans die every year from opioid overdoses,” the subcommittee mentioned in the letter – a problem which worsened considerably in the US over the next two years that followed. The <a href="https://www.cdc.gov/nchs/pressroom/nchs_press_releases/2021/20211117.htm" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">latest estimates</a> provided by the Center for Disease Control reveal that over 75,000 Americans now die of opiate overdoses on an annual scale, accounting for about 76% of all drug overdose fatalities in the nation.</p>



<p>While many darknet markets operating today implement a strict no-fentanyl or related analog policy, threatening to ban vendors caught selling these times, fentanyl is still frequently <a href="https://archives.drugabuse.gov/emerging-trends/fake-prescription-drugs-laced-fentanyl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">used as</a><a href="https://archives.drugabuse.gov/emerging-trends/fake-prescription-drugs-laced-fentanyl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"> a</a><a href="https://archives.drugabuse.gov/emerging-trends/fake-prescription-drugs-laced-fentanyl" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">n adulterant</a> in many fake pill formulations. These include products branded as Oxycontin, Percocet, Hydrocodone, and even Xanax.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/us-senate-targets-darknet-drug-dealers-in-new-bill/">US Senate Targets Darknet Drug Dealers in New Bill</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/us-senate-targets-darknet-drug-dealers-in-new-bill/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Darknet Economy Slow to Grow Compared to Other &#8216;Illicit&#8217; Areas of Crypto</title>
		<link>/darknet-economy-slow-to-grow-compared-to-other-illicit-areas-of-crypto/</link>
					<comments>/darknet-economy-slow-to-grow-compared-to-other-illicit-areas-of-crypto/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 08 Jan 2022 14:44:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1065</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The percentage of all cryptocurrency transactions considered to be ‘illicit’ declined to its lowest level yet in 2021,</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-economy-slow-to-grow-compared-to-other-illicit-areas-of-crypto/">Darknet Economy Slow to Grow Compared to Other &#8216;Illicit&#8217; Areas of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The percentage of all cryptocurrency transactions considered to be ‘illicit’ <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-crypto-crime-report-introduction/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">declined to its lowest level</a> yet in 2021, with the statistic being measured annually by blockchain analysts at <em>Chainalysis</em>. While the digital forensics experts note that crypto addresses associated with darknet markets and scams also “contribute significantly” to fund totals deemed illicit, darknet-related transactions rose less than 15% year-over-year, significantly under-pacing the other categories analyzed.</p>



<p>Transactions to cryptocurrency addresses identified as ‘illicit’ represented a slender 0.15% of all transaction volume last year, despite a rise in the number of darknet market and ransomware operators. This figure, though tiny compared to the overall volume of crypto transactions, still represents $14 billion in “illicit activity.” This poses a severe problem, according to <em>Chainalysis</em>, which believes the size of the number “creates huge impediments for continued adoption,” among other issues.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">there’s your headline <a href="https://t.co/gTWlkf9KcI">pic.twitter.com/gTWlkf9KcI</a></p>&mdash; Neeraj K. Agrawal (@NeerajKA) <a href="https://twitter.com/NeerajKA/status/1479194968925290500?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">January 6, 2022</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The categories of crime determined and tracked by <em>Chainalysis</em> include Stolen Funds, Scams, Ransomware, Cybercriminal Administrator, Fraud Shop, Darknet Market, and Child Abuse Material. Approximately $3.2 billion in crypto was stolen via various means in 2021, representing a 516% increase over 2020. About 72% of this amount was taken in different DeFi hacks.</p>



<p>Scamming revenue was the biggest single category, which rose to $7.8 billion in 2021. Over $2.8 billion of this came from rug pulls; most of which are former DeFi projects. The report also stressed the continued, widescale use of DeFi for money laundering purposes, which dwarfs all activity deemed illicit on the dark web by several fold.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="692" height="273" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1067" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1.png 692w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/01/1-1-300x118.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 692px) 100vw, 692px" /></figure>



<p><em>Chainalysis</em> notes that it is keeping track of “illicit addresses hold(ing) at least $10 billion worth of cryptocurrency” as of January 2022, with the “vast majority of this held by wallets associated with cryptocurrency theft.”</p>



<p>Despite this setback for the public’s perception of cryptocurrency, the report’s authors conclude that “crime is becoming a smaller and smaller part of the cryptocurrency ecosystem,” with widespread crypto adoption continuing to outpace the growth of darknet markets – a trend which has been in place since at least 2017.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/darknet-economy-slow-to-grow-compared-to-other-illicit-areas-of-crypto/">Darknet Economy Slow to Grow Compared to Other &#8216;Illicit&#8217; Areas of Crypto</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/darknet-economy-slow-to-grow-compared-to-other-illicit-areas-of-crypto/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</title>
		<link>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/</link>
					<comments>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Oct 2021 11:06:39 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[alphabay]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[desnake]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=853</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, AlphaBay, is failing to impress the community, with</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>The grand ‘return’ of the world’s second-most famous darknet market, <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/">AlphaBay</a>, is failing to impress the community, with many would-be users avoiding the site due to an assortment of concerns. Nearly seven weeks after AlphaBay’s supposed ‘re-opening,’ the market has managed to attract just a small number of vendors and even fewer customers. This is despite the relatively massive attention its re-opening has received in the media.</p>



<p>A recent article by <a href="https://www.wired.com/story/alphabay-desnake-dark-web-interview/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>Wired</em></a><em>, </em>which features an interview with <a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a> admin DeSnake, attempted to shed some light as to why the market hasn’t taken off. Among the reasons are persistent DDOS attacks and the decision to accept Monero (XMR)-only for order payments, but the main problem is a lack of trust by the community. Flashpoint security expert Ian Gray told <em>Wired</em> that he was personally distrustful of DeSnake and that “across communities there’s a general distrust.”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="630" height="312" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-855" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1.png 630w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/1-300x149.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 630px) 100vw, 630px" /><figcaption><em>The legitimacy of the new AlphaBay is being heavily </em><a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/darknet/comments/pij727/is_the_new_alphabay_a_honeypot/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener"><em>questioned</em></a><em> by Redditors on r/darknet.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p><a href="/directory/listing/alphabay-market/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">AlphaBay</a>’s listings currently total slightly less than 800, with about 400 of them in the Drugs &amp; Chemicals section. As there were only 300 total listings just three weeks ago, this represents a 167% increase in the last 20 days. At the peak of its popularity in 2017, the market had approximately 350,000 listings.</p>



<p>Sales, on the other hand, remain scarce and limited to a handful of vendors. Most sections, though filled with listings and vendors awaiting customers, have zero product sales according to stats kept on each listing. There were single sales spotted for listings of shrooms, marijuana, cocaine, and alprazolam. One listing for Ecstasy had two sales.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="807" height="354" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png" alt="" class="wp-image-856" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2.png 807w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-300x132.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/10/2-768x337.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 807px) 100vw, 807px" /><figcaption><em>The scarcity of listings and near complete lack of sales on AlphaBay give it an almost ghost town feel.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>The market’s welcome message and the first return <a href="http://dreadytofatroptsdj6io7l3xptbet6onoyno2yv7jicoxknyazubrad.onion/post/196fffff69ffe348636e" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">message</a> left by DeSnake insist this is not the “new AlphaBay” or “AlphaBay 2.0” but rather a continuation of the same market that shut down in 2017. Not many are sure that this is the case, however, despite DeSnake being verified as a former AlphaBay admin by senior members of the Dread forum.</p>



<p>“The entire point of us returning is about rebuilding the AlphaBay brand and creating something unique and new which will set the standard for a new way how things can be approached,” wrote DeSnake on Dread when asked why he chose not to rebrand the operation. “No other big market has come from the &#8216;dead&#8217; so whether it is a good decision business-wise &#8211; time will tell.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/">Reborn Darknet Market AlphaBay Slow to Find Customers</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/reborn-darknet-market-alphabay-slow-to-find-customers/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</title>
		<link>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/</link>
					<comments>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Mon, 21 Jun 2021 11:09:06 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[india]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[lsd]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=652</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>The country’s narcotics bureau ramped up efforts against the drug in recent weeks, hoping to break the supply</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/">India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>The country’s narcotics bureau ramped up efforts against the drug in recent weeks, hoping to break the supply chain for distributors servicing demand from tourists and college students.</em></p>



<p>Yesterday’s <a href="https://www.freepressjournal.in/mumbai/thane-three-college-students-held-with-1466-lsd-paper-worth-rs-102-cr" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrest</a> of three college students and seizure of 1466 sheets of blotter acid in India is the latest incident to make the news in the country’s ongoing takedown of LSD sales. The Mumbai-based students are accused of being part of an international drug smuggling ring after police determined they had bought large quantities of the drug from a darknet market.</p>



<p>Just last week, India’s Narcotics Control Bureau <a href="https://www.hindustantimes.com/cities/mumbai-news/man-held-by-ncb-mumbai-for-providing-bitcoin-to-peddlers-for-drug-purchase-101623900590378.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">arrested a man who facilitated the sales of LSD through the darknet</a>. Known by his online moniker “Crypto King,” the man is thought to be responsible for arranging the purchase of thousands of doses of LSD by local resellers and various criminal enterprises. He accomplished this by acting as an intermediary between darknet market vendors and buyers who want to pay with cash.</p>



<p>According to the NCB, &#8220;His modus operandi was to receive cash and provide bitcoins on marginal profits by using his wallet that was used to purchase drugs from the Darknet.”</p>



<p>The NCB first became aware of Crypto King after a November 2020 raid in Mumbai yielded 40 tabs of European-manufactured LSD. The LSD was later determined to have been brought into the country by Crypto King in an order placed over the darknet.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">sochne ki baat:- He had multiple btc wallets of forms like..to sirf wazirx ka nam q likha gya, baki ka naam kidhar hai? Suspicious game of defaming.<br>Or europe &amp; poland se India me laya kaise gya LSD, wo bhi wazirx se download kar lia kya? Smone playing dirty game..<a href="https://twitter.com/hashtag/wazirXwarriors?src=hash&amp;ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">#wazirXwarriors</a> <a href="https://t.co/9a0tas05w6">pic.twitter.com/9a0tas05w6</a></p>&mdash; Vijay Gir (@imvijaygir) <a href="https://twitter.com/imvijaygir/status/1405834826742046723?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">June 18, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>LSD, along with cannabis, were not formally illegalized in India until 1985. A popular tourist destination, the country’s Goa region has a long-standing association with the psychedelic counterculture movement. In March 2021, it was <a href="https://www.heraldgoa.in/Goa/LSD-resurfaces-as-party-drug-in-Goa/172264" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">reported</a> that a resurgence in the popularity of LSD was underway in the area, heavily fueled by imports of high-quality Netherlands-made product.</p>



<p>In April, a tip-off led the NCB to <a href="https://www.news18.com/news/india/ncb-recovers-lsd-concealed-in-hitlers-biography-in-mumbai-3636689.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recover a copy of Adolf Hitler’s biography in which 80 tabs of LSD had been concealed</a>. The book had been flagged by the local postal service as suspicious. Later investigation revealed the drugs has been purchased on the darknet from a European vendor.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/">India Cracks Down on Darknet Sales of LSD</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/india-cracks-down-on-darknet-sales-of-lsd/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</title>
		<link>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/</link>
					<comments>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sat, 05 Jun 2021 10:25:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[cyber attack]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[data breach]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[hacker]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=601</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Personal data collected off insecure systems by phishers and attackers is being used to steal even more data</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/">Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><em>Personal data collected off insecure systems by phishers and attackers is being used to steal even more data in a positive feedback loop that is amplifying out of control.</em></p>



<p>A new <a href="https://www.imperva.com/resources/resource-library/white-papers/lessons-learned-from-analyzing-100-data-breaches/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> by security research experts at Imperva predicts that roughly 40 billion records will be compromised in data breaches by the end of 2021. This figure represents a 100% increase from 2020, a year which saw a lot of businesses transition operations online due to restrictions imposed by COVID. The report analyzed 100 data breaches and found that 74% of stolen records contained personal data, while 15.6% contained login credentials and 10.4% was credit card information. All three types of data are frequently found for sale on darknet markets.</p>



<p>The report comes at a time when <a href="https://www.csis.org/programs/strategic-technologies-program/significant-cyber-incidents" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">significant cyberattacks are at an all-time high</a>. In addition to the <a href="https://www.cnn.com/2021/06/04/politics/white-house-ransomware/index.html" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">highly-publicized ransomware attacks</a> that have netted attackers tens of millions in 2021, the number of reported data breaches is skyrocketing. According to cyber attack report aggregators at <a href="https://www.databreaches.net/news/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Databreaches.net</a>, there were 11 major data breach incidents reported just yesterday, Jun 4<sup>th</sup>. This represents a significant uptick from activity reported just one year ago.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-large"><img loading="lazy" width="868" height="364" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart.png" alt="" class="wp-image-603" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart.png 868w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart-300x126.png 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/06/chart-768x322.png 768w" sizes="(max-width: 868px) 100vw, 868px" /><figcaption>Source: Lessons learned from analyzing 100 data breaches, imperva.com</figcaption></figure>



<p>“We are definitely seeing a spike in ransomware attacks that also have a data breach component to them,” said cybersecurity attorney Brian Finch on a <a href="https://www.jdsupra.com/legalnews/ransomware-data-breaches-and-the-5474731/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">recent legal podcast episode</a>.</p>



<p>“Not only is your data encrypted, but it’s being stolen as well, and the hackers are demanding a ransom not only to unlock your system, but also to prevent them from releasing the private information&#8230; So, it’s sort of a two-fer attack. You get the ransom, and you get data breach as well.”</p>



<p>As noted in the report by Imperva, the stolen data put up for sale on the dark web is often used for extortion and phishing attempts designed to pilfer even more data. The report also analyzed root causes of initial breaches and found that almost 50% of the time it was due to poor website design.</p>



<p>“In most of the analyzed breaches the lack of in-depth security stands out as a main reason,” the report concludes.</p>



<p>“Organizations can reduce the attack surface by securing their database environments. Since a significant number of the attacks target web applications, separating the database server from the application server can make a big difference. Together with dilution of excessive privileges from key users and strong authentication mechanisms, these practices in combination can help you avoid a data breach.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/">Report: Data Breach Epidemic Fuels Cycle of Demand on the Darknet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/report-data-breach-epidemic-fuels-cycle-of-demand-on-the-darknet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 13:57:05 by W3 Total Cache
-->