<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>fraud &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/fraud/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 17:26:15 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>fraud &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Identity Thieves Busted Using Murder Victim ID</title>
		<link>/identity-thieves-busted-using-murder-victim-id/</link>
					<comments>/identity-thieves-busted-using-murder-victim-id/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 05 Dec 2021 17:26:12 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[DisrupTOR]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fraud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1005</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Two Georgia men will serve time in prison after their identity theft operation took a turn for the</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/identity-thieves-busted-using-murder-victim-id/">Identity Thieves Busted Using Murder Victim ID</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Two Georgia men will serve time in prison after their identity theft operation took a turn for the bizarre, leading to their capture by authorities.</p>



<p>According to <a href="https://www.justice.gov/usao-ndga/pr/two-georgia-men-sentenced-using-dark-web-steal-identities-elderly-victims" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">federal prosecutors</a>, Durrell Tyler and DeShawn Johnson used darknet markets to purchase personal identifiable information (PII), using it to open lines of credit under the names of their victims. To accomplish this, they forwarded victim phone lines, mailing addresses, and emails to themselves. This allowed Tyler and Johnson to fully impersonate their victims without letting them catch on to the scam, which netted an estimated $130,000.</p>



<p>Most of the duo’s 75 victims were elderly, and many had been the target of identity theft before.</p>



<p>It was one particular purchase that Tyler made that caught the eye of federal investigators. Among the sets of data he bought from the dark web was the personal information of Ron and Dorothy Hess, an elderly Georgia couple that had been <a href="https://www.wuga.org/post/barrow-county-murders-tied-opioid-investigation#stream/0" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">murdered</a> in 2019. Adding to the intrigue is the <a href="https://www.wsbtv.com/news/local/barrow-county/barrow-county-couples-murder-tied-opioids-dark-web-authorities-say/T6OWP6WKP5AXRFT6IGYCQGRPDI/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">report</a> that the couple’s information was being used by Tyler “within days after being brutally killed.”</p>



<p>County Sheriffs in Barrow, Georgia – the home county of the Hess’ – have not named Tyler as a suspect in the double homicide, but also haven’t ruled his involvement out “in any case, shape or form.” The case of what happened to Hess’ remains unsolved but has sparked some deal of <a href="https://www.websleuths.com/forums/threads/ga-william-hess-71-dorothy-72-shot-to-death-in-home-winder-20-may-2019.446011" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">speculation among internet detectives</a> over the last two years.</p>



<p>Tyler’s arrest stems from the actions of ‘Operation DisrupTOR,’ which is a “coordinated international effort to disrupt opioid trafficking on the darknet.” To date, DisrupTOR has led to 120 arrests and the seizure of 270+ kilograms of various drugs.</p>



<p>Tyler, who plead guilty to the charges in May, will serve 5 years and 10 months in prison, while Johnson will serve 3 years and 6 months. The investigation for the case was carried out by the US Postal Inspection Service and the US Secret Service.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/identity-thieves-busted-using-murder-victim-id/">Identity Thieves Busted Using Murder Victim ID</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/identity-thieves-busted-using-murder-victim-id/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Governments Lack Plan to Deal with Fake Covid Vaccination Cards</title>
		<link>/governments-lack-plan-to-deal-with-fake-covid-vaccination-cards/</link>
					<comments>/governments-lack-plan-to-deal-with-fake-covid-vaccination-cards/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Wed, 03 Nov 2021 15:40:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[fraud]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=917</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Darknet market sales of forged covid-19 vaccination cards are booming according to security researchers studying the issue on</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/governments-lack-plan-to-deal-with-fake-covid-vaccination-cards/">Governments Lack Plan to Deal with Fake Covid Vaccination Cards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Darknet market sales of forged covid-19 vaccination cards are <a href="https://www.rt.com/russia/539208-darknet-fake-covid-vaccine-certificates/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">booming</a> according to security researchers studying the issue on both American and European fronts. A flurry of vaccine-related mandates issued by both U.S. and European leaders has led to a surge in demand for the fake records as significant portions of the global population continue to resist vaccination.</p>



<p>The number of vendors offering vaccination card or test services has <a href="https://news.bloomberglaw.com/privacy-and-data-security/fake-vaccine-cards-pose-enforcement-challenge-as-mandates-rise" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">skyrocketed</a> from around 1,000 in August to 10,000 in September, according to security experts at <em>Check Point Research</em>.</p>



<p>In America, where vaccination is increasingly a requirement for societal participation, the problem faced when attempting to crack down on fraudulent vaccine records involves a general lack of coordination between government agencies enforcing card-checking policies. Europe and Russia, on the other hand, suffer more from a disconnectedness between IT companies providing vaccination QR code-checking infrastructure.</p>



<p>“No coherent approach has emerged to deter their use, or to provide guidance to businesses responsible for checking proof of vaccination,” staff of <em>The Crime Report</em> wrote in an October <a href="https://thecrimereport.org/2021/10/29/amid-mandates-fake-vaccine-cards-present-new-challenge-for-law-enforcement/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">editorial</a>, referring to the vaccination card issue. “And because buyers can prolong an illegal scheme unless someone tips off the government to the fraud, businesses are on their own to check these cards,” they said.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="513" height="300" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-919" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1.png 513w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/11/1-1-300x175.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 513px) 100vw, 513px" /><figcaption><em>Covid vaccination card market listing example.</em></figcaption></figure>



<p>While several popular darknet markets carry forged vaccination cards in their “Fraud,” Counterfeits,” “Forgeries” or “Digital Items” sections, some markets refuse to support anything remotely related to covid.</p>



<p>“Fellow Americans, everyone deserves autonomy, medical privacy &amp; equality,” penned one vaccine card vendor in the opening to their listing description. “We are here for you to prevent you from being intimidated &amp; pressured into taking vaccines,” they continued, before going on to describe how they obtained the cards and what actions went into the forgery of a filled card.</p>



<p>Prices of the cards on darknet markets tend to range between $50 and $500, with an average card costing around $100 in the U.S. and $300 in Europe. The cards vary in price depending on the level of complexity required to forge the card. Some come complete with scannable QR codes; others are simply digital renderings as often a photocopy is all that is required for verification purposes.</p>



<p>One vaccination card vendor was offering an additional $500 service to have an “insider” place a customer’s corresponding information in a “national database.”</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/governments-lack-plan-to-deal-with-fake-covid-vaccination-cards/">Governments Lack Plan to Deal with Fake Covid Vaccination Cards</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/governments-lack-plan-to-deal-with-fake-covid-vaccination-cards/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:15:19 by W3 Total Cache
-->