<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>silkroad &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/silkroad/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:03:34 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>silkroad &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Vendor ‘SuperTrips’ Proclaimed ‘Escobar of Silk Road’ Publicizes Tell-All Book</title>
		<link>/vendor-proclaimed-escobar-of-silk-road-publicizes-tell-all-book/</link>
					<comments>/vendor-proclaimed-escobar-of-silk-road-publicizes-tell-all-book/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 12 Dec 2021 16:02:45 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silkroad]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[supertrips]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1021</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Convicted Silk Road vendor Maikel Slomp, aka SuperTrips, took to social media recently to promote his new memoir,</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendor-proclaimed-escobar-of-silk-road-publicizes-tell-all-book/">Vendor ‘SuperTrips’ Proclaimed ‘Escobar of Silk Road’ Publicizes Tell-All Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Convicted Silk Road vendor Maikel Slomp, aka SuperTrips, <a href="https://www.reddit.com/r/onions/comments/rbzhvc/supertrips_the_pablo_escobar_of_silkroad_did_7/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">took to social media</a> recently to promote his new memoir, titled “SuperTrips: The Pablo Escobar of Silkroad.” The book, nearly 200 pages in length, was released for sale on Dec 2 and is already proving to be the subject of some controversy in the darknet market community.</p>



<p>According to a description provided on <a href="https://www.amazon.com/SuperTrips-Escobar-Silkroad-Dane-Spring/dp/B09MYVPVW1/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">Amazon</a>, the book is “a compendium of the experiences of the successful ‘Pablo Escobar of Silk Road’,” a nickname given to Slomp in an <a href="https://www.vocativ.com/underworld/crime/fallen-kingpins-silk-road/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">article</a> published in 2014. The nickname was also part of the headline for a <a href="https://www.vice.com/en/article/4adjaw/i-made-millions-selling-drugs-online-then-it-all-came-crashing-down" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow"><em>Vice</em></a> article which detailed how Slomp had been hospitalized by covid and been released from prison in early April on grounds of compassionate release.</p>



<p>“How else would a simple software programmer who earned meagre sums from gigs, only a month before his exploration in this international business, become a Bitcoin millionaire in a matter of months?” the description posits, before providing an explanation, “The answer is simple, Silk Road!”</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="900" height="450" src="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1.jpg" alt="" class="wp-image-1023" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1.jpg 900w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-300x150.jpg 300w, /wp-content/uploads/2021/12/1-1-768x384.jpg 768w" sizes="(max-width: 900px) 100vw, 900px" /><figcaption><em>Photo of Maikel Slomp, aka SuperTrips. Source: Google+</em></figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>Though Slomp’s numbers as a vendor might be small in comparison to those of modern day darknet pros, his eyewatering estimate of 385,000 BTC received as payment for drug sales was enough for him to earn the title of “Kingpin” by the media. He sold large quantities of MDMA, ecstasy, cocaine, benzodiazepine, amphetamine, LSD, and marijuana from his home country of the Netherlands.</p>



<p>At the height of his career, Slomp decided to retire and sell his Silk Road business to a buyer who had asked to purchase it. The buyer turned out to be an agent from the FBI, who had been on his case since his fingerprints were lifted from a DVD case used to ship product in 2012. Slomp was arrested at the airport in the U.S. and served over seven years in federal prison before his release earlier this year.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Someone claiming to be SuperTrips from Silk Road is on Reddit spruiking a book claiming to be by SuperTrips but he won&#39;t respond to my requests to prove he is SuperTrips. So he may or may not be and I ordered the book anyway</p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1469157888425807876?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">December 10, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Slomp, who seems to enjoy playing off the infamy of his SuperTrips persona, has made personal appeals on both Reddit and Dread, attempting to drum up business for his book. “I’m notorious, and if I can make some money off of that, it’s fine with me,” he told <em>Vice</em> back in April.</p>



<p>Communities from both social media platforms were slow to respond, and the response that trickled in tended to be less than positive.</p>



<p>“Helping feds to build a case vs Ross. That’s a no for me,” said one Redditor, who seemed to speak for the majority of those who were interested. As with similar criticism on Dread, Slomp was quick to respond, absolving himself of responsibility. Although he offered to testify against Ross Ulbricht &#8211; founder of Silk Road &#8211; in exchange for a lesser sentence, Slomp was never called to the witness stand in his trial.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/vendor-proclaimed-escobar-of-silk-road-publicizes-tell-all-book/">Vendor ‘SuperTrips’ Proclaimed ‘Escobar of Silk Road’ Publicizes Tell-All Book</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/vendor-proclaimed-escobar-of-silk-road-publicizes-tell-all-book/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</title>
		<link>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/</link>
					<comments>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 07 Nov 2021 16:35:25 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet arrest]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet market]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[silkroad]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=923</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>A British man who allegedly masterminded the development of Silk Road 2.0 was ordered to forfeit $670,000 in</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/">Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A British man who allegedly masterminded the development of <em>Silk Road 2.0</em> was <a href="https://coinmarketcap.com/alexandria/article/silk-road-boss-told-to-hand-over-670-000-in-btc" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">ordered</a> to forfeit $670,000 in Bitcoin on Wednesday. The order is the result of a financial investigation conducted while suspected admin Thomas White, 26, remains behind bars. White, who went by the online nickname Cthulhu, plead guilty to charges stemming from his admin activities in 2019, for which he was handed a sentence of five and a half years.</p>



<p>The order comes a few days shy of the seventh anniversary of the <a href="https://www.wired.com/2013/11/silk-road/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">takedown</a> of the original <em>Silk Road</em>, of which White was an elevated member. England’s National Crime Agency <a href="https://nationalcybersecuritynews.today/british-administrator-for-darknet-market-silk-road-ordered-to-forfeit-490000-in-bitcoin-science-tech-news-computerhacking-hacking/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">described</a> White as “a well-regarded member of the original Silk Road hierarchy,” using his position of influence in the group and community to establish his own market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">Serious Organised Crime evolves at pace, our response must keep up! Meticulous investigation took down the criminal Dark Web marketplace Silk Road 2.0, now our <br>investigation leads to the confiscation of nearly £0.5m in cryptocurency, the ill gotten gains of this criminal. <a href="https://t.co/kpkF4Sa5vV">https://t.co/kpkF4Sa5vV</a></p>&mdash; Matt Horne Deputy Director Investigations (@MattHorneNCA) <a href="https://twitter.com/MattHorneNCA/status/1455596581105848329?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 2, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>Though investigators remain unsure of the total profits accrued by White as <em>Silk Road 2.0</em> administrator, it is known that he received a commission between 1% and 5% of each sale, without around $96 million in goods traded under his leadership. This amounts to tens of thousands of users.</p>



<p>White had been enrolled in an accounting degree program at a Liverpool university before dropping out to work for <em>Silk Road</em>. He managed to re-open the market under its “2.0” version within a month of the shutdown of the original. The National Crime Agency noted that although he was unemployed at the time, White put up over $11,000 to rent a “plush apartment on Liverpool’s city waterfront” while suspected of operating his market.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-embed is-type-rich is-provider-twitter wp-block-embed-twitter"><div class="wp-block-embed__wrapper">
<blockquote class="twitter-tweet" data-width="550" data-dnt="true"><p lang="en" dir="ltr">7 years ago today&#8230; Silk Road 2.0 was seized, exactly one year after it opened. Soon after, we discovered there had been a Homeland Security officer on staff the whole time <a href="https://t.co/JmxZUL2cuL">pic.twitter.com/JmxZUL2cuL</a></p>&mdash; Eileen Ormsby (@EileenOrmsby) <a href="https://twitter.com/EileenOrmsby/status/1457090624889384962?ref_src=twsrc%5Etfw">November 6, 2021</a></blockquote><script async src="https://platform.twitter.com/widgets.js" charset="utf-8"></script>
</div></figure>



<p>The investigation into White’s finances on the blockchain estimated his fortune to be somewhere between $1.5 and $2 million.</p>



<p>Ross Ulbricht, who was sentenced in 2013 for charges related to his role in constructing and operating <em>Silk Road</em>, continues to serve a life term without the possibility of parole.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/">Investigation into Silk Road 2.0 Admin Finances Reveals Hidden Stash</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/investigation-into-silk-road-2-0-admin-finances-reveals-hidden-stash/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:12:06 by W3 Total Cache
-->