<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>darknet markets &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<atom:link href="/tag/darknet-markets/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>/</link>
	<description>Darknet Markets &#124; Darknet Market News, Reviews and Unbiased Information</description>
	<lastBuildDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:27:51 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=5.9.3</generator>

<image>
	<url>/wp-content/uploads/2021/05/cropped-darknet-markets-logo-32x32.png</url>
	<title>darknet markets &#8211; DarknetMarkets</title>
	<link>/</link>
	<width>32</width>
	<height>32</height>
</image> 
	<item>
		<title>Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</title>
		<link>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/</link>
					<comments>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 01 Apr 2022 10:27:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet markets]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[direct deals]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[nature]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1403</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Darknet markets may serve larger roles economically by acting as catalysts for new trading relationships formed off-market, according</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/">Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Darknet markets may serve larger roles economically by acting as catalysts for new trading relationships formed off-market, according to results of a scientific study released yesterday, March 31<sup>st</sup>.</p>



<p>A new <a href="https://www.nature.com/articles/s41598-022-07492-x" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a> published in <em>Nature</em>, one of the world’s pre-eminent scientific journals, concludes that user-to-user (U2U) cryptocurrency transactions consistently beat darknet market-based transactions in volume &#8212; a trend that has been in tact since the early days of Silk Road.</p>



<p>Researchers at the University of London, The Alan Touring Institute, and <a href="/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Chainalysis</a> analyzed 31 million Bitcoin transactions found to be associated with 40 darknet markets between 2011-2021 and found that volume between direct buyer-seller transactions exceeded that which flowed through the markets themselves, for all 40 of the markets analyzed.</p>



<p>Even though it is characteristic of darknet markets to expressly forbid their vendors from doing off-market deals with buyers, the report found that monthly trading volume between off-market U2U pairs consistently surpassed that of on-market trading volume. To put things in perspective, the researchers found that while $7.5 billion had flowed through the darknet markets analyzed over the last 10 years, the figure traded directly between buyers and sellers during this timeframe approached $30 billion, which is three-fold greater in total amount.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img width="645" height="488" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1405" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1.png 645w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/04/1-300x227.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 645px) 100vw, 645px" /></figure>



<p><em>Dynamics of single-market transaction relationships vs cross-market relationships. Source: Nature</em></p>



<p>The report detailed the process through which a certain percentage of buyers and sellers formed relationships on-market and then slowly moved business off-market, conducting deals directly among themselves. Several of these relationships were found to persist even after the darknet market on which they had formed closed, often exceeding the length of time for which markets were in operation. These “stable pairs” (as referenced in the report) accounted for only 1.7% of all U2U pairs identified yet accounted for 5% of the total $30 billion trading volume.</p>



<p>The report also found that U2U trades have been steadily increasing since the inception of darknet markets and the phenomenon seems to be resilient to any type of macroeconomic setback, only momentarily slowing down once: during the initial panic induced by COVID-19 in first half of 2020. It concludes that law enforcement efforts could possibly be better directed by analyzing the blockchain habits of individual sellers rather than that of whole market operations.</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/">Nature: Off-Market Deals Surpass Markets in Volume Across All Darknet Markets</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/nature-off-market-deals-surpass-markets-in-volume-across-all-darknet-markets/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Chainalysis: 2021 Biggest Year for Darknet Markets Yet</title>
		<link>/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/</link>
					<comments>/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[DNetSEO]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 15:57:38 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Darknet News]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Chainalysis]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[darknet markets]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">/?p=1324</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[<p>Darknet markets had their biggest year yet in 2021, according to a new report by Chainalysis, the blockchain</p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/">Chainalysis: 2021 Biggest Year for Darknet Markets Yet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">Darknet markets</a> had their biggest year yet in 2021, according to a new <a href="https://blog.chainalysis.com/reports/2022-crypto-crime-report-preview-criminal-balances-criminal-whales/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">report</a> by <em>Chainalysis</em>, the blockchain analytics firm. Proceeds received by crypto wallets linked to <a href="/darknet-markets-list/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">darknet market</a> activity jumped 19% year-over-year to its biggest annual total ever – from $1.7 billion in 2020 to $2.1 billion in 2021.</p>



<p>These figures remain relatively small compared to the amount of stolen crypto funds, which jumped from $3 to $11 billion between 2020 and 2021. Most of these funds were stolen in successful hacking and phishing attempts, with proceeds concentrated among a much smaller number of “criminal whales” than darknet market whales.</p>



<p>Criminal whales – defined by Chainalysis as holding more than $1 million in illicitly-obtained cryptocurrency – now own over $25 billion in crypto funds, the report estimates.</p>



<figure class="wp-block-image size-full"><img loading="lazy" width="763" height="426" src="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.png" alt="" class="wp-image-1326" srcset="/wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1.png 763w, /wp-content/uploads/2022/02/1-300x167.png 300w" sizes="(max-width: 763px) 100vw, 763px" /><figcaption>Source: Chainalysis</figcaption></figure>



<p></p>



<p>Chainalysis also monitored the movement of funds belonging 768 criminal whales, plotting them according to times of transacting, and found that most activity occurred between the UTC time zones of 1-4, which suggests the majority of these whale reside in Russia. This also infers that most of the darknet market-associated whales use Hydra, which is based in Russia and is the biggest darknet market in the world.</p>



<p>“The ability to efficiently track criminal whales and quantify their holdings from one public data set is a major difference between cryptocurrency-based crime and fiat-based crime,” concluded Chainalysis in their report, noting that in some ways it is easier to hold crypto criminals accountable for their crimes.</p>



<p>“<em>In fiat, the highest net worth criminals have murky networks of foreign banks and shell corporations to obfuscate their holdings. But in cryptocurrency, transactions are saved on the blockchain for all to see.” – </em>Chainalysis</p>



<p>While use of privacy coin Monero (XMR) makes blockchain analysis much more difficult for law enforcement, Bitcoin (BTC) <a href="https://ambcrypto.com/which-coin-dominates-the-darknet-market-space-surprisingly-its-not-monero/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">still </a><a href="https://ambcrypto.com/which-coin-dominates-the-darknet-market-space-surprisingly-its-not-monero/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener nofollow">d</a><a href="https://ambcrypto.com/which-coin-dominates-the-darknet-market-space-surprisingly-its-not-monero/" target="_blank" rel="noreferrer noopener">ominates</a> darknet markets as the coin of choice, supported by 93% of such markets, as opposed to Monero’s 67%.</p>



<p></p>
<p>The post <a rel="nofollow" href="/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/">Chainalysis: 2021 Biggest Year for Darknet Markets Yet</a> appeared first on <a rel="nofollow" href="/">DarknetMarkets</a>.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>/chainalysis-2021-biggest-year-for-darknet-markets-yet/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>

<!--
Performance optimized by W3 Total Cache. Learn more: https://www.boldgrid.com/w3-total-cache/


Served from: greatstuff.darknetmarkets.com @ 2022-05-01 14:09:18 by W3 Total Cache
-->